const questionPool = {"q1":{"id":"q1","difficulty":0.03226991623,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Canada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Coalition States"},{"id":"a3","text":"Creta"},{"id":"a4","text":"Glubbdubdrib"}]},"q2":{"id":"q2","difficulty":0.05704898763,"question":"The capital of Mexico is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mexico City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Puebla"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ciudad del Carmen"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ecatepec de Morelos"}]},"q3":{"id":"q3","difficulty":0.1264639329,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saudi Arabia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Amestris"},{"id":"a3","text":"Antegria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equestria"}]},"q4":{"id":"q4","difficulty":0.4606135992,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tajikistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belize"}]},"q5":{"id":"q5","difficulty":0.4608451767,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Haiti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q6":{"id":"q6","difficulty":0.4614533304,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cambodia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iran"}]},"q7":{"id":"q7","difficulty":0.4615576253,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iraq","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estonia"}]},"q8":{"id":"q8","difficulty":0.4619475196,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Syria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Denmark"}]},"q9":{"id":"q9","difficulty":0.4622318419,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Honduras","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Italy"}]},"q10":{"id":"q10","difficulty":0.462375095,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cambodia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lithuania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Togo"}]},"q11":{"id":"q11","difficulty":0.4624679014,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burkina Faso","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Blefuscu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Borduria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Buranda"}]},"q12":{"id":"q12","difficulty":0.1277379367,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nepal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bialya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Borduria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Coalition States"}]},"q13":{"id":"q13","difficulty":0.4625123967,"question":"The Cote d'Azur translates to what?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Blue Coast","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Green Coast"},{"id":"a3","text":"Pink Coast"},{"id":"a4","text":"White Coast"}]},"q14":{"id":"q14","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Fes","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Rabat?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Morocco"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burundi"}]},"q15":{"id":"q15","difficulty":0.4629157951,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Andorra","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aurelia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chernarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Earthsea"}]},"q16":{"id":"q16","difficulty":0.4632275424,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nauru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arstotzka"},{"id":"a3","text":"Calbia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kashfar"}]},"q17":{"id":"q17","difficulty":0.463622808,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kazakhstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guinea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lebanon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Portugal"}]},"q18":{"id":"q18","difficulty":0.463674058,"question":"La Manche is the French name for what?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"The English Channel","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a3","text":"The Eurotunnel"},{"id":"a4","text":"The North Sea"}]},"q19":{"id":"q19","difficulty":0.4639118687,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Antigua and Barbuda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"France"}]},"q20":{"id":"q20","difficulty":0.4641129032,"question":"The Indus River runs through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Pakistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Israel"},{"id":"a3","text":"Japan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Myanmar"}]},"q21":{"id":"q21","difficulty":0.1280541796,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Costa Rica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Babar's Kingdom"},{"id":"a3","text":"Carpathia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Latveria"}]},"q22":{"id":"q22","difficulty":0.4642899359,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Bolivia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Quito","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Santa Cruz de la Sierra"},{"id":"a3","text":"El Alto"},{"id":"a4","text":"La Paz"}]},"q23":{"id":"q23","difficulty":0.4643600684,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Switzerland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Italy"}]},"q24":{"id":"q24","difficulty":0.4645953572,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q25":{"id":"q25","difficulty":0.464673989,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sri Lanka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iran"}]},"q26":{"id":"q26","difficulty":0.4654966035,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Algeria?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Durban","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Oran"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tlemcen"},{"id":"a4","text":"Algiers"}]},"q27":{"id":"q27","difficulty":0.4655121424,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Andorra","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gabon"}]},"q28":{"id":"q28","difficulty":0.4661525476,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Botswana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cambodia"}]},"q29":{"id":"q29","difficulty":0.128783088,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Singapore","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cobrastan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equestria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Idris"}]},"q30":{"id":"q30","difficulty":0.4666679458,"question":"The capital of Myanmar is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Naypyidaw","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mandalay"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kuala Lumpur"},{"id":"a4","text":"Manama"}]},"q31":{"id":"q31","difficulty":0.4666679458,"question":"Naypyidaw is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Myanmar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Israel"}]},"q32":{"id":"q32","difficulty":0.4674213384,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saudi Arabia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jordan"}]},"q33":{"id":"q33","difficulty":0.4675399274,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Morocco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Central African Republic"}]},"q34":{"id":"q34","difficulty":0.4676943673,"question":"Phnom Penh is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cambodia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Indonesia"}]},"q35":{"id":"q35","difficulty":0.1289962417,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Peru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brobdingnag"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guilder"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hyrule"}]},"q36":{"id":"q36","difficulty":0.4683157147,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahrain","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estonia"}]},"q37":{"id":"q37","difficulty":0.4685010518,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Cambodia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Phnom Penh","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dubai"},{"id":"a3","text":"Savar Upazila"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sharjah"}]},"q38":{"id":"q38","difficulty":0.4687731781,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tanzania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkmenistan"}]},"q39":{"id":"q39","difficulty":0.469604069,"question":"What is the capital of Kyrgyzstan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bishkek","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Beijing"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jakarta"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kabul"}]},"q40":{"id":"q40","difficulty":0.4699270329,"question":"The capital of Honduras is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tegucigalpa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San Pedro Sula"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kingstown"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kingston"}]},"q41":{"id":"q41","difficulty":0.4699931802,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkey","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Niger"},{"id":"a3","text":"Peru"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sri Lanka"}]},"q42":{"id":"q42","difficulty":0.4701971714,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Kenya?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mombasa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Yaoundé"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malabo"}]},"q43":{"id":"q43","difficulty":0.4703143654,"question":"Tirana is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Albania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q44":{"id":"q44","difficulty":0.4703143654,"question":"What is the capital of Albania?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tirana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Berlin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bratislava"},{"id":"a4","text":"Podgorica"}]},"q45":{"id":"q45","difficulty":0.4704857131,"question":"What is the capital of Morocco?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rabat","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fes"},{"id":"a4","text":"Casablanca"}]},"q46":{"id":"q46","difficulty":0.4706723315,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Germany","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Colombia"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Korea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Venezuela"}]},"q47":{"id":"q47","difficulty":0.1295255017,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Morocco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Corto Maltese"},{"id":"a3","text":"Genosha"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ivalice"}]},"q48":{"id":"q48","difficulty":0.4708958452,"question":"Laos contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vientiane","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Rawalpindi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kabul"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kathmandu"}]},"q49":{"id":"q49","difficulty":0.4709884377,"question":"Sofia is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bulgaria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q50":{"id":"q50","difficulty":0.4710939881,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jamaica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a4","text":"Canada"}]},"q51":{"id":"q51","difficulty":0.4712962188,"question":"The Colossus of Rhodes can be found in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Greece","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malta"}]},"q52":{"id":"q52","difficulty":0.471966038,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Thailand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tanzania"}]},"q53":{"id":"q53","difficulty":0.4723299214,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ecuador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Georgia"}]},"q54":{"id":"q54","difficulty":0.4725734339,"question":"Uzbekistan contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tashkent","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Manila"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nineveh Governorate"},{"id":"a4","text":"Narayanganj"}]},"q55":{"id":"q55","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Hollywood Sign?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Los Angeles","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Davenport"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q56":{"id":"q56","difficulty":0.4726339508,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bolivia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saudi Arabia"}]},"q57":{"id":"q57","difficulty":0.4729026129,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lesotho","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Blefuscu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Farfelu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Halla"}]},"q58":{"id":"q58","difficulty":0.4730412198,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saudi Arabia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Turkey"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkmenistan"}]},"q59":{"id":"q59","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Georgia Dome?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Atlanta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Augusta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q60":{"id":"q60","difficulty":0.474158113,"question":"Sarajevo is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a4","text":"Austria"}]},"q61":{"id":"q61","difficulty":0.474158113,"question":"The capital of Bosnia and Herzegovina is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sarajevo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a3","text":"Moscow"},{"id":"a4","text":"Prague"}]},"q62":{"id":"q62","difficulty":0.474243568,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Senegal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jordan"}]},"q63":{"id":"q63","difficulty":0.4744129929,"question":"Sana'a is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yemen","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iran"}]},"q64":{"id":"q64","difficulty":0.4746265411,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Azerbaijan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Colombia"}]},"q65":{"id":"q65","difficulty":0.4748842098,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mexico"}]},"q66":{"id":"q66","difficulty":0.474967958,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uganda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q67":{"id":"q67","difficulty":0.4750372982,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Haiti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Latvia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Republic of Ireland"}]},"q68":{"id":"q68","difficulty":0.4756548086,"question":"What is the capital of Saudi Arabia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Riyadh","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jeddah"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mecca"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hofuf"}]},"q69":{"id":"q69","difficulty":0.4756608707,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bangladesh","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Colombia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Uganda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yemen"}]},"q70":{"id":"q70","difficulty":0.1327248138,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uruguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aerugo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Buenaventura"},{"id":"a4","text":"Caledonia"}]},"q71":{"id":"q71","difficulty":0.4761937924,"question":"In which country would you find Augusta National Golf Club?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Honduras"}]},"q72":{"id":"q72","difficulty":0.4763089433,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q73":{"id":"q73","difficulty":0.4764418477,"question":"Montevideo is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uruguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q74":{"id":"q74","difficulty":0.4770818115,"question":"What is the dominant religion in the Philippines?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Christianity","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Buddhism"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hindu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Islam"}]},"q75":{"id":"q75","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Maracaibo","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Caracas are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Venezuela"},{"id":"a4","text":"Argentina"}]},"q76":{"id":"q76","difficulty":0.4777499464,"question":"Madagascar contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Antananarivo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Yaoundé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tripoli"}]},"q77":{"id":"q77","difficulty":0.4777575442,"question":"How many African countries have a coastline on the Mediterranean?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"5","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"2"},{"id":"a3","text":"3"},{"id":"a4","text":"4"}]},"q78":{"id":"q78","difficulty":0.478036095,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Haiti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q79":{"id":"q79","difficulty":0.05777188439,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Egypt","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arstotzka"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brobdingnag"},{"id":"a4","text":"Genosha"}]},"q80":{"id":"q80","difficulty":0.1330628985,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominican Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Blefuscu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Earthsea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Metrofulus"}]},"q81":{"id":"q81","difficulty":0.4782191866,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Canada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominica"}]},"q82":{"id":"q82","difficulty":0.4784162437,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Peru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q83":{"id":"q83","difficulty":0.4784868549,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Switzerland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Niger"},{"id":"a4","text":"Syria"}]},"q84":{"id":"q84","difficulty":0.4785812321,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Costa Rica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominica"}]},"q85":{"id":"q85","difficulty":0.4785835958,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bhutan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Georgia"}]},"q86":{"id":"q86","difficulty":0.4786924176,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Benin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saudi Arabia"}]},"q87":{"id":"q87","difficulty":0.4788742023,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Panama","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bhutan"}]},"q88":{"id":"q88","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Whitney Museum of American Art?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"New York City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Austin"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q89":{"id":"q89","difficulty":0.4791617483,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Solomon Islands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea-Bissau"},{"id":"a4","text":"New Zealand"}]},"q90":{"id":"q90","difficulty":0.1336534551,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kenya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arendelle"},{"id":"a3","text":"Calbia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cobra Island"}]},"q91":{"id":"q91","difficulty":0.4794663199,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bangladesh","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Liechtenstein"}]},"q92":{"id":"q92","difficulty":0.4795130451,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Nigeria?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ibadan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Alexandria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mombasa"},{"id":"a4","text":"São Tomé"}]},"q93":{"id":"q93","difficulty":0.479589893,"question":"Which country's capital is Georgetown?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guyana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q94":{"id":"q94","difficulty":0.4796315637,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Swaziland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Saint Lucia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Samoa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Singapore"}]},"q95":{"id":"q95","difficulty":0.4798627158,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Comoros","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Babar's Kingdom"},{"id":"a3","text":"Borduria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Borostyria"}]},"q96":{"id":"q96","difficulty":0.4800984677,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Philippines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q97":{"id":"q97","difficulty":0.1343832414,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Panama?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Panama City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Puebla"},{"id":"a3","text":"Calgary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mexico City"}]},"q98":{"id":"q98","difficulty":0.4804103135,"question":"The capital of Djibouti is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Djibouti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cairo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tripoli"}]},"q99":{"id":"q99","difficulty":0.4804984007,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bhutan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q100":{"id":"q100","difficulty":0.4805247022,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"India"}]},"q101":{"id":"q101","difficulty":0.4810207862,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Arab Emirates","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jamaica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovenia"}]},"q102":{"id":"q102","difficulty":0.4811348042,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Solomon Islands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sri Lanka"}]},"q103":{"id":"q103","difficulty":0.481571505,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kuwait"}]},"q104":{"id":"q104","difficulty":0.1345771291,"question":"What country borders the United States to the south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mexico","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cruzeiro"},{"id":"a3","text":"Houston"},{"id":"a4","text":"New York"}]},"q105":{"id":"q105","difficulty":0.481813404,"question":"What is the capital of Bahamas?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nassau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guatemala City"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kingstown"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mexico City"}]},"q106":{"id":"q106","difficulty":0.482049793,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bahamas"}]},"q107":{"id":"q107","difficulty":0.4821305468,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkey","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"Liechtenstein"}]},"q108":{"id":"q108","difficulty":0.4825710369,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Togo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bulgaria"}]},"q109":{"id":"q109","difficulty":0.4826959621,"question":"Riyadh is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saudi Arabia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brunei"}]},"q110":{"id":"q110","difficulty":0.4829573085,"question":"Ethiopia contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Axum","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cairo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Luanda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Marrakesh"}]},"q111":{"id":"q111","difficulty":0.4833180227,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Afghanistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nigeria"}]},"q112":{"id":"q112","difficulty":0.4833385131,"question":"Andorra la Vella is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Andorra","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Latvia"}]},"q113":{"id":"q113","difficulty":0.483463249,"question":"The capital of Malta is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Valletta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dublin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lisbon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Madrid"}]},"q114":{"id":"q114","difficulty":0.1351889783,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bulgaria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Blefuscu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equestria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kangan"}]},"q115":{"id":"q115","difficulty":0.483463249,"question":"Valletta is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a4","text":"Croatia"}]},"q116":{"id":"q116","difficulty":0.4836298801,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Lucia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Azerbaijan"}]},"q117":{"id":"q117","difficulty":0.4836586494,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Bolivia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"El Alto","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brasília"},{"id":"a4","text":"Maracaibo"}]},"q118":{"id":"q118","difficulty":0.4837165015,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saudi Arabia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"}]},"q119":{"id":"q119","difficulty":0.4841962832,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vanuatu","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Axphain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Emmeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hyrule"}]},"q120":{"id":"q120","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Trump Tower?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"New York City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Atlanta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q121":{"id":"q121","difficulty":0.4849199572,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jordan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Benin"}]},"q122":{"id":"q122","difficulty":0.4849952963,"question":"In which of these countries could you see the Niger River?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mali","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mozambique"}]},"q123":{"id":"q123","difficulty":0.4852369585,"question":"The capital of Nicaragua is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Managua","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kingstown"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mexico City"},{"id":"a4","text":"St. John's"}]},"q124":{"id":"q124","difficulty":0.4852369585,"question":"Managua is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nicaragua","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Costa Rica"}]},"q125":{"id":"q125","difficulty":0.4853921551,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sierra Leone","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Djibouti"}]},"q126":{"id":"q126","difficulty":0.4854374581,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belize","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Germany"}]},"q127":{"id":"q127","difficulty":0.4855592508,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"}]},"q128":{"id":"q128","difficulty":0.4856560993,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Luxembourg","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mongolia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Singapore"}]},"q129":{"id":"q129","difficulty":0.4857606415,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Benin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q130":{"id":"q130","difficulty":0.1394622714,"question":"Which of these rivers is the longest?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nile","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Paraná River"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mississippi River"},{"id":"a4","text":"Niger River"}]},"q131":{"id":"q131","difficulty":0.4864950433,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Sudan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cape Town","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Khartoum"},{"id":"a3","text":"Khartoum North"},{"id":"a4","text":"Omdurman"}]},"q132":{"id":"q132","difficulty":0.4867268596,"question":"Muscat is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Oman","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bhutan"}]},"q133":{"id":"q133","difficulty":0.4867268596,"question":"The capital of Oman is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Muscat","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Manila"},{"id":"a3","text":"Beirut"},{"id":"a4","text":"Amman"}]},"q134":{"id":"q134","difficulty":0.4868823625,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Papua New Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gambia"}]},"q135":{"id":"q135","difficulty":0.4869667815,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Myanmar?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mandalay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dhi Qar Governorate"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mashhad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Limbuwan"}]},"q136":{"id":"q136","difficulty":0.4869976223,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Palau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Italy"}]},"q137":{"id":"q137","difficulty":0.4873460605,"question":"The capital of Ethiopia is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Addis Ababa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Axum"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yaoundé"}]},"q138":{"id":"q138","difficulty":0.1405149219,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Arab Emirates","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Axphain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bangalla"},{"id":"a4","text":"Earthsea"}]},"q139":{"id":"q139","difficulty":0.4875024471,"question":"The capital of Lithuania is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vilnius","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Lisbon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Paris"},{"id":"a4","text":"Prague"}]},"q140":{"id":"q140","difficulty":0.48760138,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Palau"},{"id":"a4","text":"Solomon Islands"}]},"q141":{"id":"q141","difficulty":0.4876248194,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Estonia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Benin"}]},"q142":{"id":"q142","difficulty":0.4877156657,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Afghanistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iran"},{"id":"a4","text":"Israel"}]},"q143":{"id":"q143","difficulty":0.4877872594,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Panama","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"North Korea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Suriname"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q144":{"id":"q144","difficulty":0.488324691,"question":"The capital of Belarus is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Minsk","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kiev"},{"id":"a4","text":"Madrid"}]},"q145":{"id":"q145","difficulty":0.488324691,"question":"Minsk is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belarus","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Austria"}]},"q146":{"id":"q146","difficulty":0.1416666667,"question":"In which of these countries could you find the Rocky Mountains?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a3","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Haiti"}]},"q147":{"id":"q147","difficulty":0.4887417613,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gabon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lesotho"}]},"q148":{"id":"q148","difficulty":0.4887930043,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"North Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"Spain"}]},"q149":{"id":"q149","difficulty":null,"question":"Bondi Beach can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Sydney","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" Australia\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Calgary"},{"id":"a4","text":" Canada\""}]},"q150":{"id":"q150","difficulty":0.4890975503,"question":"Which country's capital is Ulaanbaatar?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mongolia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iran"},{"id":"a4","text":"Israel"}]},"q151":{"id":"q151","difficulty":0.4890975503,"question":"The capital of Mongolia is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ulaanbaatar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Baku"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jerusalem"},{"id":"a4","text":"Islamabad"}]},"q152":{"id":"q152","difficulty":0.4893816957,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uruguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eritrea"}]},"q153":{"id":"q153","difficulty":0.4902749405,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"El Salvador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lebanon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q154":{"id":"q154","difficulty":0.4904724172,"question":"Vietnam does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Karaj","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Can Tho"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hanoi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ho Chi Minh City"}]},"q155":{"id":"q155","difficulty":0.4923417353,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Antigua and Barbuda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belize"}]},"q156":{"id":"q156","difficulty":0.4925815809,"question":"Tashkent is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uzbekistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Israel"}]},"q157":{"id":"q157","difficulty":0.4925815809,"question":"What is the capital of Uzbekistan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tashkent","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Baghdad"},{"id":"a3","text":"Damascus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kathmandu"}]},"q158":{"id":"q158","difficulty":0.4926856881,"question":"What is the capital of Sudan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Khartoum","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Khartoum North"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malabo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Conakry"}]},"q159":{"id":"q159","difficulty":0.05953474722,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"North Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Creta"},{"id":"a3","text":"Eagleland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Glubbdubdrib"}]},"q160":{"id":"q160","difficulty":null,"question":"Hollywood Boulevard can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Los Angeles","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Atlanta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q161":{"id":"q161","difficulty":0.4926856881,"question":"Khartoum is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equatorial Guinea"}]},"q162":{"id":"q162","difficulty":0.4926934318,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Trinidad and Tobago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belize"}]},"q163":{"id":"q163","difficulty":0.4927338091,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gabon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"France"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kenya"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Sudan"}]},"q164":{"id":"q164","difficulty":0.4931530205,"question":"Which country's capital is Tripoli?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Libya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cape Verde"}]},"q165":{"id":"q165","difficulty":0.4931530205,"question":"The capital of Libya is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tripoli","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benghazi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Luanda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kinshasa"}]},"q166":{"id":"q166","difficulty":0.4932605895,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a3","text":"Netherlands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sri Lanka"}]},"q167":{"id":"q167","difficulty":0.493278723,"question":"Which of these is a major road junction in south London?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Elephant and Castle","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Giraffe and Cathedral"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gorilla and Courtyard"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lion and Cul-de-Sac"}]},"q168":{"id":"q168","difficulty":0.4936456964,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belize","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Singapore"}]},"q169":{"id":"q169","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Whiteface Mountain?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Wilmington","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Long Beach"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q170":{"id":"q170","difficulty":0.1449431225,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Papua New Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arendelle"},{"id":"a3","text":"Earthsea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estoccia"}]},"q171":{"id":"q171","difficulty":0.4944382575,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Haiti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a4","text":"Canada"}]},"q172":{"id":"q172","difficulty":0.4945517915,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Venezuela","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Libya"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q173":{"id":"q173","difficulty":0.4947192283,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Eritrea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ghana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"Paraguay"}]},"q174":{"id":"q174","difficulty":0.494739629,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jamaica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Lucia"},{"id":"a4","text":"San Marino"}]},"q175":{"id":"q175","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Willis Tower?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Chicago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Atlanta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q176":{"id":"q176","difficulty":0.494910775,"question":"What is the capital of Luxembourg?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Luxembourg City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Berlin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bratislava"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dublin"}]},"q177":{"id":"q177","difficulty":0.494910775,"question":"Which country's capital is Luxembourg City?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Luxembourg","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belarus"}]},"q178":{"id":"q178","difficulty":0.4951105226,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Egypt"}]},"q179":{"id":"q179","difficulty":0.4956908903,"question":"Guangzhou Baiyun is a major airport in which Asian country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"China","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"India"},{"id":"a3","text":"Japan"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Korea"}]},"q180":{"id":"q180","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Santa Cruz de la Sierra","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and La Paz are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Argentina"}]},"q181":{"id":"q181","difficulty":0.496566933,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a4","text":"France"}]},"q182":{"id":"q182","difficulty":0.4965706447,"question":"What name was given to the Rocky Mountain trail used by settlers traveling to the Pacific in the 1840's?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Oregon Trail","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Idaho Trail"},{"id":"a3","text":"Montana Trail"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ohio Trail"}]},"q183":{"id":"q183","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Mandalay","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Yangon are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Myanmar"},{"id":"a4","text":"China"}]},"q184":{"id":"q184","difficulty":0.4968972457,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iran","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cambodia"}]},"q185":{"id":"q185","difficulty":0.1456277159,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paraguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Amestris"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kumbolaland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kyrzbekistan"}]},"q186":{"id":"q186","difficulty":0.4969322229,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Eritrea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Borduria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Carpathia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estovakia"}]},"q187":{"id":"q187","difficulty":0.4979297174,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Barbados","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nauru"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"},{"id":"a4","text":"San Marino"}]},"q188":{"id":"q188","difficulty":0.4980726117,"question":"The North Island and which other Moai island make up New Zealand?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Island","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Sandy Island"},{"id":"a3","text":"Starry Island"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sunny Island"}]},"q189":{"id":"q189","difficulty":0.4982712161,"question":"Rabat is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Morocco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Congo"}]},"q190":{"id":"q190","difficulty":0.498341705,"question":"Yerevan is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Armenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q191":{"id":"q191","difficulty":0.4990627422,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Laos","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q192":{"id":"q192","difficulty":0.4990697097,"question":"Angkor Wat can be found in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cambodia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iran"}]},"q193":{"id":"q193","difficulty":0.1461167162,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Algeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangalla"},{"id":"a3","text":"Eagleland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gondor"}]},"q194":{"id":"q194","difficulty":0.4992912356,"question":"Tunisia contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tunis","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Yaoundé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kano"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lubumbashi"}]},"q195":{"id":"q195","difficulty":0.4994720251,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lesotho"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malawi"}]},"q196":{"id":"q196","difficulty":0.4996243426,"question":"Which of these cities is in the Mojave Desert?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Las Vegas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chicago"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mexico City"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tombstone"}]},"q197":{"id":"q197","difficulty":0.4997303775,"question":"In which of these countries could you see the Lena River?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Russia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moldova"}]},"q198":{"id":"q198","difficulty":0.500198865,"question":"What is the capital of Yemen?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sana'a","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Beijing"},{"id":"a3","text":"Baku"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jakarta"}]},"q199":{"id":"q199","difficulty":0.5004477232,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paraguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominica"}]},"q200":{"id":"q200","difficulty":0.5005140305,"question":"The capital of Bhutan is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Thimphu","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Baghdad"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kuala Lumpur"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tokyo"}]},"q201":{"id":"q201","difficulty":0.5007068524,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Zambia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lusaka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Alexandria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sharm El Sheikh"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tlemcen"}]},"q202":{"id":"q202","difficulty":0.5008119324,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Colombia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Japan"}]},"q203":{"id":"q203","difficulty":0.5008136896,"question":"The capital of Mauritius is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Port Louis","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a4","text":"Luanda"}]},"q204":{"id":"q204","difficulty":0.5015474678,"question":"Kampala is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uganda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Congo"}]},"q205":{"id":"q205","difficulty":0.5015478613,"question":"Morocco contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Salé","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ibadan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lubumbashi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tripoli"}]},"q206":{"id":"q206","difficulty":0.501588221,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bhutan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guatemala"},{"id":"a4","text":"Suriname"}]},"q207":{"id":"q207","difficulty":0.5023086009,"question":"Whistler Blackcomb can be found in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Canada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Haiti"}]},"q208":{"id":"q208","difficulty":0.5028624252,"question":"Bridgetown is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Barbados","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guatemala"}]},"q209":{"id":"q209","difficulty":0.1462622912,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Australia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mexico"},{"id":"a4","text":"Somalia"}]},"q210":{"id":"q210","difficulty":0.5032992967,"question":"Mogadishu is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Somalia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gambia"}]},"q211":{"id":"q211","difficulty":0.5032992967,"question":"What is the capital of Somalia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mogadishu","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Hargeisa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Luanda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dakar"}]},"q212":{"id":"q212","difficulty":0.5033592781,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bulgaria"}]},"q213":{"id":"q213","difficulty":0.5035202385,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Albania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mauritius"}]},"q214":{"id":"q214","difficulty":0.5036951471,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Libya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q215":{"id":"q215","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Chittagong","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Bogra are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bhutan"}]},"q216":{"id":"q216","difficulty":0.148572654,"question":"What is the capital of United Kingdom?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"London","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Lisbon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Prague"},{"id":"a4","text":"Rome"}]},"q217":{"id":"q217","difficulty":0.5039585553,"question":"Kinshasa is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ethiopia"}]},"q218":{"id":"q218","difficulty":0.5041993756,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Netherlands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q219":{"id":"q219","difficulty":0.5047219927,"question":"The capital of Georgia is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tbilisi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bratislava"},{"id":"a3","text":"Helsinki"},{"id":"a4","text":"London"}]},"q220":{"id":"q220","difficulty":0.5048125638,"question":"What is the capital of Uganda?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kampala","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Moroni"},{"id":"a3","text":"Luanda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nairobi"}]},"q221":{"id":"q221","difficulty":0.5050006091,"question":"The capital of Latvia is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Riga","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Berlin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Copenhagen"},{"id":"a4","text":"Helsinki"}]},"q222":{"id":"q222","difficulty":0.1490683857,"question":"The Moscow Kremlin can be found in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Russia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a4","text":"Portugal"}]},"q223":{"id":"q223","difficulty":0.5057442242,"question":"In which city is the skyscraper Petronas Towers located?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kuala Lumpur","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dubai"},{"id":"a3","text":"New York"},{"id":"a4","text":"Shanghai"}]},"q224":{"id":"q224","difficulty":0.5062950432,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Benin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangalla"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guilder"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kashfar"}]},"q225":{"id":"q225","difficulty":0.506310386,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uganda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Japan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Russia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q226":{"id":"q226","difficulty":0.5073326451,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Singapore","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Japan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jordan"}]},"q227":{"id":"q227","difficulty":0.5073515206,"question":"Libya contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tripoli","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Moroni"},{"id":"a3","text":"Axum"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nairobi"}]},"q228":{"id":"q228","difficulty":0.5078722457,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vietnam","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lesotho"}]},"q229":{"id":"q229","difficulty":0.1497307106,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q230":{"id":"q230","difficulty":0.5079095541,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"El Salvador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burundi"}]},"q231":{"id":"q231","difficulty":0.5079237721,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Moldova"},{"id":"a4","text":"Panama"}]},"q232":{"id":"q232","difficulty":0.5080000088,"question":"Which country's capital is Asunción?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paraguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q233":{"id":"q233","difficulty":0.5080637852,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Poland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Montenegro"}]},"q234":{"id":"q234","difficulty":0.5085696157,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Timor-Leste","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Egypt"}]},"q235":{"id":"q235","difficulty":0.5091474781,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Moldova","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q236":{"id":"q236","difficulty":0.509184862,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Egypt","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Indonesia"}]},"q237":{"id":"q237","difficulty":0.0618758935,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Russia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chernarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Deltora"},{"id":"a4","text":"Elbonia"}]},"q238":{"id":"q238","difficulty":0.5101117115,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Kyrgyzstan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bishkek","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Damascus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jakarta"},{"id":"a4","text":"Narayanganj"}]},"q239":{"id":"q239","difficulty":0.5101340123,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tanzania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Libya"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q240":{"id":"q240","difficulty":0.510610062,"question":"Tanzania contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mbeya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Casablanca"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tripoli"}]},"q241":{"id":"q241","difficulty":0.5106511744,"question":"The capital of Liechtenstein is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vaduz","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Berlin"},{"id":"a3","text":"London"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lisbon"}]},"q242":{"id":"q242","difficulty":0.5107167392,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"},{"id":"a4","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe"}]},"q243":{"id":"q243","difficulty":0.5109924911,"question":"Which of these would you not associate with Denmark?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Pasta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bacon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hans Christian Andersen"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vikings"}]},"q244":{"id":"q244","difficulty":0.5110074048,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Austria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a4","text":"France"}]},"q245":{"id":"q245","difficulty":0.5110220727,"question":"What is the capital of Slovenia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ljubljana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bratislava"},{"id":"a3","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiev"}]},"q246":{"id":"q246","difficulty":0.5110220727,"question":"Which country's capital is Ljubljana?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q247":{"id":"q247","difficulty":0.1499942185,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Somalia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arendelle"},{"id":"a3","text":"Atlantis"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equestria"}]},"q248":{"id":"q248","difficulty":0.5112136417,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"France","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Peru"},{"id":"a4","text":"Syria"}]},"q249":{"id":"q249","difficulty":0.5113659839,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Romania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iran"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q250":{"id":"q250","difficulty":0.5113848181,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Timor-Leste","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Denmark"}]},"q251":{"id":"q251","difficulty":0.5115189311,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sierra Leone","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q252":{"id":"q252","difficulty":0.5115636096,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yemen","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Africa"}]},"q253":{"id":"q253","difficulty":0.5118497999,"question":"Which European country has not had a monarch for over 200 years?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"France","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belgium"},{"id":"a3","text":"Netherlands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Spain"}]},"q254":{"id":"q254","difficulty":0.5120043284,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea-Bissau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Sudan"}]},"q255":{"id":"q255","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find New Jersey Performing Arts Center?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Newark","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Los Angeles"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q256":{"id":"q256","difficulty":0.5122061679,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Libya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lesotho"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q257":{"id":"q257","difficulty":0.1501680394,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kazakhstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Elbonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gondour"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guilder"}]},"q258":{"id":"q258","difficulty":0.5127569315,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Haiti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tonga"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vanuatu"}]},"q259":{"id":"q259","difficulty":0.5132918697,"question":"Ashgabat is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkmenistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Japan"}]},"q260":{"id":"q260","difficulty":0.5132918697,"question":"What is the capital of Turkmenistan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ashgabat","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bishkek"},{"id":"a3","text":"Baku"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kuala Lumpur"}]},"q261":{"id":"q261","difficulty":0.5134389859,"question":"What city is located where the Mississippi meets the Missouri river?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"St. Louis","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Atlanta"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chicago"},{"id":"a4","text":"Indianapolis"}]},"q262":{"id":"q262","difficulty":0.5136897003,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"San Marino","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Costa Rica"}]},"q263":{"id":"q263","difficulty":0.5138680128,"question":"Which country's capital is Harare?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zimbabwe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Congo"}]},"q264":{"id":"q264","difficulty":0.5138998139,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mexico","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Congo"}]},"q265":{"id":"q265","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Union Square?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"San Francisco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Austin"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q266":{"id":"q266","difficulty":0.1502041669,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kazakhstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q267":{"id":"q267","difficulty":0.5144153784,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nicaragua","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Rwanda"}]},"q268":{"id":"q268","difficulty":0.5146844589,"question":"Which building did Parisians capture at the start of The French Revolution?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"The Bastille","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Notre-Dame Cathedral"},{"id":"a3","text":"Palace of Versailles"},{"id":"a4","text":"The Louvre Museum"}]},"q269":{"id":"q269","difficulty":0.5148652002,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paraguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q270":{"id":"q270","difficulty":null,"question":"St Paul's Cathedral can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"London","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" UK\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Agra"},{"id":"a4","text":" India\""}]},"q271":{"id":"q271","difficulty":0.5149964448,"question":"The capital of Montenegro is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Podgorica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dublin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kiev"},{"id":"a4","text":"London"}]},"q272":{"id":"q272","difficulty":0.5151808623,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritius","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chad"}]},"q273":{"id":"q273","difficulty":0.5152319521,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Azerbaijan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Baku","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aleppo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mandalay"},{"id":"a4","text":"Icheon"}]},"q274":{"id":"q274","difficulty":0.5152905356,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Myanmar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Botswana"}]},"q275":{"id":"q275","difficulty":0.5155934605,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Syria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Japan"}]},"q276":{"id":"q276","difficulty":null,"question":"Big Ben can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"London","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" UK\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Ascot"},{"id":"a4","text":" UK\""}]},"q277":{"id":"q277","difficulty":0.5157396337,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritius","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tonga"}]},"q278":{"id":"q278","difficulty":0.516128915,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Democratic Republic of the Congo?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dakar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Goma"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kananga"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kinshasa"}]},"q279":{"id":"q279","difficulty":0.5165959391,"question":"Which country's capital is Bratislava?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovakia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Denmark"}]},"q280":{"id":"q280","difficulty":0.5172058164,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Romania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Italy"}]},"q281":{"id":"q281","difficulty":0.5173218161,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cameroon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mauritania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nigeria"}]},"q282":{"id":"q282","difficulty":0.5175543019,"question":"What is the DLR in London?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Overland Tube Line","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"A Bar"},{"id":"a3","text":"A Degree Course"},{"id":"a4","text":"A Road"}]},"q283":{"id":"q283","difficulty":0.1519068391,"question":"What is the capital of Australia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Canberra","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brisbane"},{"id":"a3","text":"Perth"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ngerulmud"}]},"q284":{"id":"q284","difficulty":0.5175940688,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Czech Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jamaica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Timor-Leste"}]},"q285":{"id":"q285","difficulty":0.5177555888,"question":"What is the capital of Tanzania?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dodoma","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dar es Salaam"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mbeya"}]},"q286":{"id":"q286","difficulty":0.5177555888,"question":"Dodoma is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tanzania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"}]},"q287":{"id":"q287","difficulty":0.5183766643,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Suriname","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jamaica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Norway"}]},"q288":{"id":"q288","difficulty":0.5184452803,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominica"}]},"q289":{"id":"q289","difficulty":0.1522081671,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Czech Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Earthsea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Genovia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kazirstan"}]},"q290":{"id":"q290","difficulty":0.5187867324,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Angola?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Luanda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cairo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Casablanca"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hargeisa"}]},"q291":{"id":"q291","difficulty":0.5189799191,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burkina Faso","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Germany"}]},"q292":{"id":"q292","difficulty":0.5191540929,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Eritrea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guatemala"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sri Lanka"}]},"q293":{"id":"q293","difficulty":0.5192863157,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liberia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Panama"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sierra Leone"},{"id":"a4","text":"Togo"}]},"q294":{"id":"q294","difficulty":0.5193358161,"question":"Which country's capital is Port Moresby?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Papua New Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiribati"}]},"q295":{"id":"q295","difficulty":0.51953125,"question":"In which city is the Juilliard School of dance and drama?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"New York","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Boston"},{"id":"a3","text":"Paris"},{"id":"a4","text":"Rome"}]},"q296":{"id":"q296","difficulty":0.5196309841,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Libya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Venezuela"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zimbabwe"}]},"q297":{"id":"q297","difficulty":0.5196867799,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tonga","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Palau"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tuvalu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q298":{"id":"q298","difficulty":0.5197892241,"question":"In what country is the wooded mountain range known as Schwarzwald located?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Germany","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Romania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Spain"}]},"q299":{"id":"q299","difficulty":0.1538671976,"question":"Rome is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Italy","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q300":{"id":"q300","difficulty":0.5198457855,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Samoa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Palau"}]},"q301":{"id":"q301","difficulty":0.5198664172,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Croatia"}]},"q302":{"id":"q302","difficulty":0.520384343,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bahrain"}]},"q303":{"id":"q303","difficulty":0.5204128525,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tajikistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kazakhstan"}]},"q304":{"id":"q304","difficulty":0.5204977935,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Singapore","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"Croatia"}]},"q305":{"id":"q305","difficulty":0.520904124,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bolivia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cameroon"}]},"q306":{"id":"q306","difficulty":0.5210735373,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Singapore","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Rwanda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovakia"}]},"q307":{"id":"q307","difficulty":0.5213150642,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q308":{"id":"q308","difficulty":null,"question":"Bridgestone Arena can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Nashville","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Atlanta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q309":{"id":"q309","difficulty":0.5218457944,"question":"In which of these countries could you see the Yukon River?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Canada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guatemala"}]},"q310":{"id":"q310","difficulty":0.5219204684,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belize","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kiribati"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q311":{"id":"q311","difficulty":0.522285587,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Honduras","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Canada"}]},"q312":{"id":"q312","difficulty":0.5223084814,"question":"The Great Barrier Reef has its own what?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Post box","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Car Wash"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fish and Chip Shop"},{"id":"a4","text":"Supermarket"}]},"q313":{"id":"q313","difficulty":0.5226910292,"question":"Suva is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Fiji","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Marshall Islands"}]},"q314":{"id":"q314","difficulty":0.522708983,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominican Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brunei"}]},"q315":{"id":"q315","difficulty":null,"question":"What colors are the three horizontal fields on the flag of Bolivia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Red","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" yellow and green\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Green"},{"id":"a4","text":" brown and blue\""}]},"q316":{"id":"q316","difficulty":0.5228318255,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Montenegro","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guyana"}]},"q317":{"id":"q317","difficulty":0.5228578578,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovakia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Rwanda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tonga"}]},"q318":{"id":"q318","difficulty":0.1547509637,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brazil","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mexico"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tanzania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ukraine"}]},"q319":{"id":"q319","difficulty":0.5233017029,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malawi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Korea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uzbekistan"}]},"q320":{"id":"q320","difficulty":0.5234004662,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Colombia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Netherlands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yemen"}]},"q321":{"id":"q321","difficulty":null,"question":"Shoreline Amphitheatre can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Mountain View","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Angkor"},{"id":"a4","text":" Cambodia\""}]},"q322":{"id":"q322","difficulty":0.5236756896,"question":"Zimbabwe contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Harare","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cairo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Victoria"}]},"q323":{"id":"q323","difficulty":0.5240071746,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Denmark","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q324":{"id":"q324","difficulty":0.5242015117,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bulgaria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a4","text":"Austria"}]},"q325":{"id":"q325","difficulty":0.5242745084,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Georgia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tbilisi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Severovýchod"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hamburg"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moscow"}]},"q326":{"id":"q326","difficulty":0.06187944012,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Netherlands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Borostyria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Corto Maltese"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ivalice"}]},"q327":{"id":"q327","difficulty":0.1563066455,"question":"Which country's capital is Seoul?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kuwait"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malaysia"}]},"q328":{"id":"q328","difficulty":0.5244660392,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nepal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Sudan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q329":{"id":"q329","difficulty":0.5244767143,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burundi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belarus"}]},"q330":{"id":"q330","difficulty":0.5246017955,"question":"Which country's capital is Astana?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kazakhstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Israel"}]},"q331":{"id":"q331","difficulty":0.5246017955,"question":"The capital of Kazakhstan is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Astana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Almaty"},{"id":"a3","text":"Baghdad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Damascus"}]},"q332":{"id":"q332","difficulty":0.5246103203,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iraq","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mozambique"}]},"q333":{"id":"q333","difficulty":0.5246842283,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q334":{"id":"q334","difficulty":0.5247465076,"question":"Togo contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lomé","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Alexandria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cairo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Khartoum"}]},"q335":{"id":"q335","difficulty":0.1566114999,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Armenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Atlantis"},{"id":"a3","text":"Aurelia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cagliostro"}]},"q336":{"id":"q336","difficulty":0.5247679054,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"North Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Indonesia"}]},"q337":{"id":"q337","difficulty":null,"question":"The New England Aquarium can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Boston","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Athens"},{"id":"a4","text":" Greece\""}]},"q338":{"id":"q338","difficulty":0.5253054695,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Latvia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Congo"}]},"q339":{"id":"q339","difficulty":0.5254343319,"question":"The capital of Azerbaijan is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Baku","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Manila"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jakarta"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kuala Lumpur"}]},"q340":{"id":"q340","difficulty":0.5256592592,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bahamas"}]},"q341":{"id":"q341","difficulty":0.5258640347,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guatemala","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a4","text":"Canada"}]},"q342":{"id":"q342","difficulty":0.1567073197,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mexico","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q343":{"id":"q343","difficulty":0.5260580277,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Nigeria?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Fes","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin City"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kano"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kaduna"}]},"q344":{"id":"q344","difficulty":0.5264623932,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mongolia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Norway"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkmenistan"}]},"q345":{"id":"q345","difficulty":null,"question":"In which US city can you visit the National Gallery of Art and its Sculpture Garden?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Washington","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" D.C.\""},{"id":"a3","text":"Atlanta"},{"id":"a4","text":"New Orleans"}]},"q346":{"id":"q346","difficulty":0.5267488896,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jordan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Japan"}]},"q347":{"id":"q347","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Lubumbashi","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Kinshasa?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Angola"}]},"q348":{"id":"q348","difficulty":0.5271687191,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mozambique","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cape Verde"}]},"q349":{"id":"q349","difficulty":0.5272695967,"question":"Yaoundé is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cameroon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eritrea"}]},"q350":{"id":"q350","difficulty":0.527560605,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Montenegro","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Lucia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Singapore"}]},"q351":{"id":"q351","difficulty":0.157008986,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sri Lanka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangalla"},{"id":"a3","text":"Caledonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Grand Fenwick"}]},"q352":{"id":"q352","difficulty":0.5279497013,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Colombia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q353":{"id":"q353","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Gunstock Mountain Resort?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Gilford","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Bozeman"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q354":{"id":"q354","difficulty":0.5282324379,"question":"Which of these landmarks is not in London?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Balmoral Castle","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Globe Theatre"},{"id":"a3","text":"Natural History Museum"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tower Bridge"}]},"q355":{"id":"q355","difficulty":0.5282439488,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Central African Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q356":{"id":"q356","difficulty":0.528248065,"question":"Thimphu is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bhutan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bangladesh"}]},"q357":{"id":"q357","difficulty":0.5282832498,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uruguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q358":{"id":"q358","difficulty":null,"question":"Bridger Bowl Ski Area can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Bozeman","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Augusta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q359":{"id":"q359","difficulty":0.1573294193,"question":"How many presidents' faces are carved into Mount Rushmore?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"4","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"104"},{"id":"a3","text":"40"},{"id":"a4","text":"44"}]},"q360":{"id":"q360","difficulty":0.5287086916,"question":"The capital of Senegal is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dakar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Khartoum"},{"id":"a4","text":"Juba"}]},"q361":{"id":"q361","difficulty":0.5289016345,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Niger?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Niamey","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mombasa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Benghazi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cairo"}]},"q362":{"id":"q362","difficulty":0.5291689598,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Egypt","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Korea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Spain"}]},"q363":{"id":"q363","difficulty":0.5291771534,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Solomon Islands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q364":{"id":"q364","difficulty":0.5293734185,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Oman","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"France"},{"id":"a3","text":"Turkmenistan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yemen"}]},"q365":{"id":"q365","difficulty":0.5294057243,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Uganda?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kampala","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ibadan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bouaké"},{"id":"a4","text":"Marrakesh"}]},"q366":{"id":"q366","difficulty":0.5299913717,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Thailand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Pakistan"}]},"q367":{"id":"q367","difficulty":0.1578706689,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Argentina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q368":{"id":"q368","difficulty":0.5302097904,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Haiti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Madagascar"},{"id":"a3","text":"Poland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Romania"}]},"q369":{"id":"q369","difficulty":0.5302362587,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Oman","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cambodia"}]},"q370":{"id":"q370","difficulty":0.5303465019,"question":"Which country's capital is Bamako?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mali","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"}]},"q371":{"id":"q371","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Benin City","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Kano?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q372":{"id":"q372","difficulty":0.5309155835,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yemen","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q373":{"id":"q373","difficulty":0.5309299735,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tunisia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chad"}]},"q374":{"id":"q374","difficulty":0.5309951135,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Armenia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yerevan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Helsinki"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Petersburg"},{"id":"a4","text":"Warsaw"}]},"q375":{"id":"q375","difficulty":0.158484196,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cambodia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arstotzka"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bangalla"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiore"}]},"q376":{"id":"q376","difficulty":0.5316876924,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahrain","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malaysia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nauru"}]},"q377":{"id":"q377","difficulty":0.5316997873,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ethiopia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"}]},"q378":{"id":"q378","difficulty":0.5318821406,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Equatorial Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q379":{"id":"q379","difficulty":0.5321606098,"question":"Vilnius is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lithuania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a4","text":"Austria"}]},"q380":{"id":"q380","difficulty":0.5324373389,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bangladesh","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malawi"}]},"q381":{"id":"q381","difficulty":0.5326120922,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paraguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Latvia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mauritania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Namibia"}]},"q382":{"id":"q382","difficulty":0.1586155894,"question":"The capital of Cuba is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Havana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guatemala City"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nassau"},{"id":"a4","text":"St. John's"}]},"q383":{"id":"q383","difficulty":0.532784343,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Mali?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bamako","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin City"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nairobi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mfoundi"}]},"q384":{"id":"q384","difficulty":0.5328592489,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Honduras","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malawi"}]},"q385":{"id":"q385","difficulty":0.5328609967,"question":"The capital of Angola is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Luanda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Pretoria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tripoli"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malabo"}]},"q386":{"id":"q386","difficulty":0.5331005223,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Eritrea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q387":{"id":"q387","difficulty":0.5331718696,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burundi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saudi Arabia"}]},"q388":{"id":"q388","difficulty":0.5335771748,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Namibia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a3","text":"Seychelles"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tonga"}]},"q389":{"id":"q389","difficulty":0.5336640914,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Armenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ecuador"}]},"q390":{"id":"q390","difficulty":0.5336677473,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominican Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Canada"}]},"q391":{"id":"q391","difficulty":0.5340146644,"question":"The capital of Trinidad and Tobago is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Port of Spain","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San José"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guatemala City"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nassau"}]},"q392":{"id":"q392","difficulty":0.1587937178,"question":"What is the world's most widely-spoken language?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mandarin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jaffa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Satsuma"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tangerine"}]},"q393":{"id":"q393","difficulty":0.5341345134,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iceland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Palau"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tuvalu"}]},"q394":{"id":"q394","difficulty":0.534235839,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkey","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a3","text":"Japan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Thailand"}]},"q395":{"id":"q395","difficulty":0.5348149,"question":"Which country's capital is Monrovia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liberia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cape Verde"}]},"q396":{"id":"q396","difficulty":0.5348149,"question":"What is the capital of Liberia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Monrovia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Luanda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malabo"}]},"q397":{"id":"q397","difficulty":0.5350868508,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lesotho","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Israel"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kyrgyzstan"}]},"q398":{"id":"q398","difficulty":0.535180527,"question":"What is the capital of Cambodia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Phnom Penh","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kuala Lumpur"},{"id":"a3","text":"Manama"},{"id":"a4","text":"Beirut"}]},"q399":{"id":"q399","difficulty":0.5353701435,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Maldives"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moldova"}]},"q400":{"id":"q400","difficulty":0.5354192043,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nigeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q401":{"id":"q401","difficulty":0.5354194881,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mozambique","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Haiti"}]},"q402":{"id":"q402","difficulty":0.1596456033,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Greece?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Athens","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barcelona"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cologne"},{"id":"a4","text":"İzmir"}]},"q403":{"id":"q403","difficulty":0.5356835361,"question":"What is the capital of Burkina Faso?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ouagadougou","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cairo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Victoria"}]},"q404":{"id":"q404","difficulty":0.5358547942,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Oman","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kenya"}]},"q405":{"id":"q405","difficulty":0.5361449765,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Namibia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mali"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q406":{"id":"q406","difficulty":0.5367669014,"question":"The capital of Grenada is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"St. George's","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guatemala City"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mexico City"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nassau"}]},"q407":{"id":"q407","difficulty":0.5368572328,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Malta"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nauru"},{"id":"a4","text":"Palau"}]},"q408":{"id":"q408","difficulty":0.5369656904,"question":"Which country's capital is Tallinn?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Estonia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Georgia"}]},"q409":{"id":"q409","difficulty":0.5369696651,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Angola","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q410":{"id":"q410","difficulty":0.1607058439,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Qatar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Amestris"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bangalla"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estoccia"}]},"q411":{"id":"q411","difficulty":0.5370707596,"question":"Which country borders Denmark to the south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Germany","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belgium"},{"id":"a3","text":"Netherlands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sweden"}]},"q412":{"id":"q412","difficulty":0.5371680984,"question":"Which country's capital is St. George's?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Grenada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cuba"}]},"q413":{"id":"q413","difficulty":0.5372100372,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Arab Emirates","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q414":{"id":"q414","difficulty":0.5373249518,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Fiji","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiribati"}]},"q415":{"id":"q415","difficulty":0.5376057048,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lithuania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"El Salvador"}]},"q416":{"id":"q416","difficulty":0.5377481148,"question":"In which country would you find Ascot Racecourse?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Kingdom","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q417":{"id":"q417","difficulty":0.5381149775,"question":"Morocco does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Freetown","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Fes"},{"id":"a3","text":"Salé"},{"id":"a4","text":"Rabat"}]},"q418":{"id":"q418","difficulty":0.5381677308,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belarus","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"}]},"q419":{"id":"q419","difficulty":0.5389171659,"question":"What are the official languages of Djibouti?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"French and Arabic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Hebrew and English"},{"id":"a3","text":"Quechua and Aymara"},{"id":"a4","text":"Spanish"}]},"q420":{"id":"q420","difficulty":0.162110226,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arstotzka"},{"id":"a3","text":"Creta"},{"id":"a4","text":"Earthsea"}]},"q421":{"id":"q421","difficulty":0.5390615217,"question":"Sierra Leone contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Freetown","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Giza"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mombasa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Luanda"}]},"q422":{"id":"q422","difficulty":0.5392548617,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Egypt","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Germany"}]},"q423":{"id":"q423","difficulty":0.5394459028,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kuwait","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jordan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Laos"}]},"q424":{"id":"q424","difficulty":0.5399624982,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Senegal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Norway"},{"id":"a3","text":"Philippines"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zimbabwe"}]},"q425":{"id":"q425","difficulty":0.5400215769,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lithuania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Solomon Islands"}]},"q426":{"id":"q426","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Ottawa","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" is located in which Canadian province?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ontario"},{"id":"a4","text":"Alberta"}]},"q427":{"id":"q427","difficulty":0.5403345564,"question":"Which country's capital is Vientiane?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Laos","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cambodia"}]},"q428":{"id":"q428","difficulty":0.1625884106,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Equestria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fe'ausi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Loompa Land"}]},"q429":{"id":"q429","difficulty":0.5403345564,"question":"What is the capital of Laos?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vientiane","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Damascus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Naypyidaw"},{"id":"a4","text":"Pyongyang"}]},"q430":{"id":"q430","difficulty":0.5404121449,"question":"The capital of Belize is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belmopan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guatemala City"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kingstown"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ottawa"}]},"q431":{"id":"q431","difficulty":0.5404121449,"question":"Which country's capital is Belmopan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belize","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Canada"}]},"q432":{"id":"q432","difficulty":0.5405497234,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cuba","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q433":{"id":"q433","difficulty":0.5406276735,"question":"Which country's capital is Castries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Lucia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominica"}]},"q434":{"id":"q434","difficulty":0.1632713964,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jordan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arstotzka"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estoccia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Grand Fenwick"}]},"q435":{"id":"q435","difficulty":0.5410296881,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vatican City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Germany"}]},"q436":{"id":"q436","difficulty":0.5410382239,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Albania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Italy"}]},"q437":{"id":"q437","difficulty":0.5411665643,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Haiti"}]},"q438":{"id":"q438","difficulty":0.5415259861,"question":"Which country's capital is Riga?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Latvia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bulgaria"}]},"q439":{"id":"q439","difficulty":0.5417224281,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kenya"}]},"q440":{"id":"q440","difficulty":0.5417910553,"question":"Senegal contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dakar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benghazi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Moroni"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cairo"}]},"q441":{"id":"q441","difficulty":0.5418470677,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Republic of Ireland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mauritius"},{"id":"a4","text":"Swaziland"}]},"q442":{"id":"q442","difficulty":0.1634840219,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uzbekistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Borostyria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Coalition States"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cobrastan"}]},"q443":{"id":"q443","difficulty":0.5421031142,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Syria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Haiti"}]},"q444":{"id":"q444","difficulty":0.5421650162,"question":"Chad contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"N'Djamena","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Axum"},{"id":"a3","text":"Blantyre"},{"id":"a4","text":"Khartoum"}]},"q445":{"id":"q445","difficulty":0.5421725888,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nicaragua","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Barbados"}]},"q446":{"id":"q446","difficulty":0.5423902794,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ecuador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lesotho"},{"id":"a4","text":"Namibia"}]},"q447":{"id":"q447","difficulty":0.5425225284,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q448":{"id":"q448","difficulty":0.5426534889,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gabon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q449":{"id":"q449","difficulty":0.5427163276,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Russia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sudan"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q450":{"id":"q450","difficulty":0.5431639964,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Argentina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Niger"},{"id":"a3","text":"Yemen"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zimbabwe"}]},"q451":{"id":"q451","difficulty":0.5432413323,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Swaziland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Egypt"}]},"q452":{"id":"q452","difficulty":0.544198645,"question":"The capital of Barbados is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bridgetown","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San José"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guatemala City"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mexico City"}]},"q453":{"id":"q453","difficulty":0.5443178622,"question":"Côte d’Ivoire contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bouaké","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Matola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Wouri"},{"id":"a4","text":"Salé"}]},"q454":{"id":"q454","difficulty":0.544326981,"question":"The capital of San Marino is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"San Marino","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dublin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Monaco"},{"id":"a4","text":"Madrid"}]},"q455":{"id":"q455","difficulty":0.544326981,"question":"San Marino is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"San Marino","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iceland"}]},"q456":{"id":"q456","difficulty":0.5443943554,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Lucia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Panama"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovenia"}]},"q457":{"id":"q457","difficulty":0.1648520628,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iceland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Congo"}]},"q458":{"id":"q458","difficulty":0.5447023553,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kuwait","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Luxembourg"},{"id":"a3","text":"Republic of Macedonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vanuatu"}]},"q459":{"id":"q459","difficulty":0.5447480384,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Maldives"}]},"q460":{"id":"q460","difficulty":0.5447482924,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ghana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Congo"}]},"q461":{"id":"q461","difficulty":0.5452237497,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mexico","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q462":{"id":"q462","difficulty":0.5452425534,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"Niger"}]},"q463":{"id":"q463","difficulty":0.545300723,"question":"Dushanbe is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tajikistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Japan"}]},"q464":{"id":"q464","difficulty":0.545300723,"question":"What is the capital of Tajikistan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dushanbe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Manila"},{"id":"a3","text":"Baghdad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Naypyidaw"}]},"q465":{"id":"q465","difficulty":0.1664029133,"question":"In which country would you find San Francisco Ferry Building?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cuba"}]},"q466":{"id":"q466","difficulty":0.5458527491,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Peru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saudi Arabia"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q467":{"id":"q467","difficulty":0.5459237357,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Algeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bolivia"}]},"q468":{"id":"q468","difficulty":0.5461890317,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Rwanda?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kigali","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Marrakesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tripoli"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mtwara"}]},"q469":{"id":"q469","difficulty":null,"question":"Hillsong Church can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Sydney","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" Australia\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Florence"},{"id":"a4","text":" Italy\""}]},"q470":{"id":"q470","difficulty":0.5468144355,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ethiopia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saudi Arabia"}]},"q471":{"id":"q471","difficulty":0.547048474,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mexico","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Japan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mali"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zimbabwe"}]},"q472":{"id":"q472","difficulty":0.5471459706,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q473":{"id":"q473","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Khartoum","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Omdurman?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sudan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burkina Faso"}]},"q474":{"id":"q474","difficulty":0.5478730518,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Sudan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Khartoum North","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Yaoundé"},{"id":"a4","text":"Victoria"}]},"q475":{"id":"q475","difficulty":0.5480222368,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Grenada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bulgaria"}]},"q476":{"id":"q476","difficulty":0.5481362385,"question":"In which country would you find Alamo Mission in San Antonio?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominica"}]},"q477":{"id":"q477","difficulty":0.5484512803,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Venezuela","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kazakhstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Portugal"}]},"q478":{"id":"q478","difficulty":0.5488201755,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Barbados","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q479":{"id":"q479","difficulty":0.5490204304,"question":"The capital of Cameroon is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yaoundé","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cairo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mfoundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Wouri"}]},"q480":{"id":"q480","difficulty":0.5491573098,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ghana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Pakistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Korea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkey"}]},"q481":{"id":"q481","difficulty":0.167307799,"question":"In which country would you find The Notre Dame de Paris?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"France","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Montenegro"}]},"q482":{"id":"q482","difficulty":0.549248734,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Cameroon?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kano","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mfoundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Wouri"},{"id":"a4","text":"Douala"}]},"q483":{"id":"q483","difficulty":0.5494589422,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jordan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nepal"}]},"q484":{"id":"q484","difficulty":0.5498187092,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Panama","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cuba"}]},"q485":{"id":"q485","difficulty":0.5501290386,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Morocco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Egypt"}]},"q486":{"id":"q486","difficulty":0.5504015723,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bangladesh","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Israel"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lebanon"}]},"q487":{"id":"q487","difficulty":0.5505632143,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Suriname","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sweden"},{"id":"a4","text":"Thailand"}]},"q488":{"id":"q488","difficulty":0.5506864047,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Togo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Netherlands"}]},"q489":{"id":"q489","difficulty":0.5514293348,"question":"What is the capital of Estonia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tallinn","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Copenhagen"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dublin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moscow"}]},"q490":{"id":"q490","difficulty":0.0663769413,"question":"London is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Kingdom","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q491":{"id":"q491","difficulty":0.1678274707,"question":"Baghdad is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iraq","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kyrgyzstan"}]},"q492":{"id":"q492","difficulty":0.5522795359,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guatemala","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madagascar"},{"id":"a4","text":"New Zealand"}]},"q493":{"id":"q493","difficulty":0.5523851418,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Namibia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malaysia"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Kingdom"}]},"q494":{"id":"q494","difficulty":0.5524271299,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Papua New Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Colombia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mongolia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Venezuela"}]},"q495":{"id":"q495","difficulty":0.5526623575,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Qatar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea-Bissau"}]},"q496":{"id":"q496","difficulty":0.5527663934,"question":"The Yangtze runs through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"China","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"India"},{"id":"a3","text":"Maldives"},{"id":"a4","text":"Philippines"}]},"q497":{"id":"q497","difficulty":0.5529441274,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Samoa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovakia"}]},"q498":{"id":"q498","difficulty":0.5533053472,"question":"What is the capital of Guyana?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Georgetown","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Quito"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brasília"}]},"q499":{"id":"q499","difficulty":0.5534216455,"question":"What is the capital of Samoa?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Apia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"South Tarawa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ngerulmud"},{"id":"a4","text":"Wellington"}]},"q500":{"id":"q500","difficulty":0.5534216455,"question":"Which country's capital is Apia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Samoa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiribati"}]},"q501":{"id":"q501","difficulty":0.1687089466,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ethiopia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Drachma"},{"id":"a3","text":"Eagleland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Holy Britannian Empire"}]},"q502":{"id":"q502","difficulty":0.5538327768,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Moldova","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tajikistan"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Arab Emirates"}]},"q503":{"id":"q503","difficulty":0.5540901875,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burkina Faso"}]},"q504":{"id":"q504","difficulty":0.55441241,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zimbabwe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Egypt"}]},"q505":{"id":"q505","difficulty":0.5546069616,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guyana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lebanon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moldova"}]},"q506":{"id":"q506","difficulty":0.5547690474,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brunei","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Croatia"}]},"q507":{"id":"q507","difficulty":0.5549550069,"question":"What is the capital of Rwanda?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kigali","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Khartoum"},{"id":"a4","text":"Luanda"}]},"q508":{"id":"q508","difficulty":0.5549550069,"question":"Kigali is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rwanda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Central African Republic"}]},"q509":{"id":"q509","difficulty":0.1691235172,"question":"Which major river runs through Cairo?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nile","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Euphrates"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tigris"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yangtze"}]},"q510":{"id":"q510","difficulty":null,"question":"The Chrysler Building can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"New York City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Boston"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q511":{"id":"q511","difficulty":0.5555620316,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guyana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vanuatu"}]},"q512":{"id":"q512","difficulty":0.5556104795,"question":"Which of these rivers is the longest?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yellow River","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"White Nile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mississippi River"},{"id":"a4","text":"Irtysh River"}]},"q513":{"id":"q513","difficulty":0.5557951168,"question":"In what year did the world's population go past the 7 billion mark?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"2011","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"2008"},{"id":"a3","text":"2009"},{"id":"a4","text":"2010"}]},"q514":{"id":"q514","difficulty":0.5558405671,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uzbekistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a4","text":"Israel"}]},"q515":{"id":"q515","difficulty":0.5560296748,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malawi"}]},"q516":{"id":"q516","difficulty":0.5564296852,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Moldova","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Latvia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nepal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Togo"}]},"q517":{"id":"q517","difficulty":0.5565405011,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Mauritania?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nouakchott","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Fes"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hargeisa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Luanda"}]},"q518":{"id":"q518","difficulty":0.5569901055,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"El Salvador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belize"}]},"q519":{"id":"q519","difficulty":0.5572389149,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Denmark","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guyana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mongolia"}]},"q520":{"id":"q520","difficulty":0.1692837619,"question":"What is the capital of China?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Beijing","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chengdu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chongqing"},{"id":"a4","text":"Singapore"}]},"q521":{"id":"q521","difficulty":0.5575002643,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Croatia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equatorial Guinea"}]},"q522":{"id":"q522","difficulty":0.5575116037,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lebanon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q523":{"id":"q523","difficulty":0.557712051,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jamaica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q524":{"id":"q524","difficulty":0.5578446196,"question":"Which country's capital is Lilongwe?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malawi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea"}]},"q525":{"id":"q525","difficulty":0.5582477099,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nigeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a4","text":"Poland"}]},"q526":{"id":"q526","difficulty":0.5582499947,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Philippines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lesotho"}]},"q527":{"id":"q527","difficulty":0.558381295,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Samoa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Djibouti"}]},"q528":{"id":"q528","difficulty":0.5586385385,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Trinidad and Tobago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kuwait"},{"id":"a4","text":"Qatar"}]},"q529":{"id":"q529","difficulty":0.5588174838,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nauru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q530":{"id":"q530","difficulty":0.5589792741,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kazakhstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"France"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nepal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uganda"}]},"q531":{"id":"q531","difficulty":0.5591468155,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tunisia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Eritrea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q532":{"id":"q532","difficulty":0.5591755038,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kenya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q533":{"id":"q533","difficulty":0.5594060775,"question":"Paramaribo is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Suriname","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q534":{"id":"q534","difficulty":0.5594060775,"question":"The capital of Suriname is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paramaribo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Quito"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brasília"}]},"q535":{"id":"q535","difficulty":0.1692837619,"question":"Beijing is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"China","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"India"}]},"q536":{"id":"q536","difficulty":0.5595317665,"question":"Vaduz is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liechtenstein","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a4","text":"Latvia"}]},"q537":{"id":"q537","difficulty":0.5598440397,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belize","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominica"}]},"q538":{"id":"q538","difficulty":0.5601223757,"question":"The capital of Namibia is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Windhoek","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Khartoum"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malabo"}]},"q539":{"id":"q539","difficulty":0.5604287369,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Armenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lithuania"}]},"q540":{"id":"q540","difficulty":0.5605071159,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Qatar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"}]},"q541":{"id":"q541","difficulty":0.5606654012,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahamas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burundi"}]},"q542":{"id":"q542","difficulty":0.5612988721,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liberia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"}]},"q543":{"id":"q543","difficulty":0.5626042033,"question":"Cameroon contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mfoundi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kumasi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sharm El Sheikh"},{"id":"a4","text":"Matola"}]},"q544":{"id":"q544","difficulty":0.5629833309,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Morocco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saudi Arabia"}]},"q545":{"id":"q545","difficulty":0.5631415621,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Botswana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nepal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Philippines"}]},"q546":{"id":"q546","difficulty":0.5631768735,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Africa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"}]},"q547":{"id":"q547","difficulty":0.563288245,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Benin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkmenistan"}]},"q548":{"id":"q548","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Yaoundé","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Douala?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burkina Faso"}]},"q549":{"id":"q549","difficulty":0.5636515322,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bolivia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a4","text":"Colombia"}]},"q550":{"id":"q550","difficulty":0.5640611165,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Lucia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burundi"}]},"q551":{"id":"q551","difficulty":0.5640756656,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Botswana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Lucia"},{"id":"a4","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe"}]},"q552":{"id":"q552","difficulty":0.1711378069,"question":"What is the capital of Canada?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ottawa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San José"},{"id":"a3","text":"Calgary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kingstown"}]},"q553":{"id":"q553","difficulty":0.5640933749,"question":"Which country's capital is Bishkek?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kyrgyzstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"China"}]},"q554":{"id":"q554","difficulty":0.5641338696,"question":"Which of these rivers is the longest?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yangtze","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"White Nile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lena River"},{"id":"a4","text":"Niger River"}]},"q555":{"id":"q555","difficulty":0.5644138147,"question":"Which of these countries first colonized New York? ","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Netherlands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"England"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Spain"}]},"q556":{"id":"q556","difficulty":0.5644385165,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Myanmar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Israel"}]},"q557":{"id":"q557","difficulty":0.564977823,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Swaziland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guyana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nauru"}]},"q558":{"id":"q558","difficulty":0.5652026014,"question":"Port Louis is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritius","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burundi"}]},"q559":{"id":"q559","difficulty":0.5657988101,"question":"Djibouti is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Djibouti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Egypt"}]},"q560":{"id":"q560","difficulty":0.5658708565,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malawi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kenya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a4","text":"Poland"}]},"q561":{"id":"q561","difficulty":0.5660469293,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sweden","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Honduras"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"Laos"}]},"q562":{"id":"q562","difficulty":0.5660608127,"question":"Which country's capital is Kingstown?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Costa Rica"}]},"q563":{"id":"q563","difficulty":0.5660763472,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Libya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q564":{"id":"q564","difficulty":0.566091642,"question":"Which country's capital is Podgorica?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Montenegro","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q565":{"id":"q565","difficulty":0.5664743069,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ethiopia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madagascar"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mauritius"}]},"q566":{"id":"q566","difficulty":0.5670721472,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Germany","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q567":{"id":"q567","difficulty":0.567671883,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Angola","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Liberia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malawi"}]},"q568":{"id":"q568","difficulty":0.5677237302,"question":"The capital of Tasmania is what?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hobart","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canberra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Darwin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Newcastle"}]},"q569":{"id":"q569","difficulty":0.5681351623,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cameroon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q570":{"id":"q570","difficulty":0.5681942997,"question":"Which country's capital is St. John's?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Antigua and Barbuda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominica"}]},"q571":{"id":"q571","difficulty":0.5684199511,"question":"N'Djamena is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Liberia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Libya"}]},"q572":{"id":"q572","difficulty":0.5684199511,"question":"The capital of Chad is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"N'Djamena","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cairo"}]},"q573":{"id":"q573","difficulty":0.568750408,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Estonia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Honduras"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Arab Emirates"}]},"q574":{"id":"q574","difficulty":0.5691711866,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Venezuela","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q575":{"id":"q575","difficulty":0.06677449779,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iran","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Carpathia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Kundu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Genovia"}]},"q576":{"id":"q576","difficulty":0.1716354454,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Panama","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Amestris"},{"id":"a3","text":"Antegria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bialya"}]},"q577":{"id":"q577","difficulty":0.5692783613,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Croatia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Germany"}]},"q578":{"id":"q578","difficulty":0.5693627768,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Namibia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Niger"}]},"q579":{"id":"q579","difficulty":0.5694057086,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Algeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ethiopia"}]},"q580":{"id":"q580","difficulty":0.5697170203,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kyrgyzstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guatemala"}]},"q581":{"id":"q581","difficulty":0.569932183,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belize","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea-Bissau"}]},"q582":{"id":"q582","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find RMS Queen Mary?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Long Beach","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Birmingham"},{"id":"a4","text":" UK\""}]},"q583":{"id":"q583","difficulty":0.5701126275,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kenya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Djibouti"}]},"q584":{"id":"q584","difficulty":0.5703000631,"question":"Banjul is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eritrea"}]},"q585":{"id":"q585","difficulty":0.5705949505,"question":"Which country's capital is Bandar Seri Begawan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brunei","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iran"}]},"q586":{"id":"q586","difficulty":0.570624989,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Benin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q587":{"id":"q587","difficulty":0.5710059172,"question":"In what year did Italy unify?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"1861","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"1249"},{"id":"a3","text":"1945"},{"id":"a4","text":"1989"}]},"q588":{"id":"q588","difficulty":0.571374709,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lesotho","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chad"}]},"q589":{"id":"q589","difficulty":0.5715141711,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cambodia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malawi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mozambique"}]},"q590":{"id":"q590","difficulty":0.5719478905,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ukraine","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a3","text":"Rwanda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zimbabwe"}]},"q591":{"id":"q591","difficulty":0.172258198,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bolivia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Deltora"},{"id":"a3","text":"Genosha"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kashfar"}]},"q592":{"id":"q592","difficulty":0.5725437112,"question":"Praia is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cape Verde","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chad"}]},"q593":{"id":"q593","difficulty":0.5726965254,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rwanda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lesotho"}]},"q594":{"id":"q594","difficulty":0.5728250378,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Barbados","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Marshall Islands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tonga"}]},"q595":{"id":"q595","difficulty":0.5733226925,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lebanon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kuwait"}]},"q596":{"id":"q596","difficulty":0.5735218086,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mali","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"}]},"q597":{"id":"q597","difficulty":0.5735752737,"question":"The capital of Zimbabwe is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Harare","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Yaoundé"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bulawayo"}]},"q598":{"id":"q598","difficulty":0.573858719,"question":"Malawi contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Blantyre","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Sharm El Sheikh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Victoria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mbuji-Mayi"}]},"q599":{"id":"q599","difficulty":0.1723484603,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Croatia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Borostyria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kahndaq"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kashfar"}]},"q600":{"id":"q600","difficulty":0.5742250013,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Laos","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iran"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jordan"}]},"q601":{"id":"q601","difficulty":0.5744258679,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nigeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q602":{"id":"q602","difficulty":0.5744558165,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Timor-Leste","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bhutan"}]},"q603":{"id":"q603","difficulty":0.5746077418,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yemen","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kyrgyzstan"}]},"q604":{"id":"q604","difficulty":0.5746628037,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Eritrea?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Asmara","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kano"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tripoli"}]},"q605":{"id":"q605","difficulty":0.5749896534,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Equatorial Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gambia"}]},"q606":{"id":"q606","difficulty":0.5750556806,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Czech Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estonia"}]},"q607":{"id":"q607","difficulty":0.5751865405,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ukraine","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nicaragua"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uganda"}]},"q608":{"id":"q608","difficulty":0.5752314815,"question":"In which of these countries could you NOT see the Mekong?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iraq","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Myanmar"},{"id":"a3","text":"Thailand"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q609":{"id":"q609","difficulty":0.1734181172,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yemen","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antegria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cagliostro"},{"id":"a4","text":"Deltora"}]},"q610":{"id":"q610","difficulty":0.5752493551,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Japan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Pakistan"}]},"q611":{"id":"q611","difficulty":0.5752823223,"question":"Roseau is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"El Salvador"}]},"q612":{"id":"q612","difficulty":0.5752823223,"question":"What is the capital of Dominica?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Roseau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San José"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guatemala City"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mexico City"}]},"q613":{"id":"q613","difficulty":0.5754388361,"question":"Which of the following is not an Autonomous Community of Spain?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lorraine","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andalusia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Catalonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Galicia"}]},"q614":{"id":"q614","difficulty":0.5755043593,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guyana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Sweden"},{"id":"a3","text":"Thailand"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zambia"}]},"q615":{"id":"q615","difficulty":0.575617284,"question":"What is the second longest river in Europe?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Danube","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Rhine"},{"id":"a3","text":"Thames"},{"id":"a4","text":"Volga"}]},"q616":{"id":"q616","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In Paris","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"[NULL]","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arc de Triomphe"},{"id":"a3","text":"Champs-Elysees"},{"id":"a4","text":"The Eiffel Tower"}]},"q617":{"id":"q617","difficulty":0.5757948351,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Albania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Montenegro"}]},"q618":{"id":"q618","difficulty":0.1742561729,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Fe'ausi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ixania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kinakuta"}]},"q619":{"id":"q619","difficulty":0.5759607343,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mali","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"France"},{"id":"a3","text":"North Korea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Poland"}]},"q620":{"id":"q620","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Science Museum of Minnesota?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Saint Paul","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Dallas"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q621":{"id":"q621","difficulty":0.5763126257,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hungary","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q622":{"id":"q622","difficulty":0.5764531114,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liberia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Maldives"},{"id":"a4","text":"Trinidad and Tobago"}]},"q623":{"id":"q623","difficulty":0.5769108295,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Morocco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guatemala"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sweden"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tunisia"}]},"q624":{"id":"q624","difficulty":0.5771133192,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Japan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Colombia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mexico"},{"id":"a4","text":"Namibia"}]},"q625":{"id":"q625","difficulty":0.5772349126,"question":"What is the capital of Brunei?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bandar Seri Begawan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bishkek"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kabul"},{"id":"a4","text":"Manama"}]},"q626":{"id":"q626","difficulty":0.5772396866,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"North Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a3","text":"United Kingdom"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zimbabwe"}]},"q627":{"id":"q627","difficulty":0.5774305477,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"New Zealand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Luxembourg"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malta"}]},"q628":{"id":"q628","difficulty":0.1749124592,"question":"Vatican City is landlocked within what other city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rome","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Milan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Naples"},{"id":"a4","text":"Palermo"}]},"q629":{"id":"q629","difficulty":0.5780720158,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cape Verde","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Norway"},{"id":"a4","text":"Panama"}]},"q630":{"id":"q630","difficulty":0.5781138214,"question":"Which country's capital is Dakar?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Senegal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ghana"}]},"q631":{"id":"q631","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Trevi Fountain?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Rome","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" Italy\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Chicago"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q632":{"id":"q632","difficulty":0.5783553299,"question":"What is the capital of Togo?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lomé","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Moroni"},{"id":"a3","text":"Victoria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nairobi"}]},"q633":{"id":"q633","difficulty":0.578475942,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tanzania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"}]},"q634":{"id":"q634","difficulty":0.5785215736,"question":"Juba is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ethiopia"}]},"q635":{"id":"q635","difficulty":0.5785934782,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liechtenstein","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Haiti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jamaica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Montenegro"}]},"q636":{"id":"q636","difficulty":0.5788751715,"question":"What is the world's highest capital city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"La Paz","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Asuncion"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kathmandu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zurich"}]},"q637":{"id":"q637","difficulty":0.175021947,"question":"What is the capital of South Korea?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Seoul","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Daegu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Icheon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kathmandu"}]},"q638":{"id":"q638","difficulty":0.5788751715,"question":"Where in London can one view the Magna Carta and the Rosetta Stone?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"British Museum","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"National Gallery"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tate Gallery"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tower of London"}]},"q639":{"id":"q639","difficulty":0.5791410022,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Philippines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Peru"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uganda"}]},"q640":{"id":"q640","difficulty":0.5793751374,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Romania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Eritrea"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Arab Emirates"}]},"q641":{"id":"q641","difficulty":0.5794798249,"question":"What is the capital of Burundi?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bujumbura","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Tripoli"},{"id":"a3","text":"Addis Ababa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Antananarivo"}]},"q642":{"id":"q642","difficulty":0.5794885296,"question":"Which country's capital is Abuja?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nigeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a3","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equatorial Guinea"}]},"q643":{"id":"q643","difficulty":0.5798649699,"question":"The capital of Mali is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bamako","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a4","text":"Djibouti"}]},"q644":{"id":"q644","difficulty":0.5798898072,"question":"Which of these is the name of a rock formation in Australia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Three Sisters","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Three Degrees"},{"id":"a3","text":"Three Musketeers"},{"id":"a4","text":"Three Stooges"}]},"q645":{"id":"q645","difficulty":0.5802888161,"question":"Luanda is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Angola","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burkina Faso"}]},"q646":{"id":"q646","difficulty":0.5803069687,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Colombia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"China"}]},"q647":{"id":"q647","difficulty":0.580535863,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Honduras","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Oman"},{"id":"a3","text":"Romania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uganda"}]},"q648":{"id":"q648","difficulty":0.1754757484,"question":"The Art Institute of Chicago can be found in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guatemala"}]},"q649":{"id":"q649","difficulty":0.5814307613,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tonga","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eritrea"}]},"q650":{"id":"q650","difficulty":0.5816275929,"question":"The capital of Mozambique is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Maputo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Moroni"},{"id":"a3","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a4","text":"Victoria"}]},"q651":{"id":"q651","difficulty":0.5825559344,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Democratic Republic of the Congo?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lubumbashi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Moroni"},{"id":"a3","text":"Durban"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kaduna"}]},"q652":{"id":"q652","difficulty":0.5826176517,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malawi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chad"}]},"q653":{"id":"q653","difficulty":0.5828716648,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Colombia"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iraq"}]},"q654":{"id":"q654","difficulty":0.5834684621,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kyrgyzstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bhutan"}]},"q655":{"id":"q655","difficulty":0.5836436915,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rwanda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Romania"}]},"q656":{"id":"q656","difficulty":0.5837867177,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Botswana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iran"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mongolia"}]},"q657":{"id":"q657","difficulty":0.5839103347,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Antigua and Barbuda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lesotho"}]},"q658":{"id":"q658","difficulty":0.5843730589,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bangladesh","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Republic of Ireland"}]},"q659":{"id":"q659","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Lake Travis?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Austin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Breckenridge"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q660":{"id":"q660","difficulty":0.5846278385,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Thailand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Botswana"}]},"q661":{"id":"q661","difficulty":0.5847617514,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Côte d’Ivoire","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q662":{"id":"q662","difficulty":0.5851214492,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Equatorial Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Panama"}]},"q663":{"id":"q663","difficulty":0.5853370212,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q664":{"id":"q664","difficulty":0.06716533086,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Greece","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antegria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gondour"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kinakuta"}]},"q665":{"id":"q665","difficulty":0.1776268448,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"El Salvador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Corto Maltese"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kasnia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kolechia"}]},"q666":{"id":"q666","difficulty":0.5858586873,"question":"Maputo is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mozambique","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ethiopia"}]},"q667":{"id":"q667","difficulty":0.5867010004,"question":"Niamey is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Niger","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ghana"}]},"q668":{"id":"q668","difficulty":0.5867010004,"question":"The capital of Niger is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Niamey","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Victoria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kinshasa"}]},"q669":{"id":"q669","difficulty":0.5868097967,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Angola","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Honduras"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mauritania"}]},"q670":{"id":"q670","difficulty":0.5872285221,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Argentina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mongolia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mozambique"},{"id":"a4","text":"Thailand"}]},"q671":{"id":"q671","difficulty":0.587910516,"question":"Guinea contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Conakry","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Axum"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ibadan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Victoria"}]},"q672":{"id":"q672","difficulty":0.1793670341,"question":"Which country's capital is Brasília?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brazil","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Colombia"}]},"q673":{"id":"q673","difficulty":0.5879342054,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liberia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Botswana"}]},"q674":{"id":"q674","difficulty":0.5879486893,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equatorial Guinea"}]},"q675":{"id":"q675","difficulty":0.5879753371,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"France","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Libya"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mali"}]},"q676":{"id":"q676","difficulty":0.5881712709,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jamaica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Rwanda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Solomon Islands"}]},"q677":{"id":"q677","difficulty":0.5883858477,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Barbados","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Botswana"}]},"q678":{"id":"q678","difficulty":0.5886322278,"question":"Mbabane is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Swaziland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Central African Republic"}]},"q679":{"id":"q679","difficulty":0.1797227319,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Norway","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q680":{"id":"q680","difficulty":0.5898352456,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iran","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kenya"}]},"q681":{"id":"q681","difficulty":0.5906139685,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Thailand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Madagascar"}]},"q682":{"id":"q682","difficulty":0.5906737508,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Panama","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bolivia"}]},"q683":{"id":"q683","difficulty":0.5908722783,"question":"What is the capital of South Sudan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Juba","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Moroni"},{"id":"a3","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a4","text":"Victoria"}]},"q684":{"id":"q684","difficulty":0.590917664,"question":"What is the capital of São Tomé and Príncipe?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"São Tomé","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tripoli"},{"id":"a4","text":"Antananarivo"}]},"q685":{"id":"q685","difficulty":0.1798181246,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ecuador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Coalition States"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cobrastan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Freedonia"}]},"q686":{"id":"q686","difficulty":0.5909763314,"question":"The Paraná River does NOT run through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chile","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a4","text":"Paraguay"}]},"q687":{"id":"q687","difficulty":0.5912810543,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cambodia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lebanon"}]},"q688":{"id":"q688","difficulty":0.5914259528,"question":"What is the capital of Botswana?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gaborone","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Victoria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kinshasa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nouakchott"}]},"q689":{"id":"q689","difficulty":0.5914259528,"question":"Which country's capital is Gaborone?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Botswana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cape Verde"}]},"q690":{"id":"q690","difficulty":0.5919467302,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iraq","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sri Lanka"},{"id":"a4","text":"Syria"}]},"q691":{"id":"q691","difficulty":0.591993761,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Arab Emirates","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iraq"}]},"q692":{"id":"q692","difficulty":0.5921393136,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Austria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q693":{"id":"q693","difficulty":0.5923780488,"question":"In which of these countries could you see the Irtysh River?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kazakhstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saudi Arabia"}]},"q694":{"id":"q694","difficulty":0.5923780488,"question":"The Irtysh River does NOT run through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brunei","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mongolia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q695":{"id":"q695","difficulty":0.1798356384,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Italy","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Latvia"}]},"q696":{"id":"q696","difficulty":0.5924649007,"question":"The capital of Congo is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brazzaville","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cairo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Khartoum"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kinshasa"}]},"q697":{"id":"q697","difficulty":0.5924649007,"question":"Which country's capital is Brazzaville?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cape Verde"}]},"q698":{"id":"q698","difficulty":0.5926817299,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guyana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q699":{"id":"q699","difficulty":0.5927150331,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ghana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Honduras"}]},"q700":{"id":"q700","difficulty":0.5928721349,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Congo?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brazzaville","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mombasa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Axum"},{"id":"a4","text":"Luanda"}]},"q701":{"id":"q701","difficulty":0.5930535933,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iraq","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a3","text":"New Zealand"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q702":{"id":"q702","difficulty":null,"question":"Grauman's Chinese Theatre can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Los Angeles","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Atlanta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q703":{"id":"q703","difficulty":0.5935886474,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Italy","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mexico"}]},"q704":{"id":"q704","difficulty":0.5940344842,"question":"Which country's capital is Lomé?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Togo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ethiopia"}]},"q705":{"id":"q705","difficulty":0.1801458311,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Archenland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Babar's Kingdom"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equestria"}]},"q706":{"id":"q706","difficulty":0.5943088454,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Netherlands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q707":{"id":"q707","difficulty":0.594357668,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Albania?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tirana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Adana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kiev"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jihozápad"}]},"q708":{"id":"q708","difficulty":0.594476752,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tanzania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mexico"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q709":{"id":"q709","difficulty":0.5951744468,"question":"The capital of Fiji is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Suva","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ngerulmud"},{"id":"a3","text":"Wellington"},{"id":"a4","text":"Funafuti"}]},"q710":{"id":"q710","difficulty":0.5955990266,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Colombia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q711":{"id":"q711","difficulty":0.5956497945,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Croatia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"Singapore"}]},"q712":{"id":"q712","difficulty":0.5959381892,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Costa Rica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q713":{"id":"q713","difficulty":0.1803680133,"question":"In which country would you find The Sydney Opera House?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Australia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nauru"},{"id":"a3","text":"Palau"},{"id":"a4","text":"Samoa"}]},"q714":{"id":"q714","difficulty":0.5962110793,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tunisia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brunei"}]},"q715":{"id":"q715","difficulty":0.5963283399,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Costa Rica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guyana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Latvia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Republic of Macedonia"}]},"q716":{"id":"q716","difficulty":0.5966561871,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Antigua and Barbuda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kuwait"},{"id":"a4","text":"Qatar"}]},"q717":{"id":"q717","difficulty":0.5969328704,"question":"Where is the Astronaut Hall of Fame located?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cape Canaveral","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Houston"},{"id":"a3","text":"New York"},{"id":"a4","text":"Washington"}]},"q718":{"id":"q718","difficulty":0.5969512601,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Burkina Faso?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ouagadougou","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Luanda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Juba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tripoli"}]},"q719":{"id":"q719","difficulty":0.597429859,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Ghana?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Accra","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kano"},{"id":"a3","text":"Luanda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nairobi"}]},"q720":{"id":"q720","difficulty":0.5976203353,"question":"The Dominican Republic has a land border with only one country. Which is it?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Haiti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jamaica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Puerto Rico"}]},"q721":{"id":"q721","difficulty":0.1813031935,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Morocco"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sudan"}]},"q722":{"id":"q722","difficulty":0.5979526973,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovakia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Luxembourg"},{"id":"a4","text":"Montenegro"}]},"q723":{"id":"q723","difficulty":0.598115263,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paraguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sudan"}]},"q724":{"id":"q724","difficulty":0.5987697067,"question":"The capital of Guinea is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Conakry","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Addis Ababa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ouagadougou"}]},"q725":{"id":"q725","difficulty":0.5988245853,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tonga","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Montenegro"}]},"q726":{"id":"q726","difficulty":0.599066335,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Lucia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lebanon"}]},"q727":{"id":"q727","difficulty":0.5991392289,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uganda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guatemala"}]},"q728":{"id":"q728","difficulty":0.599325194,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q729":{"id":"q729","difficulty":0.5994154397,"question":"The capital of Gambia is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Banjul","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Yaoundé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nairobi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yamoussoukro"}]},"q730":{"id":"q730","difficulty":0.5994526834,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paraguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iceland"}]},"q731":{"id":"q731","difficulty":0.5996348566,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Côte d’Ivoire","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mozambique"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zambia"}]},"q732":{"id":"q732","difficulty":0.6005737956,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Uganda"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Kingdom"}]},"q733":{"id":"q733","difficulty":0.6005830904,"question":"Finish the European country's name: The Grand Duchy of _______.","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Luxembourg","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a3","text":"Monaco"},{"id":"a4","text":"San Marino"}]},"q734":{"id":"q734","difficulty":0.6007418153,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Syria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Kingdom"}]},"q735":{"id":"q735","difficulty":0.6008489052,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Eritrea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ecuador"}]},"q736":{"id":"q736","difficulty":0.6009795666,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iceland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Solomon Islands"}]},"q737":{"id":"q737","difficulty":0.6010134303,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Norway","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Libya"},{"id":"a4","text":"Venezuela"}]},"q738":{"id":"q738","difficulty":0.1823750487,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Finland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Croatia"}]},"q739":{"id":"q739","difficulty":0.6012780287,"question":"What is the capital of Andorra?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Andorra la Vella","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Podgorica"},{"id":"a3","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lisbon"}]},"q740":{"id":"q740","difficulty":0.6020408163,"question":"Great Britain has which of these climatic zones?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Temperate forest","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dry grassland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mediterranean"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mountain region"}]},"q741":{"id":"q741","difficulty":0.6022376318,"question":"Lahti and Oulu are cities in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Finland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Latvia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lithuania"}]},"q742":{"id":"q742","difficulty":0.6025963399,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sri Lanka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q743":{"id":"q743","difficulty":0.6026139507,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q744":{"id":"q744","difficulty":0.6027334784,"question":"The capital of Paraguay is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Asunción","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Quito"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a4","text":"Buenos Aires"}]},"q745":{"id":"q745","difficulty":0.6028235127,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Venezuela","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mauritius"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mozambique"}]},"q746":{"id":"q746","difficulty":0.06754966202,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"France","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Eriador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Impor"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kolechia"}]},"q747":{"id":"q747","difficulty":0.1824229356,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uganda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aerugo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Earthsea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gondor"}]},"q748":{"id":"q748","difficulty":0.6029283761,"question":"What is the capital of Uruguay?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Montevideo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brasília"},{"id":"a4","text":"Buenos Aires"}]},"q749":{"id":"q749","difficulty":0.6032475159,"question":"Dili is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Timor-Leste","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"China"}]},"q750":{"id":"q750","difficulty":0.6032475159,"question":"The capital of Timor-Leste is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dili","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Manila"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bishkek"},{"id":"a4","text":"Singapore"}]},"q751":{"id":"q751","difficulty":0.6033901208,"question":"Which country's capital is Chișinău?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Moldova","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Georgia"}]},"q752":{"id":"q752","difficulty":0.6034879292,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belize","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ecuador"}]},"q753":{"id":"q753","difficulty":0.6035987584,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Somalia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lesotho"}]},"q754":{"id":"q754","difficulty":0.6037959707,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tonga","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Georgia"}]},"q755":{"id":"q755","difficulty":0.1831783799,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Albania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Equatorial Kundu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kasnia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kyrat"}]},"q756":{"id":"q756","difficulty":0.6037995579,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Suriname","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Georgia"}]},"q757":{"id":"q757","difficulty":0.6043970286,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritius","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kuwait"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lebanon"}]},"q758":{"id":"q758","difficulty":0.60500904,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Suriname","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q759":{"id":"q759","difficulty":0.6052922013,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Azerbaijan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Qatar"}]},"q760":{"id":"q760","difficulty":0.6060059065,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lebanon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a3","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q761":{"id":"q761","difficulty":0.6071037253,"question":"What is the symbol of the Amazon?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Royal Water Lily","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Royal Mimosa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Royal Orchid"},{"id":"a4","text":"Royal Periwinkle"}]},"q762":{"id":"q762","difficulty":0.6074429772,"question":"The Tagalog language is most common in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"The Philippines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Thailand"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q763":{"id":"q763","difficulty":0.6075154327,"question":"What is the capital of Côte d’Ivoire?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yamoussoukro","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Victoria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bouaké"}]},"q764":{"id":"q764","difficulty":0.1833269794,"question":"Canada does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chicago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Calgary"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ottawa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Toronto"}]},"q765":{"id":"q765","difficulty":0.6075230867,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Andorra","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nauru"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"},{"id":"a4","text":"San Marino"}]},"q766":{"id":"q766","difficulty":0.6075515779,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Syria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a3","text":"Togo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tunisia"}]},"q767":{"id":"q767","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Apple Campus?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Cupertino","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Augusta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q768":{"id":"q768","difficulty":0.6077600244,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Romania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sierra Leone"},{"id":"a4","text":"Togo"}]},"q769":{"id":"q769","difficulty":0.6087408949,"question":"In which of these countries could you NOT see the White Nile?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Rwanda"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Sudan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sudan"}]},"q770":{"id":"q770","difficulty":0.6088179197,"question":"Nouakchott is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"}]},"q771":{"id":"q771","difficulty":0.609105697,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Trinidad and Tobago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q772":{"id":"q772","difficulty":0.6092567762,"question":"Which country's capital is Freetown?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sierra Leone","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ghana"}]},"q773":{"id":"q773","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Brisbane","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Adelaide?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"}]},"q774":{"id":"q774","difficulty":0.6092567762,"question":"The capital of Sierra Leone is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Freetown","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Luanda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Juba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tripoli"}]},"q775":{"id":"q775","difficulty":0.6093403943,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Qatar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Israel"}]},"q776":{"id":"q776","difficulty":0.6097978554,"question":"What is the capital of Democratic Republic of the Congo?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kinshasa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Lubumbashi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Goma"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mbuji-Mayi"}]},"q777":{"id":"q777","difficulty":0.6100413456,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brunei","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cambodia"}]},"q778":{"id":"q778","difficulty":0.6101651053,"question":"How many Emirates make up the United Arab Emirates?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"7","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"10"},{"id":"a3","text":"3"},{"id":"a4","text":"5"}]},"q779":{"id":"q779","difficulty":0.6101850354,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Georgia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Latvia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tonga"}]},"q780":{"id":"q780","difficulty":0.610370754,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Moldova","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Denmark"}]},"q781":{"id":"q781","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Tokyo","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Sapporo are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Japan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bahrain"}]},"q782":{"id":"q782","difficulty":0.6107794679,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malawi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a4","text":"El Salvador"}]},"q783":{"id":"q783","difficulty":0.6109224396,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Malaysia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Peru"},{"id":"a4","text":"Venezuela"}]},"q784":{"id":"q784","difficulty":0.6111332642,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Antigua and Barbuda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nauru"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"},{"id":"a4","text":"San Marino"}]},"q785":{"id":"q785","difficulty":0.6112122789,"question":"Which country's major rivers are the Elbe and the Vltava?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Czech Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Romania"}]},"q786":{"id":"q786","difficulty":0.6112679115,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cambodia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"India"}]},"q787":{"id":"q787","difficulty":0.6116516262,"question":"The capital of Malawi is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lilongwe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Yaoundé"},{"id":"a4","text":"Blantyre"}]},"q788":{"id":"q788","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Fox Theatre?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Atlanta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Calgary"},{"id":"a4","text":" Canada\""}]},"q789":{"id":"q789","difficulty":0.6126003582,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vanuatu","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ethiopia"}]},"q790":{"id":"q790","difficulty":0.6132574643,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Canada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Japan"}]},"q791":{"id":"q791","difficulty":0.6133391774,"question":"Guyana's main economic driver is what?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Agriculture","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"IT"},{"id":"a3","text":"Oil"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tourism"}]},"q792":{"id":"q792","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Washington Monument?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Washington","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" D.C."},{"id":"a3","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a4","text":"\"Los Angeles"}]},"q793":{"id":"q793","difficulty":0.6135239361,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Republic of Ireland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Maldives"},{"id":"a3","text":"Slovenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Swaziland"}]},"q794":{"id":"q794","difficulty":0.6137809035,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Kingdom","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Liberia"}]},"q795":{"id":"q795","difficulty":0.6143330175,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kenya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malawi"},{"id":"a4","text":"North Korea"}]},"q796":{"id":"q796","difficulty":0.6145801631,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kenya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nepal"},{"id":"a3","text":"Norway"},{"id":"a4","text":"Suriname"}]},"q797":{"id":"q797","difficulty":0.6149459536,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Barbados","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"El Salvador"}]},"q798":{"id":"q798","difficulty":0.6155583382,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Djibouti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gambia"}]},"q799":{"id":"q799","difficulty":0.6156677826,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belarus","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nepal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sri Lanka"}]},"q800":{"id":"q800","difficulty":0.6156696677,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Afghanistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Japan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Philippines"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q801":{"id":"q801","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Lincoln Memorial?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Washington","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" D.C."},{"id":"a3","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a4","text":"\"Barcelona"}]},"q802":{"id":"q802","difficulty":0.6158474376,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rwanda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Djibouti"}]},"q803":{"id":"q803","difficulty":0.6159252171,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malaysia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q804":{"id":"q804","difficulty":0.6161034777,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Denmark","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Romania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Senegal"}]},"q805":{"id":"q805","difficulty":0.6168570187,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"El Salvador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mali"}]},"q806":{"id":"q806","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Dar es Salaam","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Mtwara?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tanzania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burkina Faso"}]},"q807":{"id":"q807","difficulty":0.6170816833,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burundi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tonga"}]},"q808":{"id":"q808","difficulty":0.6172113907,"question":"Tanzania does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Giza","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dar es Salaam"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mbeya"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mtwara"}]},"q809":{"id":"q809","difficulty":0.61722046,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Comoros","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ghana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q810":{"id":"q810","difficulty":0.6174379823,"question":"Mozambique contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Matola","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Hargeisa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kananga"},{"id":"a4","text":"Wouri"}]},"q811":{"id":"q811","difficulty":0.1854661171,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovakia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Amestris"},{"id":"a3","text":"Archenland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Axphain"}]},"q812":{"id":"q812","difficulty":0.6181624476,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovenia"}]},"q813":{"id":"q813","difficulty":0.6182430296,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Solomon Islands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q814":{"id":"q814","difficulty":0.6183233698,"question":"Conakry is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea-Bissau"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mauritania"}]},"q815":{"id":"q815","difficulty":null,"question":"Museum of Old and New Art can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Hobart","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" Australia\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Giza"},{"id":"a4","text":" Egypt\""}]},"q816":{"id":"q816","difficulty":0.6184938318,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Barbados","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Montenegro"}]},"q817":{"id":"q817","difficulty":0.6187046827,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kuwait","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea"}]},"q818":{"id":"q818","difficulty":0.6187392874,"question":"Bujumbura is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burundi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Djibouti"}]},"q819":{"id":"q819","difficulty":0.6190256877,"question":"Lusaka is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cape Verde"}]},"q820":{"id":"q820","difficulty":0.6193590503,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cuba","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ghana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uganda"}]},"q821":{"id":"q821","difficulty":null,"question":"Shark Reef at Mandalay Bay can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Las Vegas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"New York City"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q822":{"id":"q822","difficulty":0.1854876644,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guatemala","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Amestris"},{"id":"a3","text":"Atlantis"},{"id":"a4","text":"Buranda"}]},"q823":{"id":"q823","difficulty":0.6197246528,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Qatar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mauritius"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Lucia"}]},"q824":{"id":"q824","difficulty":0.6203977425,"question":"What is Scotland's northernmost city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Inverness","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aberdeen"},{"id":"a3","text":"Edinburgh"},{"id":"a4","text":"Glasgow"}]},"q825":{"id":"q825","difficulty":0.6205248805,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liechtenstein","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nauru"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tuvalu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q826":{"id":"q826","difficulty":0.6205604505,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Benin?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cotonou","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Axum"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sharm El Sheikh"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dar es Salaam"}]},"q827":{"id":"q827","difficulty":0.6206984456,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Equatorial Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q828":{"id":"q828","difficulty":0.6215036389,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"San Marino","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Seychelles"},{"id":"a4","text":"Swaziland"}]},"q829":{"id":"q829","difficulty":0.6217321569,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vietnam","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Colombia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uganda"}]},"q830":{"id":"q830","difficulty":0.6219077411,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lithuania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liberia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Senegal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q831":{"id":"q831","difficulty":0.6219771191,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burundi"}]},"q832":{"id":"q832","difficulty":0.6221998778,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iraq","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"France"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Pakistan"}]},"q833":{"id":"q833","difficulty":0.1859016076,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Haiti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Amestris"},{"id":"a3","text":"Borduria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Borginia"}]},"q834":{"id":"q834","difficulty":0.6222926838,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Oman","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lesotho"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malta"}]},"q835":{"id":"q835","difficulty":0.6223044107,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zimbabwe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malawi"}]},"q836":{"id":"q836","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Where in the world are the Maluku Islands","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"[NULL]","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"South East Asia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Caribbean"},{"id":"a4","text":"Off Madagascar"}]},"q837":{"id":"q837","difficulty":0.6231146717,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Senegal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chad"}]},"q838":{"id":"q838","difficulty":0.6232102717,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iran","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Japan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Pakistan"}]},"q839":{"id":"q839","difficulty":0.6232488801,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"El Salvador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"North Korea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sierra Leone"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Arab Emirates"}]},"q840":{"id":"q840","difficulty":0.6235184514,"question":"Graz is the second largest city in what European country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Austria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Romania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Slovakia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovenia"}]},"q841":{"id":"q841","difficulty":0.6238801363,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"North Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Netherlands"}]},"q842":{"id":"q842","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Shedd Aquarium?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Chicago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Atlanta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q843":{"id":"q843","difficulty":0.1861945262,"question":"The capital of Iraq is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Baghdad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dhi Qar Governorate"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nineveh Governorate"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sulaymaniyah Governorate"}]},"q844":{"id":"q844","difficulty":0.6250357607,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liberia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Denmark"}]},"q845":{"id":"q845","difficulty":0.6255837563,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Azerbaijan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iraq"}]},"q846":{"id":"q846","difficulty":0.6257510019,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Singapore","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Botswana"}]},"q847":{"id":"q847","difficulty":0.6259667166,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Afghanistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Philippines"}]},"q848":{"id":"q848","difficulty":0.6261223904,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Senegal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lesotho"}]},"q849":{"id":"q849","difficulty":0.6265568469,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Montenegro","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Marshall Islands"},{"id":"a4","text":"San Marino"}]},"q850":{"id":"q850","difficulty":null,"question":"National Exhibition Centre can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Birmingham","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" UK\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Ascot"},{"id":"a4","text":" UK\""}]},"q851":{"id":"q851","difficulty":0.6268982274,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Venezuela","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a3","text":"New Zealand"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sweden"}]},"q852":{"id":"q852","difficulty":0.6271573604,"question":"What is the capital of Benin?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Porto-Novo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Luanda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tripoli"}]},"q853":{"id":"q853","difficulty":0.1865056338,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Japan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jordan"}]},"q854":{"id":"q854","difficulty":0.6273661011,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chile","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Sudan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tunisia"}]},"q855":{"id":"q855","difficulty":0.6274376132,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahrain","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Qatar"}]},"q856":{"id":"q856","difficulty":0.6276337612,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Grenada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Botswana"}]},"q857":{"id":"q857","difficulty":null,"question":"John Hancock Center can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Chicago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"George"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q858":{"id":"q858","difficulty":0.627904921,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkmenistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mongolia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Suriname"}]},"q859":{"id":"q859","difficulty":0.6279739883,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iran","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q860":{"id":"q860","difficulty":0.6279743338,"question":"What is the capital of Bahrain?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Manama","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bishkek"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jerusalem"},{"id":"a4","text":"Singapore"}]},"q861":{"id":"q861","difficulty":0.6282889876,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Togo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Australia"}]},"q862":{"id":"q862","difficulty":0.6284132072,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Trinidad and Tobago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malta"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"}]},"q863":{"id":"q863","difficulty":0.6284742625,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Italy","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Korea"}]},"q864":{"id":"q864","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Madison Square Garden?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"New York City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Atlanta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q865":{"id":"q865","difficulty":0.6287109675,"question":"Basseterre is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Costa Rica"}]},"q866":{"id":"q866","difficulty":0.6289631772,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Sudan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tanzania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Thailand"}]},"q867":{"id":"q867","difficulty":0.6290656681,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Samoa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nauru"}]},"q868":{"id":"q868","difficulty":0.6292728251,"question":"On which continent is the country of Suriname?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Africa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Asia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Europe"}]},"q869":{"id":"q869","difficulty":0.6294381997,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Georgia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q870":{"id":"q870","difficulty":0.6294484453,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equatorial Guinea"}]},"q871":{"id":"q871","difficulty":0.6298506512,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahrain","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a3","text":"Palau"},{"id":"a4","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe"}]},"q872":{"id":"q872","difficulty":0.1898228941,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Canada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mali"}]},"q873":{"id":"q873","difficulty":0.6300452601,"question":"How many Brazilian states have a capital city with the same name?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Two","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"None"},{"id":"a3","text":"One"},{"id":"a4","text":"Three"}]},"q874":{"id":"q874","difficulty":0.6301585927,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Luxembourg","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Lucia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"}]},"q875":{"id":"q875","difficulty":0.6301951245,"question":"Where are the rivers Narva and Parnu?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Estonia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a3","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Latvia"}]},"q876":{"id":"q876","difficulty":0.6307217209,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sweden","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mongolia"}]},"q877":{"id":"q877","difficulty":0.6317820513,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ethiopia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"New Zealand"},{"id":"a3","text":"Poland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Somalia"}]},"q878":{"id":"q878","difficulty":0.63208098,"question":"Asmara is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Eritrea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea-Bissau"}]},"q879":{"id":"q879","difficulty":0.63208098,"question":"What is the capital of Eritrea?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Asmara","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cairo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Victoria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Khartoum"}]},"q880":{"id":"q880","difficulty":0.1902525381,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Georgia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cobrastan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Emmeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Holy Britannian Empire"}]},"q881":{"id":"q881","difficulty":0.6333255671,"question":"Manama is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahrain","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"Indonesia"}]},"q882":{"id":"q882","difficulty":0.6334060702,"question":"Which of these Balkan states is landlocked?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Macedonia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovenia"}]},"q883":{"id":"q883","difficulty":0.6334857897,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Egypt","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iran"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kazakhstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sudan"}]},"q884":{"id":"q884","difficulty":0.6346183334,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Senegal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Denmark"}]},"q885":{"id":"q885","difficulty":null,"question":"The Ryman Auditorium can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Nashville","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Atlanta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q886":{"id":"q886","difficulty":0.6351730032,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Croatia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guyana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iceland"}]},"q887":{"id":"q887","difficulty":0.1928291659,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Madagascar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kyrzbekistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Metrofulus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Palombia"}]},"q888":{"id":"q888","difficulty":0.6352540859,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Equatorial Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Lucia"},{"id":"a4","text":"San Marino"}]},"q889":{"id":"q889","difficulty":0.6354997678,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Poland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a3","text":"Syria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zambia"}]},"q890":{"id":"q890","difficulty":0.6355476124,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Laos","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a3","text":"Morocco"},{"id":"a4","text":"Papua New Guinea"}]},"q891":{"id":"q891","difficulty":0.6356600518,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Greece","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Norway"},{"id":"a4","text":"Singapore"}]},"q892":{"id":"q892","difficulty":0.6358766722,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sierra Leone","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sweden"}]},"q893":{"id":"q893","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Roman Forum?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Rome","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" Italy\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Florence"},{"id":"a4","text":" Italy\""}]},"q894":{"id":"q894","difficulty":0.6365384539,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uganda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Madagascar"}]},"q895":{"id":"q895","difficulty":0.6368469296,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Algeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Haiti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mali"}]},"q896":{"id":"q896","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Mount Lemmon?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Tucson","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Chicago"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q897":{"id":"q897","difficulty":0.1930468499,"question":"The capital of Afghanistan is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kabul","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bishkek"},{"id":"a3","text":"Baku"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jerusalem"}]},"q898":{"id":"q898","difficulty":0.6374705551,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uganda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q899":{"id":"q899","difficulty":0.6376280366,"question":"The capital of Guinea-Bissau is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bissau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cairo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kinshasa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malabo"}]},"q900":{"id":"q900","difficulty":0.6377035526,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iceland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a3","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Paraguay"}]},"q901":{"id":"q901","difficulty":0.637716763,"question":"The White Nile runs through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malawi"}]},"q902":{"id":"q902","difficulty":0.6378772112,"question":"Which of these was the original name for the island of Tasmania?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Van Diemen's Land","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Christmas Island"},{"id":"a3","text":"Heard Island"},{"id":"a4","text":"Norfolk Island"}]},"q903":{"id":"q903","difficulty":0.6383072476,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Eritrea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a4","text":"Congo"}]},"q904":{"id":"q904","difficulty":0.638316906,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahrain","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malta"}]},"q905":{"id":"q905","difficulty":0.6386390227,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lesotho"}]},"q906":{"id":"q906","difficulty":0.1940947,"question":"What is the capital of France?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paris","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Podgorica"},{"id":"a3","text":"London"},{"id":"a4","text":"Rome"}]},"q907":{"id":"q907","difficulty":0.6387075981,"question":"Which country's capital is Bissau?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea-Bissau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burundi"}]},"q908":{"id":"q908","difficulty":0.6388254635,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Japan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Syria"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Kingdom"}]},"q909":{"id":"q909","difficulty":0.6388762314,"question":"What is the capital of Lesotho?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Maseru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cairo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Luanda"}]},"q910":{"id":"q910","difficulty":0.6388762314,"question":"Which country's capital is Maseru?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lesotho","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chad"}]},"q911":{"id":"q911","difficulty":0.6401244912,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guyana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q912":{"id":"q912","difficulty":0.6401603276,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q913":{"id":"q913","difficulty":0.6402929626,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Laos","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gambia"}]},"q914":{"id":"q914","difficulty":0.6404160534,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Central African Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q915":{"id":"q915","difficulty":0.6404792823,"question":"Bangui is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Central African Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Congo"}]},"q916":{"id":"q916","difficulty":0.6404792823,"question":"The capital of Central African Republic is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bangui","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Moroni"},{"id":"a3","text":"Khartoum"},{"id":"a4","text":"Luanda"}]},"q917":{"id":"q917","difficulty":0.6410298665,"question":"Accra is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ghana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"}]},"q918":{"id":"q918","difficulty":0.6414840446,"question":"Pompeii was destroyed when?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"79AD","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"143AD"},{"id":"a3","text":"187AD"},{"id":"a4","text":"23AD"}]},"q919":{"id":"q919","difficulty":0.6422513904,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sri Lanka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Qatar"}]},"q920":{"id":"q920","difficulty":0.6424363427,"question":"What is the capital of Antigua and Barbuda?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"St. John's","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kingstown"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nassau"},{"id":"a4","text":"Havana"}]},"q921":{"id":"q921","difficulty":0.6425462152,"question":"The city of St Louis is which of the following?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"A Port","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"A State Capital"},{"id":"a3","text":"A Surfing Resort"},{"id":"a4","text":"The Financial Center of the US"}]},"q922":{"id":"q922","difficulty":0.6425494849,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ecuador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q923":{"id":"q923","difficulty":0.6426522491,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Niger","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Djibouti"}]},"q924":{"id":"q924","difficulty":0.6430365511,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Niger","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Libya"},{"id":"a4","text":"Switzerland"}]},"q925":{"id":"q925","difficulty":0.6435486623,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Suriname","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q926":{"id":"q926","difficulty":0.643704116,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burkina Faso","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bolivia"}]},"q927":{"id":"q927","difficulty":0.6445575641,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Djibouti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Qatar"},{"id":"a3","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vanuatu"}]},"q928":{"id":"q928","difficulty":0.644866375,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Luxembourg","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q929":{"id":"q929","difficulty":0.64504344,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ghana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Botswana"}]},"q930":{"id":"q930","difficulty":0.6456110664,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Maldives"}]},"q931":{"id":"q931","difficulty":0.07336101172,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Eagleland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lilliput"},{"id":"a4","text":"Meropis"}]},"q932":{"id":"q932","difficulty":0.194893994,"question":"The capital of Brazil is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brasília","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a3","text":"Buenos Aires"},{"id":"a4","text":"São Paulo"}]},"q933":{"id":"q933","difficulty":0.6459088803,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Arab Emirates","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guinea-Bissau"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kuwait"},{"id":"a4","text":"Republic of Ireland"}]},"q934":{"id":"q934","difficulty":0.6468818176,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jordan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sierra Leone"}]},"q935":{"id":"q935","difficulty":null,"question":"The Shard can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"London","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" UK\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Ascot"},{"id":"a4","text":" UK\""}]},"q936":{"id":"q936","difficulty":0.647371445,"question":"In what city can you visit the original Guggenheim museum?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"New York","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Berlin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bilbao"},{"id":"a4","text":"Venice"}]},"q937":{"id":"q937","difficulty":0.6475479374,"question":"The capital of South Africa is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Pretoria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Durban"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cape Town"}]},"q938":{"id":"q938","difficulty":0.6477062374,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Botswana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Madagascar"}]},"q939":{"id":"q939","difficulty":0.6479909904,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"North Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Israel"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jordan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q940":{"id":"q940","difficulty":0.6484931809,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Denmark","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Montenegro"},{"id":"a4","text":"Samoa"}]},"q941":{"id":"q941","difficulty":0.1950909391,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liberia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Florin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gondour"},{"id":"a4","text":"Idris"}]},"q942":{"id":"q942","difficulty":0.6486494585,"question":"What is the capital of Zambia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lusaka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Victoria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Luanda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Pretoria"}]},"q943":{"id":"q943","difficulty":0.6488726077,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Russia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q944":{"id":"q944","difficulty":0.6490481118,"question":"The capital of Gabon is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Libreville","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Luanda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tripoli"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kinshasa"}]},"q945":{"id":"q945","difficulty":0.6492567581,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Armenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Suriname"}]},"q946":{"id":"q946","difficulty":0.6493682634,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Philippines"},{"id":"a3","text":"Thailand"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q947":{"id":"q947","difficulty":0.6494891815,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Austria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jamaica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lithuania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mongolia"}]},"q948":{"id":"q948","difficulty":0.6495246473,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guatemala","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Poland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sudan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tanzania"}]},"q949":{"id":"q949","difficulty":0.6496095515,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belarus","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nicaragua"}]},"q950":{"id":"q950","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Empire State Building?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"New York City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Boston"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q951":{"id":"q951","difficulty":0.6501662072,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liechtenstein","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lesotho"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Lucia"}]},"q952":{"id":"q952","difficulty":0.650398792,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Estonia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mauritius"},{"id":"a3","text":"Solomon Islands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Timor-Leste"}]},"q953":{"id":"q953","difficulty":0.6506634968,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chile","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sudan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uzbekistan"}]},"q954":{"id":"q954","difficulty":0.6506795981,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lebanon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Sudan"}]},"q955":{"id":"q955","difficulty":0.6514446138,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guatemala","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea-Bissau"}]},"q956":{"id":"q956","difficulty":0.6517269376,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Argentina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Japan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mexico"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q957":{"id":"q957","difficulty":0.6518888541,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burundi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q958":{"id":"q958","difficulty":0.6522220814,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ghana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q959":{"id":"q959","difficulty":0.6522457568,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Latvia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guyana"}]},"q960":{"id":"q960","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Hollywood Bowl?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Los Angeles","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Ascot"},{"id":"a4","text":" UK\""}]},"q961":{"id":"q961","difficulty":0.6526897546,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Andorra","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iceland"}]},"q962":{"id":"q962","difficulty":0.6530269959,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ecuador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Haiti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lebanon"}]},"q963":{"id":"q963","difficulty":0.653132508,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rwanda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Libya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Republic of Ireland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkmenistan"}]},"q964":{"id":"q964","difficulty":0.6531548758,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Indonesia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Central African Republic"}]},"q965":{"id":"q965","difficulty":0.6537350194,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Estonia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Liechtenstein"}]},"q966":{"id":"q966","difficulty":0.6537730766,"question":"Ngerulmud is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Palau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiribati"}]},"q967":{"id":"q967","difficulty":0.6537730766,"question":"The capital of Palau is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ngerulmud","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Wellington"},{"id":"a3","text":"Suva"},{"id":"a4","text":"Funafuti"}]},"q968":{"id":"q968","difficulty":0.6541376297,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Arab Emirates","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nicaragua"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tajikistan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tunisia"}]},"q969":{"id":"q969","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Museo Nacional Del Prado?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Madrid","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" Spain\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Ascot"},{"id":"a4","text":" UK\""}]},"q970":{"id":"q970","difficulty":0.6547061201,"question":"What is the capital of Nigeria?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Abuja","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin City"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ibadan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kano"}]},"q971":{"id":"q971","difficulty":0.6561116918,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jordan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Montenegro"}]},"q972":{"id":"q972","difficulty":0.6562516596,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Swaziland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lesotho"},{"id":"a4","text":"Liberia"}]},"q973":{"id":"q973","difficulty":0.6567513972,"question":"Which currency is used on the island of Gibraltar?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Pound","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dollar"},{"id":"a3","text":"Euro"},{"id":"a4","text":"Franc"}]},"q974":{"id":"q974","difficulty":0.6575669667,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkmenistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"Poland"}]},"q975":{"id":"q975","difficulty":0.1974850546,"question":"The Queen's official residence in Central London is?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Buckingham Palace","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Balmoral"},{"id":"a3","text":"St James' Palace"},{"id":"a4","text":"Windsor Castle"}]},"q976":{"id":"q976","difficulty":0.6577541246,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ethiopia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Korea"}]},"q977":{"id":"q977","difficulty":0.6577855618,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brunei","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"},{"id":"a3","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q978":{"id":"q978","difficulty":0.6579310345,"question":"Which of these rivers is the longest?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lena River","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"White Nile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madeira River"},{"id":"a4","text":"Purus River"}]},"q979":{"id":"q979","difficulty":0.6583144841,"question":"Tegucigalpa is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Honduras","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Barbados"}]},"q980":{"id":"q980","difficulty":0.6584995239,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nicaragua","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Madagascar"}]},"q981":{"id":"q981","difficulty":null,"question":"Scott County Jail can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Davenport","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Augusta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q982":{"id":"q982","difficulty":0.6587591653,"question":"Porto-Novo is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Benin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Congo"}]},"q983":{"id":"q983","difficulty":0.1977589064,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vanuatu","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Latvia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Solomon Islands"}]},"q984":{"id":"q984","difficulty":0.658765198,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Panama","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Somalia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q985":{"id":"q985","difficulty":0.6589382519,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Latvia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Georgia"}]},"q986":{"id":"q986","difficulty":0.659023486,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bhutan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Marshall Islands"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tuvalu"}]},"q987":{"id":"q987","difficulty":-22,"question":"\"In degrees Celsius","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"[NULL]","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"-26"},{"id":"a3","text":"-14"},{"id":"a4","text":"-18"}]},"q988":{"id":"q988","difficulty":0.659969239,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Central African Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cameroon"}]},"q989":{"id":"q989","difficulty":0.6600769353,"question":"Nukuʻalofa is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tonga","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiribati"}]},"q990":{"id":"q990","difficulty":0.6600769353,"question":"The capital of Tonga is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nukuʻalofa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"South Tarawa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ngerulmud"},{"id":"a4","text":"Wellington"}]},"q991":{"id":"q991","difficulty":0.6602720588,"question":"The capital of Saint Lucia is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Castries","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San José"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guatemala City"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ottawa"}]},"q992":{"id":"q992","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Calgary","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Toronto are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"}]},"q993":{"id":"q993","difficulty":0.660559575,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Finland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nepal"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Korea"}]},"q994":{"id":"q994","difficulty":0.6610408059,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominican Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Malawi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Peru"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sudan"}]},"q995":{"id":"q995","difficulty":0.6610754489,"question":"Ouagadougou is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burkina Faso","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Djibouti"}]},"q996":{"id":"q996","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find KOKO?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"London","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" UK\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Ascot"},{"id":"a4","text":" UK\""}]},"q997":{"id":"q997","difficulty":0.6616221986,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Azerbaijan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nepal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zambia"}]},"q998":{"id":"q998","difficulty":0.6617665572,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Suriname","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominican Republic"}]},"q999":{"id":"q999","difficulty":0.6618573446,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monaco"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nauru"},{"id":"a4","text":"San Marino"}]},"q1000":{"id":"q1000","difficulty":0.1990643584,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Republic of Ireland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Buenaventura"},{"id":"a3","text":"Carpathia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Corto Maltese"}]},"q1001":{"id":"q1001","difficulty":0.6627430785,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q1002":{"id":"q1002","difficulty":0.6628842287,"question":"The Monumento a Bernardo O'Higgins is found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Santiago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brasilia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Buenos Aires"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lima"}]},"q1003":{"id":"q1003","difficulty":0.6629577592,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkmenistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iran"}]},"q1004":{"id":"q1004","difficulty":0.6636753939,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gabon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Djibouti"}]},"q1005":{"id":"q1005","difficulty":0.663681554,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Azerbaijan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Lebanon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Oman"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q1006":{"id":"q1006","difficulty":0.6638090417,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kazakhstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Colombia"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sweden"}]},"q1007":{"id":"q1007","difficulty":0.6639600137,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Eritrea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Portugal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sierra Leone"}]},"q1008":{"id":"q1008","difficulty":0.6641668305,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sri Lanka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a3","text":"Papua New Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Portugal"}]},"q1009":{"id":"q1009","difficulty":0.6645253618,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkmenistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Sudan"}]},"q1010":{"id":"q1010","difficulty":0.1997307254,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tanzania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Carpathia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chernarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Florin"}]},"q1011":{"id":"q1011","difficulty":0.6647596354,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zimbabwe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovakia"}]},"q1012":{"id":"q1012","difficulty":0.6648243575,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iran","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Morocco"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Korea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zambia"}]},"q1013":{"id":"q1013","difficulty":0.6650485592,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mongolia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kazakhstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q1014":{"id":"q1014","difficulty":0.6653614222,"question":"In which French city is the Gare du Nord situated?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paris","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bordeaux"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lyon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Marseilles"}]},"q1015":{"id":"q1015","difficulty":0.6653616789,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Colombia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Japan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Poland"}]},"q1016":{"id":"q1016","difficulty":0.6657619393,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea-Bissau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea"}]},"q1017":{"id":"q1017","difficulty":0.6660757492,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Africa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sudan"}]},"q1018":{"id":"q1018","difficulty":0.6662312619,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Lucia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Costa Rica"}]},"q1019":{"id":"q1019","difficulty":0.07346406841,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkey","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Atlantis"},{"id":"a3","text":"Emmeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gondor"}]},"q1020":{"id":"q1020","difficulty":0.200226345,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Solomon Islands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guatemala"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sierra Leone"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sri Lanka"}]},"q1021":{"id":"q1021","difficulty":0.6664879996,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tunisia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Somalia"}]},"q1022":{"id":"q1022","difficulty":0.666564249,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Moldova","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Qatar"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"}]},"q1023":{"id":"q1023","difficulty":null,"question":"The Flatiron Building can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"New York City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Augusta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1024":{"id":"q1024","difficulty":0.6681233669,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kuwait","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q1025":{"id":"q1025","difficulty":0.6683810056,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Grenada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a4","text":"El Salvador"}]},"q1026":{"id":"q1026","difficulty":0.6687478565,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Azerbaijan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malaysia"}]},"q1027":{"id":"q1027","difficulty":null,"question":"The CN Tower can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Toronto","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" Canada\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Athens"},{"id":"a4","text":" Greece\""}]},"q1028":{"id":"q1028","difficulty":0.669795875,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hungary","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mauritania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Panama"}]},"q1029":{"id":"q1029","difficulty":0.2009544845,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Russia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belize"}]},"q1030":{"id":"q1030","difficulty":0.6702837263,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Italy","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"France"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ukraine"},{"id":"a4","text":"Venezuela"}]},"q1031":{"id":"q1031","difficulty":0.6707131049,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Somalia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Oman"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sierra Leone"}]},"q1032":{"id":"q1032","difficulty":0.6710162597,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Syria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uzbekistan"}]},"q1033":{"id":"q1033","difficulty":0.6710635628,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Qatar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Oman"}]},"q1034":{"id":"q1034","difficulty":0.6713724886,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahamas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Marshall Islands"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tonga"}]},"q1035":{"id":"q1035","difficulty":0.6717805377,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Latvia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Honduras"},{"id":"a3","text":"Romania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Syria"}]},"q1036":{"id":"q1036","difficulty":0.6721405295,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Laos","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Senegal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Somalia"}]},"q1037":{"id":"q1037","difficulty":0.6723267431,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tajikistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea-Bissau"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovakia"}]},"q1038":{"id":"q1038","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Red Rocks Amphitheatre?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Morrison","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Berlin"},{"id":"a4","text":" Germany\""}]},"q1039":{"id":"q1039","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find 30 Rockefeller Plaza?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"New York City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Berlin"},{"id":"a4","text":" Germany\""}]},"q1040":{"id":"q1040","difficulty":0.6724588093,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cuba"}]},"q1041":{"id":"q1041","difficulty":0.672477698,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Benin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea-Bissau"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kenya"}]},"q1042":{"id":"q1042","difficulty":0.672680192,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Madagascar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q1043":{"id":"q1043","difficulty":0.6731867262,"question":"Which is the world's northernmost city with a population in excess of 1 million people?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Petersburg","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Helsinki"},{"id":"a3","text":"Oslo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Reykjavik"}]},"q1044":{"id":"q1044","difficulty":0.6732590819,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Djibouti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burundi"}]},"q1045":{"id":"q1045","difficulty":0.6733049692,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Georgia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guyana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kyrgyzstan"}]},"q1046":{"id":"q1046","difficulty":0.6733055886,"question":"What do you call land reclaimed by dikes in the Netherlands?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Polder","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Boulder"},{"id":"a3","text":"Holder"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moulder"}]},"q1047":{"id":"q1047","difficulty":0.6735488665,"question":"Malabo is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Equatorial Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chad"}]},"q1048":{"id":"q1048","difficulty":0.6741791781,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Estonia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"},{"id":"a4","text":"Solomon Islands"}]},"q1049":{"id":"q1049","difficulty":0.2044461552,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahamas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antegria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Axphain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cobra Island"}]},"q1050":{"id":"q1050","difficulty":0.6742315427,"question":"Which country has the World's driest desert?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chile","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mongolia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Morocco"}]},"q1051":{"id":"q1051","difficulty":0.6742816275,"question":"What is the capital of Saint Vincent and the Grenadines?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kingstown","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"St. John's"},{"id":"a3","text":"Havana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Basseterre"}]},"q1052":{"id":"q1052","difficulty":0.6744223245,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mozambique"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tanzania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uganda"}]},"q1053":{"id":"q1053","difficulty":0.6747532031,"question":"What is a traditional county of Northern Ireland?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Down","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Left"},{"id":"a3","text":"Right"},{"id":"a4","text":"Up"}]},"q1054":{"id":"q1054","difficulty":0.6747949323,"question":"The capital of Mauritania is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nouakchott","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Yaoundé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Khartoum"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kinshasa"}]},"q1055":{"id":"q1055","difficulty":0.6750640262,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q1056":{"id":"q1056","difficulty":0.6752421622,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cape Verde"}]},"q1057":{"id":"q1057","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Bushnell Center for the Performing Arts?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Hartford","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Amritsar"},{"id":"a4","text":" India\""}]},"q1058":{"id":"q1058","difficulty":0.6762158426,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Norway","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Namibia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Swaziland"}]},"q1059":{"id":"q1059","difficulty":0.6763225906,"question":"The capital of Moldova is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chișinău","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Berlin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bratislava"},{"id":"a4","text":"Helsinki"}]},"q1060":{"id":"q1060","difficulty":0.2056747404,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"China","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kenya"}]},"q1061":{"id":"q1061","difficulty":0.6764025535,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Peru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jordan"}]},"q1062":{"id":"q1062","difficulty":0.6764295727,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahamas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a4","text":"New Zealand"}]},"q1063":{"id":"q1063","difficulty":0.6767879814,"question":"In which country would you find Peoria Civic Center?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Haiti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mexico"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nicaragua"}]},"q1064":{"id":"q1064","difficulty":0.6768365997,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"San Marino","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Palau"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tuvalu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q1065":{"id":"q1065","difficulty":0.677010211,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahrain","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mauritius"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vanuatu"}]},"q1066":{"id":"q1066","difficulty":0.6770701142,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Samoa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiribati"}]},"q1067":{"id":"q1067","difficulty":0.6770721927,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ecuador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nepal"}]},"q1068":{"id":"q1068","difficulty":0.6776015983,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liechtenstein","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"Luxembourg"}]},"q1069":{"id":"q1069","difficulty":0.6778051105,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Niger","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Botswana"}]},"q1070":{"id":"q1070","difficulty":0.2061539957,"question":"In which country would you find The Acropolis of Athens?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Greece","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a3","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Liechtenstein"}]},"q1071":{"id":"q1071","difficulty":0.6778568026,"question":"What is the capital of Ghana?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Accra","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kumasi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Khartoum"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yamoussoukro"}]},"q1072":{"id":"q1072","difficulty":0.6779966159,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lithuania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"France"}]},"q1073":{"id":"q1073","difficulty":0.6780088768,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Antigua and Barbuda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Latvia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vanuatu"}]},"q1074":{"id":"q1074","difficulty":0.6786174062,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vanuatu","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Namibia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Suriname"}]},"q1075":{"id":"q1075","difficulty":0.6786438559,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kenya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Japan"}]},"q1076":{"id":"q1076","difficulty":0.6787086998,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Panama","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Maldives"},{"id":"a4","text":"Solomon Islands"}]},"q1077":{"id":"q1077","difficulty":0.6788089383,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Montenegro","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Arab Emirates"}]},"q1078":{"id":"q1078","difficulty":0.6794103247,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Haiti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lesotho"}]},"q1079":{"id":"q1079","difficulty":0.6795660186,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Niger","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Germany"}]},"q1080":{"id":"q1080","difficulty":null,"question":"Water Tower Place can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Chicago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Magelang Regency"},{"id":"a4","text":" Indonesia\""}]},"q1081":{"id":"q1081","difficulty":0.2070639039,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Myanmar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Farfelu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hyrule"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kahndaq"}]},"q1082":{"id":"q1082","difficulty":0.6801925366,"question":"The Niger River does NOT run through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Equatorial Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mali"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nigeria"}]},"q1083":{"id":"q1083","difficulty":0.6813576288,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mali","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q1084":{"id":"q1084","difficulty":0.6815326051,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Swaziland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lebanon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moldova"}]},"q1085":{"id":"q1085","difficulty":0.6816169625,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liberia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a3","text":"Switzerland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q1086":{"id":"q1086","difficulty":0.6818687957,"question":"What is the capital of Nauru?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yaren District","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"South Tarawa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ngerulmud"},{"id":"a4","text":"Wellington"}]},"q1087":{"id":"q1087","difficulty":0.6818687957,"question":"Yaren District is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nauru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Marshall Islands"}]},"q1088":{"id":"q1088","difficulty":0.2073288587,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aurelia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bangalla"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cobrastan"}]},"q1089":{"id":"q1089","difficulty":0.6822934942,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bolivia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madagascar"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uzbekistan"}]},"q1090":{"id":"q1090","difficulty":0.6830340637,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Poland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a4","text":"Thailand"}]},"q1091":{"id":"q1091","difficulty":0.6831803538,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cameroon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guyana"},{"id":"a4","text":"North Korea"}]},"q1092":{"id":"q1092","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Mall of America?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Bloomington","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Ascot"},{"id":"a4","text":" UK\""}]},"q1093":{"id":"q1093","difficulty":0.6839559258,"question":"Which of the following is in the northwestern Luzon of the Philippines?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lingayen Gulf","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ambracian Gulf"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gulf of Aden"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sea of Tranquility"}]},"q1094":{"id":"q1094","difficulty":0.6842840876,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Montenegro","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Germany"}]},"q1095":{"id":"q1095","difficulty":0.6843015125,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bhutan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"India"},{"id":"a3","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lebanon"}]},"q1096":{"id":"q1096","difficulty":0.6844451861,"question":"Somalia contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hargeisa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Alexandria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Casablanca"}]},"q1097":{"id":"q1097","difficulty":0.2074815471,"question":"The capital of Germany is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Berlin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bratislava"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cologne"},{"id":"a4","text":"Munich"}]},"q1098":{"id":"q1098","difficulty":0.6844772245,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Luxembourg","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Palau"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"},{"id":"a4","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe"}]},"q1099":{"id":"q1099","difficulty":0.6846333211,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bolivia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lebanon"}]},"q1100":{"id":"q1100","difficulty":0.684658803,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Finland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovenia"}]},"q1101":{"id":"q1101","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Kaduna","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"[NULL]","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ghana"}]},"q1102":{"id":"q1102","difficulty":0.6850904089,"question":"What is the capital of Equatorial Guinea?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malabo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Victoria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tripoli"}]},"q1103":{"id":"q1103","difficulty":0.6853211394,"question":"The capital of Papua New Guinea is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Port Moresby","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"South Tarawa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ngerulmud"},{"id":"a4","text":"Wellington"}]},"q1104":{"id":"q1104","difficulty":null,"question":"The Gorge Amphitheatre can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Quincy","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Amritsar"},{"id":"a4","text":" India\""}]},"q1105":{"id":"q1105","difficulty":0.6856948294,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Africa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a4","text":"Canada"}]},"q1106":{"id":"q1106","difficulty":0.6859578656,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Japan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Senegal"},{"id":"a3","text":"Uganda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q1107":{"id":"q1107","difficulty":0.6860196099,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea-Bissau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q1108":{"id":"q1108","difficulty":0.6862135714,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bhutan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Namibia"}]},"q1109":{"id":"q1109","difficulty":0.6862756952,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Comoros","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tonga"}]},"q1110":{"id":"q1110","difficulty":0.6865097826,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Trinidad and Tobago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kiribati"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Lucia"}]},"q1111":{"id":"q1111","difficulty":0.6866206549,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Fiji","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Luxembourg"},{"id":"a3","text":"Maldives"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"}]},"q1112":{"id":"q1112","difficulty":0.6867385787,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahrain","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"India"}]},"q1113":{"id":"q1113","difficulty":0.6868008554,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cameroon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ethiopia"}]},"q1114":{"id":"q1114","difficulty":0.6872035573,"question":"The Paraná River runs through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brazil","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Suriname"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q1115":{"id":"q1115","difficulty":0.6875887369,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malaysia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mexico"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q1116":{"id":"q1116","difficulty":0.07415500482,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Poland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bialya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Borduria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Calbia"}]},"q1117":{"id":"q1117","difficulty":0.2074815471,"question":"Berlin is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Germany","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bulgaria"}]},"q1118":{"id":"q1118","difficulty":0.6883432805,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madagascar"},{"id":"a4","text":"Netherlands"}]},"q1119":{"id":"q1119","difficulty":0.6885547382,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Sweden"},{"id":"a3","text":"Turkmenistan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Venezuela"}]},"q1120":{"id":"q1120","difficulty":0.6891198711,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bangladesh","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Poland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zimbabwe"}]},"q1121":{"id":"q1121","difficulty":0.6893608205,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Namibia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burundi"}]},"q1122":{"id":"q1122","difficulty":0.6896027687,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tajikistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madagascar"},{"id":"a4","text":"North Korea"}]},"q1123":{"id":"q1123","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Mazda Raceway Laguna Seca?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Salinas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Breckenridge"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1124":{"id":"q1124","difficulty":0.6905097238,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cambodia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Italy"}]},"q1125":{"id":"q1125","difficulty":0.6910900221,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Equatorial Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Luxembourg"},{"id":"a4","text":"Qatar"}]},"q1126":{"id":"q1126","difficulty":0.691362164,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Philippines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liberia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nicaragua"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q1127":{"id":"q1127","difficulty":0.208716625,"question":"Australia does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Honiara","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brisbane"},{"id":"a3","text":"Perth"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sydney"}]},"q1128":{"id":"q1128","difficulty":0.6919588223,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brunei","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q1129":{"id":"q1129","difficulty":0.6923150825,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Senegal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Syria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tanzania"}]},"q1130":{"id":"q1130","difficulty":0.6923806639,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nauru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mauritius"}]},"q1131":{"id":"q1131","difficulty":0.6930747922,"question":"Which of these rivers is the longest?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Congo River","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"White Nile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madeira River"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yenisei River"}]},"q1132":{"id":"q1132","difficulty":0.6933615505,"question":"Yankee Stadium is in which part of New York City? ","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"The Bronx","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brooklyn"},{"id":"a3","text":"Manhattan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Queens"}]},"q1133":{"id":"q1133","difficulty":0.693585374,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Oman","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Portugal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q1134":{"id":"q1134","difficulty":0.6937579315,"question":"Port Vila is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vanuatu","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q1135":{"id":"q1135","difficulty":null,"question":"The Golden Gate Bridge can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"San Francisco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Dallas"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1136":{"id":"q1136","difficulty":0.6943087008,"question":"The Madeira River runs through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bolivia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guyana"}]},"q1137":{"id":"q1137","difficulty":0.695198484,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Papua New Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Niger"}]},"q1138":{"id":"q1138","difficulty":0.6954773312,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cameroon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kenya"},{"id":"a3","text":"United Kingdom"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q1139":{"id":"q1139","difficulty":0.6955699338,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Greece","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"}]},"q1140":{"id":"q1140","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Detroit Zoo?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Royal Oak","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Hobart"},{"id":"a4","text":" Australia\""}]},"q1141":{"id":"q1141","difficulty":0.6974047506,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Kingdom","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Pakistan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q1142":{"id":"q1142","difficulty":0.6974085854,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominican Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Singapore"},{"id":"a3","text":"Slovenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Solomon Islands"}]},"q1143":{"id":"q1143","difficulty":0.6975904939,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Niger","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malaysia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mozambique"}]},"q1144":{"id":"q1144","difficulty":0.6976568418,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Venezuela","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Colombia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a4","text":"Pakistan"}]},"q1145":{"id":"q1145","difficulty":0.2107264248,"question":"Las Palmas is in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Spain","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Britain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q1146":{"id":"q1146","difficulty":0.6977592467,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lesotho","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a4","text":"Republic of Ireland"}]},"q1147":{"id":"q1147","difficulty":0.6981006091,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Honduras","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Togo"}]},"q1148":{"id":"q1148","difficulty":0.6986181786,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Honduras","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kuwait"},{"id":"a3","text":"Panama"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q1149":{"id":"q1149","difficulty":0.6987165793,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Netherlands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lithuania"}]},"q1150":{"id":"q1150","difficulty":0.6995497127,"question":"Cornwall lies in which part of England?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Southwest","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Northeast"},{"id":"a3","text":"Northwest"},{"id":"a4","text":"Southeast"}]},"q1151":{"id":"q1151","difficulty":0.6999858498,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Italy","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a3","text":"Poland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zambia"}]},"q1152":{"id":"q1152","difficulty":0.7001264771,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a4","text":"Oman"}]},"q1153":{"id":"q1153","difficulty":0.7004184966,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nauru"}]},"q1154":{"id":"q1154","difficulty":0.700632706,"question":"In which of these countries could you see the Ob River?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Russia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Netherlands"}]},"q1155":{"id":"q1155","difficulty":0.7008516573,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Costa Rica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nicaragua"}]},"q1156":{"id":"q1156","difficulty":0.7015475078,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Montenegro","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jamaica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkmenistan"}]},"q1157":{"id":"q1157","difficulty":0.7016267712,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovakia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mongolia"}]},"q1158":{"id":"q1158","difficulty":0.7019104462,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cape Verde","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ecuador"}]},"q1159":{"id":"q1159","difficulty":0.7022974035,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jordan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Malawi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nepal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uzbekistan"}]},"q1160":{"id":"q1160","difficulty":0.7025658249,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"New Zealand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q1161":{"id":"q1161","difficulty":0.7031407093,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a3","text":"Norway"},{"id":"a4","text":"Togo"}]},"q1162":{"id":"q1162","difficulty":0.214287931,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lebanon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Carpathia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kasnia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kazirstan"}]},"q1163":{"id":"q1163","difficulty":0.703961745,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nigeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Libya"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mexico"}]},"q1164":{"id":"q1164","difficulty":0.704757584,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Niger"},{"id":"a3","text":"Romania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tanzania"}]},"q1165":{"id":"q1165","difficulty":0.7049522749,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Greece","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Sudan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yemen"}]},"q1166":{"id":"q1166","difficulty":0.70568205,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Republic of Ireland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Poland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Romania"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Kingdom"}]},"q1167":{"id":"q1167","difficulty":0.7061630978,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Andorra","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Montenegro"},{"id":"a3","text":"Qatar"},{"id":"a4","text":"Samoa"}]},"q1168":{"id":"q1168","difficulty":0.7072838877,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Palau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lesotho"}]},"q1169":{"id":"q1169","difficulty":0.7073463057,"question":"The capital of Cape Verde is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Praia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Moroni"},{"id":"a4","text":"Khartoum"}]},"q1170":{"id":"q1170","difficulty":0.7073994679,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Qatar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Netherlands"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Arab Emirates"}]},"q1171":{"id":"q1171","difficulty":0.2150257357,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Canada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominican Republic"}]},"q1172":{"id":"q1172","difficulty":0.7075298447,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mongolia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"New Zealand"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nicaragua"}]},"q1173":{"id":"q1173","difficulty":0.7077051389,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sri Lanka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Korea"}]},"q1174":{"id":"q1174","difficulty":0.7077074776,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Arab Emirates","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Syria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zambia"}]},"q1175":{"id":"q1175","difficulty":0.7089334876,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominican Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Libya"}]},"q1176":{"id":"q1176","difficulty":0.7093694005,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sweden","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malaysia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mali"}]},"q1177":{"id":"q1177","difficulty":0.7094167616,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"El Salvador"}]},"q1178":{"id":"q1178","difficulty":0.7094743143,"question":"The capital of Swaziland is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mbabane","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Yaoundé"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dakar"}]},"q1179":{"id":"q1179","difficulty":0.7102805746,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sweden","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mauritania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nigeria"}]},"q1180":{"id":"q1180","difficulty":0.7104457614,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a3","text":"Serbia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tunisia"}]},"q1181":{"id":"q1181","difficulty":0.2151814835,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Italy?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Milan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Copenhagen"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cologne"},{"id":"a4","text":"London"}]},"q1182":{"id":"q1182","difficulty":0.7111531965,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea-Bissau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kuwait"}]},"q1183":{"id":"q1183","difficulty":0.7111700815,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Estonia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moldova"}]},"q1184":{"id":"q1184","difficulty":0.7115757741,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a3","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q1185":{"id":"q1185","difficulty":0.7118921643,"question":"What is the most populated city north of the arctic circle?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Murmansk","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aberdeen"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fairbanks"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ottawa"}]},"q1186":{"id":"q1186","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Dunkin' Donuts Center?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Providence","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Augusta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1187":{"id":"q1187","difficulty":0.7120678288,"question":"Ecuador contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guayaquil","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a3","text":"Buenos Aires"},{"id":"a4","text":"Medellín"}]},"q1188":{"id":"q1188","difficulty":0.7126073577,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Finland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q1189":{"id":"q1189","difficulty":0.7127597677,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Palau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiribati"}]},"q1190":{"id":"q1190","difficulty":0.712831118,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Grenada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a3","text":"Marshall Islands"},{"id":"a4","text":"San Marino"}]},"q1191":{"id":"q1191","difficulty":0.7132680515,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Angola","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Oman"},{"id":"a3","text":"Paraguay"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sweden"}]},"q1192":{"id":"q1192","difficulty":0.2158420265,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Thailand?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bangkok","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Johor Bahru"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chittagong"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mandalay"}]},"q1193":{"id":"q1193","difficulty":0.7137598872,"question":"The River Rhine flows into the sea by which European city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rotterdam","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Amsterdam"},{"id":"a3","text":"Copenhagen"},{"id":"a4","text":"Munich"}]},"q1194":{"id":"q1194","difficulty":0.7141388708,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"New Zealand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a4","text":"Papua New Guinea"}]},"q1195":{"id":"q1195","difficulty":0.7146498849,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saudi Arabia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a3","text":"Russia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tanzania"}]},"q1196":{"id":"q1196","difficulty":0.714713447,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tonga","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Malta"},{"id":"a3","text":"Palau"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"}]},"q1197":{"id":"q1197","difficulty":0.7149707893,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bulgaria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kuwait"},{"id":"a3","text":"Moldova"},{"id":"a4","text":"Oman"}]},"q1198":{"id":"q1198","difficulty":0.7157039193,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominican Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q1199":{"id":"q1199","difficulty":0.7163892581,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Czech Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Norway"}]},"q1200":{"id":"q1200","difficulty":0.7167812069,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jordan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Qatar"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sierra Leone"}]},"q1201":{"id":"q1201","difficulty":0.7169581621,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Austria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moldova"}]},"q1202":{"id":"q1202","difficulty":0.717247189,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tajikistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a4","text":"Norway"}]},"q1203":{"id":"q1203","difficulty":0.7183535577,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Andorra","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Marshall Islands"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nauru"},{"id":"a4","text":"Palau"}]},"q1204":{"id":"q1204","difficulty":0.7184260441,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belize"}]},"q1205":{"id":"q1205","difficulty":0.718978136,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ghana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mozambique"},{"id":"a3","text":"Thailand"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkmenistan"}]},"q1206":{"id":"q1206","difficulty":0.7194190588,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guatemala","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malaysia"}]},"q1207":{"id":"q1207","difficulty":0.719833796,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kyrgyzstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ukraine"}]},"q1208":{"id":"q1208","difficulty":0.7201642624,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Honduras"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jordan"},{"id":"a4","text":"North Korea"}]},"q1209":{"id":"q1209","difficulty":0.7207499548,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkmenistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Peru"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q1210":{"id":"q1210","difficulty":0.074322583,"question":"In which country would you find The Leaning Tower of Pisa?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Italy","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Monaco"},{"id":"a4","text":"Poland"}]},"q1211":{"id":"q1211","difficulty":0.7209138868,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Djibouti"}]},"q1212":{"id":"q1212","difficulty":0.7209531867,"question":"Which country's capital is Windhoek?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Namibia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cape Verde"}]},"q1213":{"id":"q1213","difficulty":0.721315063,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"El Salvador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Namibia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovenia"}]},"q1214":{"id":"q1214","difficulty":0.7222385116,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nauru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Maldives"}]},"q1215":{"id":"q1215","difficulty":0.7222490807,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea-Bissau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Suriname"}]},"q1216":{"id":"q1216","difficulty":0.7227027867,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Togo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Djibouti"}]},"q1217":{"id":"q1217","difficulty":0.7229180345,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ukraine","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iran"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mexico"}]},"q1218":{"id":"q1218","difficulty":0.7244437284,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Costa Rica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Luxembourg"}]},"q1219":{"id":"q1219","difficulty":0.7244614722,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Norway","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jordan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mali"}]},"q1220":{"id":"q1220","difficulty":0.7245829878,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Niger","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Indonesia"}]},"q1221":{"id":"q1221","difficulty":0.2165427522,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Fiji","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Panama"}]},"q1222":{"id":"q1222","difficulty":0.7246861178,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Singapore","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zambia"}]},"q1223":{"id":"q1223","difficulty":null,"question":"Ascend Amphitheater can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Nashville","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Chicago"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1224":{"id":"q1224","difficulty":0.7250160247,"question":"Which country lies between Panama and Nicaragua?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Costa Rica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a3","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guatemala"}]},"q1225":{"id":"q1225","difficulty":0.7251174849,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Djibouti"}]},"q1226":{"id":"q1226","difficulty":0.7255769412,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Côte d’Ivoire","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gambia"}]},"q1227":{"id":"q1227","difficulty":0.7258123086,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Singapore","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"}]},"q1228":{"id":"q1228","difficulty":0.7261136984,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Austria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guatemala"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madagascar"},{"id":"a4","text":"Senegal"}]},"q1229":{"id":"q1229","difficulty":0.7261543862,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ecuador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sweden"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkmenistan"}]},"q1230":{"id":"q1230","difficulty":0.7265267447,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sierra Leone","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea"}]},"q1231":{"id":"q1231","difficulty":0.7265782451,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Norway","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nepal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Romania"}]},"q1232":{"id":"q1232","difficulty":0.2173722231,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ghana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Axphain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Buenaventura"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chernarus"}]},"q1233":{"id":"q1233","difficulty":0.726723211,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Botswana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Israel"}]},"q1234":{"id":"q1234","difficulty":0.7270662434,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Luxembourg","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q1235":{"id":"q1235","difficulty":0.7270678232,"question":"In which year was Malawi declared a republic?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"1966","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"1946"},{"id":"a3","text":"1986"},{"id":"a4","text":"2006"}]},"q1236":{"id":"q1236","difficulty":0.7274048714,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burundi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"South Korea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sri Lanka"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Arab Emirates"}]},"q1237":{"id":"q1237","difficulty":0.7277997565,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Moldova","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kuwait"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vanuatu"}]},"q1238":{"id":"q1238","difficulty":0.728082615,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Netherlands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kenya"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sudan"}]},"q1239":{"id":"q1239","difficulty":0.7286339006,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Namibia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sweden"},{"id":"a4","text":"Thailand"}]},"q1240":{"id":"q1240","difficulty":0.7293515545,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lesotho","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burundi"}]},"q1241":{"id":"q1241","difficulty":0.7298172531,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brunei","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jamaica"}]},"q1242":{"id":"q1242","difficulty":0.7303447898,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Comoros","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Swaziland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Trinidad and Tobago"}]},"q1243":{"id":"q1243","difficulty":0.2173752638,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Mexico?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mexico City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San Pedro Sula"},{"id":"a3","text":"Los Angeles"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guatemala City"}]},"q1244":{"id":"q1244","difficulty":0.7303725986,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burkina Faso","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Central African Republic"}]},"q1245":{"id":"q1245","difficulty":0.7304492195,"question":"The capital of Comoros is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Moroni","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Pretoria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tripoli"}]},"q1246":{"id":"q1246","difficulty":0.7304492195,"question":"Moroni is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Comoros","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cape Verde"}]},"q1247":{"id":"q1247","difficulty":0.7307208691,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nepal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Somalia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sweden"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zimbabwe"}]},"q1248":{"id":"q1248","difficulty":0.7308920163,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kenya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iran"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mali"}]},"q1249":{"id":"q1249","difficulty":0.7311124331,"question":"What's the name of the currency used in Laos?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kip","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bap"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lop"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tup"}]},"q1250":{"id":"q1250","difficulty":0.7311285661,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zimbabwe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mongolia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Morocco"}]},"q1251":{"id":"q1251","difficulty":0.731236032,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cameroon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Portugal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zimbabwe"}]},"q1252":{"id":"q1252","difficulty":0.2186854594,"question":"Mexico does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"St. John's","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Puebla"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ciudad del Carmen"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mexico City"}]},"q1253":{"id":"q1253","difficulty":0.7317259817,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Myanmar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kazakhstan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madagascar"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yemen"}]},"q1254":{"id":"q1254","difficulty":0.7317987908,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mali","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Oman"},{"id":"a3","text":"Paraguay"},{"id":"a4","text":"Somalia"}]},"q1255":{"id":"q1255","difficulty":0.7321037854,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cambodia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uganda"}]},"q1256":{"id":"q1256","difficulty":0.7321834082,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Australia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ukraine"}]},"q1257":{"id":"q1257","difficulty":0.7322295525,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Czech Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a3","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uganda"}]},"q1258":{"id":"q1258","difficulty":0.7333119231,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ecuador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Latvia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malawi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Syria"}]},"q1259":{"id":"q1259","difficulty":0.7341023723,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kyrgyzstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Somalia"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Sudan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zambia"}]},"q1260":{"id":"q1260","difficulty":0.734710321,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kuwait","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lesotho"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lithuania"}]},"q1261":{"id":"q1261","difficulty":0.2194646242,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Russia"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q1262":{"id":"q1262","difficulty":0.7357679914,"question":"\"“The Garden of England\"\" is the nickname of which English county?\"","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kent","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cumbria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Devon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yorkshire"}]},"q1263":{"id":"q1263","difficulty":0.7357930334,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brunei","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guyana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Qatar"}]},"q1264":{"id":"q1264","difficulty":0.7362471307,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q1265":{"id":"q1265","difficulty":0.7367097814,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chile","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uzbekistan"}]},"q1266":{"id":"q1266","difficulty":0.7367354468,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belize","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lithuania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Namibia"}]},"q1267":{"id":"q1267","difficulty":0.7370380155,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malaysia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guyana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sierra Leone"}]},"q1268":{"id":"q1268","difficulty":0.7370450332,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kiribati"},{"id":"a3","text":"Monaco"},{"id":"a4","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe"}]},"q1269":{"id":"q1269","difficulty":0.737325371,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tonga","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiribati"}]},"q1270":{"id":"q1270","difficulty":0.7374224975,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Madagascar"}]},"q1271":{"id":"q1271","difficulty":0.2199928092,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sweden","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominica"}]},"q1272":{"id":"q1272","difficulty":0.738095168,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zimbabwe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"Morocco"}]},"q1273":{"id":"q1273","difficulty":0.7380960178,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sierra Leone","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guyana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tunisia"}]},"q1274":{"id":"q1274","difficulty":0.7382953181,"question":"In which capital city would you find Euston railway station?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"London","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belfast"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cardiff"},{"id":"a4","text":"Edinburgh"}]},"q1275":{"id":"q1275","difficulty":0.7384618503,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bhutan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a3","text":"Slovenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vanuatu"}]},"q1276":{"id":"q1276","difficulty":0.7387884244,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lithuania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jordan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkmenistan"}]},"q1277":{"id":"q1277","difficulty":0.7388072241,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Albania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q1278":{"id":"q1278","difficulty":null,"question":"Harry P. Leu Gardens can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Orlando","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Barcelona"},{"id":"a4","text":" Spain\""}]},"q1279":{"id":"q1279","difficulty":0.7389823557,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Thailand"},{"id":"a3","text":"Uzbekistan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Venezuela"}]},"q1280":{"id":"q1280","difficulty":0.7389974085,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uzbekistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Venezuela"}]},"q1281":{"id":"q1281","difficulty":0.2213881075,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bhutan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Blefuscu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kumbolaland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Norland"}]},"q1282":{"id":"q1282","difficulty":0.7390086312,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tunisia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mozambique"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sudan"}]},"q1283":{"id":"q1283","difficulty":0.739120355,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkey","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kazakhstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sudan"}]},"q1284":{"id":"q1284","difficulty":0.7401789912,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Central African Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ghana"}]},"q1285":{"id":"q1285","difficulty":null,"question":"The Three Gorges Dam can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Sandouping","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" China\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Golden"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1286":{"id":"q1286","difficulty":0.7418676383,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"San Marino","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tonga"}]},"q1287":{"id":"q1287","difficulty":0.7419662281,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Djibouti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Congo"}]},"q1288":{"id":"q1288","difficulty":0.7435900519,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lebanon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Latvia"}]},"q1289":{"id":"q1289","difficulty":0.7440989147,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Trinidad and Tobago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea-Bissau"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovenia"}]},"q1290":{"id":"q1290","difficulty":0.744238628,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Comoros","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Central African Republic"}]},"q1291":{"id":"q1291","difficulty":0.7447480725,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tajikistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Croatia"}]},"q1292":{"id":"q1292","difficulty":0.7471770434,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gabon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eritrea"}]},"q1293":{"id":"q1293","difficulty":0.7477247469,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Grenada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Canada"}]},"q1294":{"id":"q1294","difficulty":0.7478804227,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovakia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guatemala"},{"id":"a4","text":"Rwanda"}]},"q1295":{"id":"q1295","difficulty":0.7479861532,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Africa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a3","text":"Russia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q1296":{"id":"q1296","difficulty":0.7506285206,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lesotho","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Montenegro"},{"id":"a4","text":"Trinidad and Tobago"}]},"q1297":{"id":"q1297","difficulty":0.2214920786,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Algeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a4","text":"China"}]},"q1298":{"id":"q1298","difficulty":0.7513127494,"question":"In which Midland city center is there an area called the Lace Market?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nottingham","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Birmingham"},{"id":"a3","text":"Leicester"},{"id":"a4","text":"Stoke"}]},"q1299":{"id":"q1299","difficulty":0.7513922923,"question":"The famous Spanish Steps are located in this city","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rome","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barcelona"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madrid"},{"id":"a4","text":"Milan"}]},"q1300":{"id":"q1300","difficulty":0.7516051989,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lebanon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kuwait"},{"id":"a4","text":"Panama"}]},"q1301":{"id":"q1301","difficulty":0.7526187653,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritius","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Lucia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Seychelles"}]},"q1302":{"id":"q1302","difficulty":0.7532035553,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Marshall Islands"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tuvalu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q1303":{"id":"q1303","difficulty":0.7532287116,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nauru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q1304":{"id":"q1304","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Before the introduction of the Euro","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"[NULL]","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Escudo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lira"},{"id":"a4","text":"Peseta"}]},"q1305":{"id":"q1305","difficulty":0.7547577855,"question":"What's the meaning of the name of the African country Eritrea?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Red","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Hot"},{"id":"a3","text":"Pepper"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sea"}]},"q1306":{"id":"q1306","difficulty":0.7548646938,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Greece","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a4","text":"Venezuela"}]},"q1307":{"id":"q1307","difficulty":null,"question":"Lady Bird Lake can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Austin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Bozeman"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1308":{"id":"q1308","difficulty":0.07500788534,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Italy","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Archenland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Blefuscu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bolumbia"}]},"q1309":{"id":"q1309","difficulty":0.2217400235,"question":"Ottawa is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Canada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominican Republic"}]},"q1310":{"id":"q1310","difficulty":0.7551007742,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tanzania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mali"},{"id":"a3","text":"Peru"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zimbabwe"}]},"q1311":{"id":"q1311","difficulty":0.7553718502,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Grenada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nauru"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q1312":{"id":"q1312","difficulty":0.7574728838,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Fiji","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lebanon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Singapore"}]},"q1313":{"id":"q1313","difficulty":0.75770206,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Denmark","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Israel"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jordan"}]},"q1314":{"id":"q1314","difficulty":0.7580309435,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guinea-Bissau"},{"id":"a3","text":"Singapore"},{"id":"a4","text":"Switzerland"}]},"q1315":{"id":"q1315","difficulty":0.7582983858,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nicaragua","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Japan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Norway"}]},"q1316":{"id":"q1316","difficulty":0.7596345178,"question":"The capital of Saint Kitts and Nevis is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Basseterre","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guatemala City"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kingstown"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nassau"}]},"q1317":{"id":"q1317","difficulty":0.7597069235,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Thailand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"Senegal"}]},"q1318":{"id":"q1318","difficulty":0.2224155853,"question":"Cuba contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Havana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San José"},{"id":"a3","text":"Los Angeles"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mexico City"}]},"q1319":{"id":"q1319","difficulty":0.7597512521,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Grenada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lithuania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mauritius"}]},"q1320":{"id":"q1320","difficulty":0.7597937288,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Republic of Macedonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Swaziland"}]},"q1321":{"id":"q1321","difficulty":0.7597966619,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Latvia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Norway"},{"id":"a4","text":"Togo"}]},"q1322":{"id":"q1322","difficulty":0.759999131,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Senegal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Serbia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sierra Leone"},{"id":"a4","text":"Switzerland"}]},"q1323":{"id":"q1323","difficulty":0.7604516689,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"New Zealand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Morocco"},{"id":"a3","text":"Myanmar"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkmenistan"}]},"q1324":{"id":"q1324","difficulty":0.7606058961,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Djibouti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sri Lanka"}]},"q1325":{"id":"q1325","difficulty":0.7609644397,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Angola","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a3","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mali"}]},"q1326":{"id":"q1326","difficulty":0.7617152496,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Albania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jordan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lebanon"}]},"q1327":{"id":"q1327","difficulty":0.7618525824,"question":"Where is the Eurostar London terminal located?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"St Pancras","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canary Wharf"},{"id":"a3","text":"London Bridge"},{"id":"a4","text":"Waterloo"}]},"q1328":{"id":"q1328","difficulty":0.7629947028,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Romania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ukraine"},{"id":"a3","text":"Uzbekistan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Venezuela"}]},"q1329":{"id":"q1329","difficulty":0.2228340825,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in China?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nineveh Governorate","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Beijing"},{"id":"a3","text":"Shanghai"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tianjin"}]},"q1330":{"id":"q1330","difficulty":0.7633584779,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Djibouti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kiribati"},{"id":"a4","text":"Samoa"}]},"q1331":{"id":"q1331","difficulty":0.7642148419,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nicaragua","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jordan"}]},"q1332":{"id":"q1332","difficulty":0.7648612608,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uzbekistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Niger"},{"id":"a4","text":"Senegal"}]},"q1333":{"id":"q1333","difficulty":0.7654464258,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Samoa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Suriname"}]},"q1334":{"id":"q1334","difficulty":0.7656714427,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Timor-Leste","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea-Bissau"}]},"q1335":{"id":"q1335","difficulty":0.7664548057,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guyana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mauritania"}]},"q1336":{"id":"q1336","difficulty":0.7672965529,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Papua New Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Honduras"}]},"q1337":{"id":"q1337","difficulty":0.7677004701,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Palau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea-Bissau"},{"id":"a4","text":"Swaziland"}]},"q1338":{"id":"q1338","difficulty":0.7686539965,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Côte d’Ivoire","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a4","text":"Portugal"}]},"q1339":{"id":"q1339","difficulty":0.223435772,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Republic of Ireland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominica"}]},"q1340":{"id":"q1340","difficulty":0.7720255441,"question":"Which of these is not a cape in America?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cape Point","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Chidley"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Cod"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cape Horn"}]},"q1341":{"id":"q1341","difficulty":0.772029844,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Georgia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Netherlands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Switzerland"}]},"q1342":{"id":"q1342","difficulty":0.7722573293,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burundi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equatorial Guinea"}]},"q1343":{"id":"q1343","difficulty":0.7740743506,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Swaziland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Central African Republic"}]},"q1344":{"id":"q1344","difficulty":0.7746165172,"question":"Libreville is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gabon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Eritrea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gambia"}]},"q1345":{"id":"q1345","difficulty":0.7758405451,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Montenegro"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vanuatu"}]},"q1346":{"id":"q1346","difficulty":0.7760366311,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yemen","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Arab Emirates"}]},"q1347":{"id":"q1347","difficulty":0.7763191567,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Suriname","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Maldives"},{"id":"a3","text":"Seychelles"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tonga"}]},"q1348":{"id":"q1348","difficulty":0.776521229,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guatemala","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Slovakia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tajikistan"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Arab Emirates"}]},"q1349":{"id":"q1349","difficulty":0.2235072217,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Netherlands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q1350":{"id":"q1350","difficulty":0.7766596438,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ukraine","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Indonesia"}]},"q1351":{"id":"q1351","difficulty":null,"question":"How long is the Millau Bridge in France?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"8","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"000ft long\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"12"},{"id":"a4","text":"000ft long\""}]},"q1352":{"id":"q1352","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Faneuil Hall?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Boston","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Amritsar"},{"id":"a4","text":" India\""}]},"q1353":{"id":"q1353","difficulty":0.7772271115,"question":"What is the capital of Vanuatu?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Port Vila","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"South Tarawa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ngerulmud"},{"id":"a4","text":"Wellington"}]},"q1354":{"id":"q1354","difficulty":0.7773672393,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Kingdom","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Venezuela"}]},"q1355":{"id":"q1355","difficulty":0.7778149218,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Paraguay"},{"id":"a4","text":"Somalia"}]},"q1356":{"id":"q1356","difficulty":0.7785215801,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Namibia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Panama"},{"id":"a4","text":"Paraguay"}]},"q1357":{"id":"q1357","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Park Meadows?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Lone Tree","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Chicago"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1358":{"id":"q1358","difficulty":0.7793105243,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Panama","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kuwait"},{"id":"a4","text":"Swaziland"}]},"q1359":{"id":"q1359","difficulty":0.2245622047,"question":"Jakarta is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Indonesia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Israel"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jordan"}]},"q1360":{"id":"q1360","difficulty":0.7806349011,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Afghanistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kazakhstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saudi Arabia"}]},"q1361":{"id":"q1361","difficulty":0.7809840011,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jordan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"New Zealand"}]},"q1362":{"id":"q1362","difficulty":0.7814663172,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Côte d’Ivoire","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iceland"}]},"q1363":{"id":"q1363","difficulty":0.7826750493,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nicaragua","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Latvia"}]},"q1364":{"id":"q1364","difficulty":0.7828989669,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Papua New Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jamaica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Liberia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Qatar"}]},"q1365":{"id":"q1365","difficulty":0.7830593176,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cuba","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Papua New Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovakia"}]},"q1366":{"id":"q1366","difficulty":0.7830982222,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Syria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a3","text":"Morocco"},{"id":"a4","text":"Myanmar"}]},"q1367":{"id":"q1367","difficulty":0.7836742686,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gabon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sierra Leone"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Arab Emirates"}]},"q1368":{"id":"q1368","difficulty":0.7849191346,"question":"Which sea is between North Australia and South-West New Guinea?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Arafura","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aragats"},{"id":"a3","text":"Aral"},{"id":"a4","text":"Aricone"}]},"q1369":{"id":"q1369","difficulty":0.7859477124,"question":"Which of these rivers is the longest?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mekong","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"White Nile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indus River"},{"id":"a4","text":"Purus River"}]},"q1370":{"id":"q1370","difficulty":0.787088662,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Palau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malta"}]},"q1371":{"id":"q1371","difficulty":0.7871627335,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vietnam","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a3","text":"Peru"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Africa"}]},"q1372":{"id":"q1372","difficulty":0.7878722428,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guatemala"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malawi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Republic of Ireland"}]},"q1373":{"id":"q1373","difficulty":0.7879709565,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gabon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a3","text":"Oman"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q1374":{"id":"q1374","difficulty":0.7903453444,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Eritrea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lesotho"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q1375":{"id":"q1375","difficulty":0.7916510955,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahamas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nauru"},{"id":"a4","text":"Trinidad and Tobago"}]},"q1376":{"id":"q1376","difficulty":0.7949924954,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Finland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iran"},{"id":"a3","text":"Yemen"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zambia"}]},"q1377":{"id":"q1377","difficulty":0.7951463816,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belarus","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a3","text":"Somalia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ukraine"}]},"q1378":{"id":"q1378","difficulty":0.7955154989,"question":"Yamoussoukro is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Côte d’Ivoire","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q1379":{"id":"q1379","difficulty":0.2254820623,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ethiopia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a4","text":"India"}]},"q1380":{"id":"q1380","difficulty":0.796448859,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Honduras","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Netherlands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sri Lanka"}]},"q1381":{"id":"q1381","difficulty":0.7965116279,"question":"The Yenisei River runs through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mongolia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Norway"},{"id":"a3","text":"Slovakia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Switzerland"}]},"q1382":{"id":"q1382","difficulty":0.7968871755,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cape Verde","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mauritius"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"}]},"q1383":{"id":"q1383","difficulty":0.7998005793,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Comoros","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a4","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe"}]},"q1384":{"id":"q1384","difficulty":0.801067931,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yemen","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Romania"}]},"q1385":{"id":"q1385","difficulty":0.8015250897,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Armenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lebanon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Paraguay"}]},"q1386":{"id":"q1386","difficulty":0.8020071238,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Solomon Islands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Lucia"}]},"q1387":{"id":"q1387","difficulty":0.8024437716,"question":"Which African city was once known as Salisbury?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Harare","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulawayo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Town"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lusaka"}]},"q1388":{"id":"q1388","difficulty":0.8031762428,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sierra Leone","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lesotho"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mongolia"}]},"q1389":{"id":"q1389","difficulty":0.2254938683,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"New Zealand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a3","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guyana"}]},"q1390":{"id":"q1390","difficulty":0.8032581471,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Poland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tanzania"}]},"q1391":{"id":"q1391","difficulty":0.8036022966,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Timor-Leste","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mauritius"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q1392":{"id":"q1392","difficulty":0.8050965153,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uzbekistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Senegal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q1393":{"id":"q1393","difficulty":0.806129402,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"San Marino","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q1394":{"id":"q1394","difficulty":0.8081232494,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paraguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Madagascar"}]},"q1395":{"id":"q1395","difficulty":0.8090694651,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Andorra","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Haiti"}]},"q1396":{"id":"q1396","difficulty":0.8099859835,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Georgia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Togo"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Arab Emirates"}]},"q1397":{"id":"q1397","difficulty":0.8102786199,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bulgaria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Norway"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uganda"}]},"q1398":{"id":"q1398","difficulty":0.8103827826,"question":"The capital of Solomon Islands is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Honiara","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"South Tarawa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ngerulmud"},{"id":"a4","text":"Wellington"}]},"q1399":{"id":"q1399","difficulty":0.2255374938,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Poland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chad"}]},"q1400":{"id":"q1400","difficulty":0.8118785273,"question":"What fraction of the world's population lives in Africa?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"1/8/2017","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"1/12/2017"},{"id":"a3","text":"1/4/2017"},{"id":"a4","text":"1/6/2017"}]},"q1401":{"id":"q1401","difficulty":0.8121460508,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cape Verde","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a3","text":"Maldives"},{"id":"a4","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe"}]},"q1402":{"id":"q1402","difficulty":0.8140317809,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bolivia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Niger"},{"id":"a3","text":"North Korea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saudi Arabia"}]},"q1403":{"id":"q1403","difficulty":0.815383544,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jamaica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nicaragua"},{"id":"a4","text":"Serbia"}]},"q1404":{"id":"q1404","difficulty":0.8159839038,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mali","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Lebanon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Papua New Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Togo"}]},"q1405":{"id":"q1405","difficulty":0.8167160731,"question":"Honiara is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Solomon Islands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiribati"}]},"q1406":{"id":"q1406","difficulty":0.8176659157,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hungary","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Poland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q1407":{"id":"q1407","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find Thy National Park","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"[NULL]","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Netherlands"}]},"q1408":{"id":"q1408","difficulty":0.8189998804,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Haiti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Georgia"}]},"q1409":{"id":"q1409","difficulty":0.8207869656,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a3","text":"Slovakia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkmenistan"}]},"q1410":{"id":"q1410","difficulty":null,"question":"What is the capital of United States of America?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Washington","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" D.C.\""},{"id":"a3","text":"Chicago"},{"id":"a4","text":"New York City"}]},"q1411":{"id":"q1411","difficulty":0.2265789339,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Luxembourg","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Fe'ausi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kashfar"},{"id":"a4","text":"Latveria"}]},"q1412":{"id":"q1412","difficulty":0.8209404338,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Republic of Ireland"}]},"q1413":{"id":"q1413","difficulty":0.821754282,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Costa Rica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Haiti"}]},"q1414":{"id":"q1414","difficulty":0.8217832752,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tunisia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sierra Leone"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Arab Emirates"}]},"q1415":{"id":"q1415","difficulty":0.8222884879,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jamaica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Liberia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lithuania"}]},"q1416":{"id":"q1416","difficulty":0.8227808177,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"France","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Japan"}]},"q1417":{"id":"q1417","difficulty":0.8258229999,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Madagascar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Israel"},{"id":"a3","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Sudan"}]},"q1418":{"id":"q1418","difficulty":0.8261863484,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brunei","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Lucia"},{"id":"a4","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe"}]},"q1419":{"id":"q1419","difficulty":0.827393119,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vanuatu","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q1420":{"id":"q1420","difficulty":0.8274874306,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nepal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jordan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lesotho"}]},"q1421":{"id":"q1421","difficulty":0.8277413235,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Republic of Ireland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Honduras"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tunisia"}]},"q1422":{"id":"q1422","difficulty":0.8278727168,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Oman","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iceland"}]},"q1423":{"id":"q1423","difficulty":0.8298917264,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Croatia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Honduras"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sweden"}]},"q1424":{"id":"q1424","difficulty":null,"question":"\"What is the longest river in Tasmania","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"[NULL]","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"South Esk River"},{"id":"a3","text":"Coopers Creek"},{"id":"a4","text":"Murray River"}]},"q1425":{"id":"q1425","difficulty":0.8308260268,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a4","text":"Central African Republic"}]},"q1426":{"id":"q1426","difficulty":null,"question":"Merchandise Mart can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Chicago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Bloomington"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1427":{"id":"q1427","difficulty":0.8325578377,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nauru"},{"id":"a3","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q1428":{"id":"q1428","difficulty":0.8326351427,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Morocco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Poland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Senegal"}]},"q1429":{"id":"q1429","difficulty":0.8341714488,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Lucia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"}]},"q1430":{"id":"q1430","difficulty":0.2278699558,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Archenland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Emmeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eriador"}]},"q1431":{"id":"q1431","difficulty":0.8342166805,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Switzerland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a3","text":"Laos"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sierra Leone"}]},"q1432":{"id":"q1432","difficulty":0.8343506175,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Myanmar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ghana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uzbekistan"}]},"q1433":{"id":"q1433","difficulty":0.8357641296,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mozambique","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a3","text":"Syria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zambia"}]},"q1434":{"id":"q1434","difficulty":0.8360717628,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liberia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Papua New Guinea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Paraguay"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uganda"}]},"q1435":{"id":"q1435","difficulty":0.8376524409,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Latvia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kuwait"},{"id":"a3","text":"Montenegro"},{"id":"a4","text":"Samoa"}]},"q1436":{"id":"q1436","difficulty":0.8401707443,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Somalia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q1437":{"id":"q1437","difficulty":0.8402453408,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Laos","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jordan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Liberia"}]},"q1438":{"id":"q1438","difficulty":0.84182681,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Libya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Portugal"}]},"q1439":{"id":"q1439","difficulty":0.8419613464,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a3","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q1440":{"id":"q1440","difficulty":0.2279340151,"question":"Which of these rivers is the longest?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Amazon River","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"White Nile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mississippi River"},{"id":"a4","text":"Niger River"}]},"q1441":{"id":"q1441","difficulty":0.8422748925,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ethiopia"}]},"q1442":{"id":"q1442","difficulty":0.8425690848,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Maldives"},{"id":"a4","text":"Republic of Macedonia"}]},"q1443":{"id":"q1443","difficulty":0.8436551293,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Czech Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Niger"},{"id":"a4","text":"Peru"}]},"q1444":{"id":"q1444","difficulty":0.8442893821,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Central African Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cuba"}]},"q1445":{"id":"q1445","difficulty":0.845959596,"question":"The city of Vancouver is on which river?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Fraser","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mackenzie"},{"id":"a3","text":"St Lawrence"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yukon"}]},"q1446":{"id":"q1446","difficulty":0.8476478598,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Peru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Madagascar"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mozambique"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ukraine"}]},"q1447":{"id":"q1447","difficulty":0.8478361896,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rwanda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a4","text":"Panama"}]},"q1448":{"id":"q1448","difficulty":0.8502880295,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kiribati"},{"id":"a3","text":"Marshall Islands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"}]},"q1449":{"id":"q1449","difficulty":0.8504556239,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hungary","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malawi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saudi Arabia"}]},"q1450":{"id":"q1450","difficulty":0.8513897088,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Papua New Guinea"}]},"q1451":{"id":"q1451","difficulty":0.2281530183,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Barbados","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Farfelu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kumranistan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nukehavistan"}]},"q1452":{"id":"q1452","difficulty":0.8514188278,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malawi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Israel"},{"id":"a4","text":"Portugal"}]},"q1453":{"id":"q1453","difficulty":0.8521790555,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Solomon Islands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mauritius"}]},"q1454":{"id":"q1454","difficulty":0.8525585724,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritius","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lebanon"}]},"q1455":{"id":"q1455","difficulty":null,"question":"The Cloisters can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"New York City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Chicago"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1456":{"id":"q1456","difficulty":0.8536472064,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Switzerland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guinea-Bissau"},{"id":"a3","text":"Latvia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Norway"}]},"q1457":{"id":"q1457","difficulty":0.8545947529,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nauru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q1458":{"id":"q1458","difficulty":0.8547796121,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Eritrea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Netherlands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sierra Leone"}]},"q1459":{"id":"q1459","difficulty":0.8551793524,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Palau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a3","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q1460":{"id":"q1460","difficulty":0.8565654648,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burkina Faso","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a3","text":"Portugal"},{"id":"a4","text":"United Arab Emirates"}]},"q1461":{"id":"q1461","difficulty":0.8568131453,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Germany","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a3","text":"Morocco"},{"id":"a4","text":"Myanmar"}]},"q1462":{"id":"q1462","difficulty":0.2289493948,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chile","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q1463":{"id":"q1463","difficulty":0.8568829166,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Benin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Sierra Leone"},{"id":"a3","text":"Slovakia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkmenistan"}]},"q1464":{"id":"q1464","difficulty":0.86047919,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uruguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jordan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Norway"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovakia"}]},"q1465":{"id":"q1465","difficulty":0.8633114516,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uganda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a4","text":"Egypt"}]},"q1466":{"id":"q1466","difficulty":0.8654741169,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cuba","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Togo"}]},"q1467":{"id":"q1467","difficulty":0.8657829791,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burundi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea-Bissau"},{"id":"a4","text":"New Zealand"}]},"q1468":{"id":"q1468","difficulty":0.8679044519,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Lucia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Marshall Islands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"}]},"q1469":{"id":"q1469","difficulty":0.8687653068,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uruguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a4","text":"Morocco"}]},"q1470":{"id":"q1470","difficulty":0.8692033294,"question":"What is the second largest island of the United States?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kodiak Island","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Hawai'i (The Big Island)"},{"id":"a3","text":"Prince of Wales Island"},{"id":"a4","text":"Puerto Rico"}]},"q1471":{"id":"q1471","difficulty":0.8692110634,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mozambique","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Thailand"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q1472":{"id":"q1472","difficulty":0.229219111,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saudi Arabia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q1473":{"id":"q1473","difficulty":0.869807805,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kyrgyzstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Republic of Macedonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q1474":{"id":"q1474","difficulty":0.8711073174,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Armenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liberia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malawi"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Korea"}]},"q1475":{"id":"q1475","difficulty":0.8717170204,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Haiti"}]},"q1476":{"id":"q1476","difficulty":0.8728902919,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovakia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jordan"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Korea"}]},"q1477":{"id":"q1477","difficulty":0.8777047458,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vanuatu","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tonga"}]},"q1478":{"id":"q1478","difficulty":0.8777386034,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malawi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Latvia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Panama"},{"id":"a4","text":"Rwanda"}]},"q1479":{"id":"q1479","difficulty":0.8786659438,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guyana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eritrea"}]},"q1480":{"id":"q1480","difficulty":0.8799621928,"question":"The Purus River runs through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brazil","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Suriname"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q1481":{"id":"q1481","difficulty":0.8818070502,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belarus","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Norway"},{"id":"a4","text":"Republic of Ireland"}]},"q1482":{"id":"q1482","difficulty":0.8821783387,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea-Bissau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lesotho"}]},"q1483":{"id":"q1483","difficulty":0.2293491253,"question":"What is the capital of Kuwait?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kuwait City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jerusalem"},{"id":"a3","text":"Singapore"},{"id":"a4","text":"Islamabad"}]},"q1484":{"id":"q1484","difficulty":0.8872935764,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Barbados","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Swaziland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tonga"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vanuatu"}]},"q1485":{"id":"q1485","difficulty":0.8872951179,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iraq","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mali"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tanzania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkey"}]},"q1486":{"id":"q1486","difficulty":0.8888220926,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Antigua and Barbuda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nauru"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"}]},"q1487":{"id":"q1487","difficulty":0.8898198571,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vietnam","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guatemala"}]},"q1488":{"id":"q1488","difficulty":0.8904162575,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vanuatu","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Malta"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"},{"id":"a4","text":"Samoa"}]},"q1489":{"id":"q1489","difficulty":0.8922109615,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Somalia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Romania"}]},"q1490":{"id":"q1490","difficulty":0.8936109309,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Liechtenstein"},{"id":"a3","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q1491":{"id":"q1491","difficulty":0.8952230028,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Togo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mauritius"},{"id":"a4","text":"Trinidad and Tobago"}]},"q1492":{"id":"q1492","difficulty":0.9018518519,"question":"Which of these rivers is the longest?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paraná River","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"White Nile"},{"id":"a3","text":"Niger River"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yenisei River"}]},"q1493":{"id":"q1493","difficulty":0.9047811514,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Benin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a3","text":"Moldova"},{"id":"a4","text":"Netherlands"}]},"q1494":{"id":"q1494","difficulty":0.2294217305,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Botswana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangalla"},{"id":"a3","text":"Coalition States"},{"id":"a4","text":"Genovia"}]},"q1495":{"id":"q1495","difficulty":0.9054250992,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bulgaria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Niger"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sri Lanka"}]},"q1496":{"id":"q1496","difficulty":0.9102386062,"question":"Which of these capital cities has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Riyadh","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Addis Ababa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Berlin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Buenos Aires"}]},"q1497":{"id":"q1497","difficulty":0.9171673649,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Togo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Namibia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uruguay"}]},"q1498":{"id":"q1498","difficulty":0.9190237704,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Timor-Leste","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malta"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mauritius"}]},"q1499":{"id":"q1499","difficulty":0.9375,"question":"Which of these rivers is the longest?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Irtysh River","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Indus River"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madeira River"},{"id":"a4","text":"Purus River"}]},"q1500":{"id":"q1500","difficulty":0.9379769097,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"San Marino"}]},"q1501":{"id":"q1501","difficulty":0.2295526341,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tajikistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brobdingnag"},{"id":"a3","text":"Creta"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gondor"}]},"q1502":{"id":"q1502","difficulty":0.2296237642,"question":"Kathmandu is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nepal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Indonesia"}]},"q1503":{"id":"q1503","difficulty":0.2303953952,"question":"In which mountain range are the world's ten highest mountains?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Himalayas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Alps"},{"id":"a3","text":"Andes"},{"id":"a4","text":"Appalachians"}]},"q1504":{"id":"q1504","difficulty":0.2305939944,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Borduria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Glubbdubdrib"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kashfar"}]},"q1505":{"id":"q1505","difficulty":0.230855804,"question":"Which of these colors appears in the flag of France?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Red","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Black"},{"id":"a3","text":"Green"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yellow"}]},"q1506":{"id":"q1506","difficulty":0.2314527108,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Niger","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Borostyria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Eriador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kolechia"}]},"q1507":{"id":"q1507","difficulty":0.232793438,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Oman","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cobrastan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Eagleland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Genosha"}]},"q1508":{"id":"q1508","difficulty":0.2329492782,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ghana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sudan"}]},"q1509":{"id":"q1509","difficulty":0.2355081304,"question":"Canada contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Toronto","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San Pedro Sula"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guatemala City"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ecatepec de Morelos"}]},"q1510":{"id":"q1510","difficulty":0.2356568804,"question":"What is the capital of Russia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Moscow","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dublin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Petersburg"}]},"q1511":{"id":"q1511","difficulty":0.2358828697,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lithuania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aurelia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Carpathia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equestria"}]},"q1512":{"id":"q1512","difficulty":0.2378257827,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Switzerland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"}]},"q1513":{"id":"q1513","difficulty":0.2385529359,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cuba","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iraq"}]},"q1514":{"id":"q1514","difficulty":0.2391821972,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Denmark","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a3","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gabon"}]},"q1515":{"id":"q1515","difficulty":0.2397714922,"question":"What nickname is given to the Santa Clara valley in California?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Silicon Valley","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Gold Valley"},{"id":"a3","text":"Silver valley"},{"id":"a4","text":"Steel Valley"}]},"q1516":{"id":"q1516","difficulty":0.2399203175,"question":"In what country is the largest part of the Amazon rainforest located?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brazil","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a4","text":"Colombia"}]},"q1517":{"id":"q1517","difficulty":0.2405465432,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Angola","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Axphain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gondour"},{"id":"a4","text":"Grand Fenwick"}]},"q1518":{"id":"q1518","difficulty":0.2415398384,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Trinidad and Tobago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Elbonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Eriador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiore"}]},"q1519":{"id":"q1519","difficulty":0.2428779604,"question":"Japan contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nagoya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bishkek"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sulaymaniyah Governorate"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jakarta"}]},"q1520":{"id":"q1520","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Washington","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"[NULL]","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"United States of America"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Canada"}]},"q1521":{"id":"q1521","difficulty":0.2433941132,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Kingdom","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cape Verde"}]},"q1522":{"id":"q1522","difficulty":0.2441798059,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Namibia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brobdingnag"},{"id":"a3","text":"Carpathia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gondor"}]},"q1523":{"id":"q1523","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Cologne","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Hamburg are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a4","text":"Albania"}]},"q1524":{"id":"q1524","difficulty":0.2444443711,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Fiji","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Creta"},{"id":"a3","text":"Drachma"},{"id":"a4","text":"Freedonia"}]},"q1525":{"id":"q1525","difficulty":null,"question":"The Colosseum can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Rome","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" Italy\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Hartford"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1526":{"id":"q1526","difficulty":0.2451224616,"question":"In which country would you find Universal Orlando?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Haiti"}]},"q1527":{"id":"q1527","difficulty":0.245477178,"question":"United Kingdom contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"London","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dublin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hamburg"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moscow"}]},"q1528":{"id":"q1528","difficulty":0.2463079967,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Russia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madagascar"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zambia"}]},"q1529":{"id":"q1529","difficulty":0.2473528478,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"New Zealand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiribati"}]},"q1530":{"id":"q1530","difficulty":0.07766751269,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nigeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Emmeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estoccia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Glovania"}]},"q1531":{"id":"q1531","difficulty":0.2473678648,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Estonia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arstotzka"},{"id":"a3","text":"Buenaventura"},{"id":"a4","text":"Idris"}]},"q1532":{"id":"q1532","difficulty":0.2482715468,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mozambique","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mongolia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q1533":{"id":"q1533","difficulty":0.2490015155,"question":"Vienna is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Austria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Croatia"}]},"q1534":{"id":"q1534","difficulty":0.2502904646,"question":"Germany contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hamburg","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barcelona"},{"id":"a3","text":"Oslo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Stockholm"}]},"q1535":{"id":"q1535","difficulty":0.2509478487,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Honduras","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Babar's Kingdom"},{"id":"a3","text":"Caledonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Holy Britannian Empire"}]},"q1536":{"id":"q1536","difficulty":0.2510259913,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brazil","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a4","text":"Colombia"}]},"q1537":{"id":"q1537","difficulty":0.2513108122,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aerugo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Babar's Kingdom"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bolumbia"}]},"q1538":{"id":"q1538","difficulty":0.2520348108,"question":"Athens is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Greece","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belarus"}]},"q1539":{"id":"q1539","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Turin","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Naples?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"Armenia"}]},"q1540":{"id":"q1540","difficulty":0.07791353778,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brazil","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolumbia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Halla"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malicuria"}]},"q1541":{"id":"q1541","difficulty":0.2531180796,"question":"Havana is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cuba","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guatemala"}]},"q1542":{"id":"q1542","difficulty":0.2533790703,"question":"Japan does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Abdanan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Osaka"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sapporo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nagoya"}]},"q1543":{"id":"q1543","difficulty":0.2538864085,"question":"Australia contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Melbourne","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Auckland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Wellington"},{"id":"a4","text":"Funafuti"}]},"q1544":{"id":"q1544","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Chongqing","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Tianjin are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"Afghanistan"}]},"q1545":{"id":"q1545","difficulty":0.2556503235,"question":"What is the capital of New Zealand?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Wellington","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"South Tarawa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Auckland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ngerulmud"}]},"q1546":{"id":"q1546","difficulty":0.2556503235,"question":"Which country's capital is Wellington?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"New Zealand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Marshall Islands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nauru"}]},"q1547":{"id":"q1547","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities São Paulo","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Rio de Janeiro?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bolivia"}]},"q1548":{"id":"q1548","difficulty":0.2560359378,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brobdingnag"},{"id":"a3","text":"Corto Maltese"},{"id":"a4","text":"Glovania"}]},"q1549":{"id":"q1549","difficulty":0.2564020316,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vatican City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Caledonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Coalition States"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kangan"}]},"q1550":{"id":"q1550","difficulty":0.07879187817,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Indonesia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Estovakia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hyrule"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kangan"}]},"q1551":{"id":"q1551","difficulty":0.2565074264,"question":"What is the capital of Nepal?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kathmandu","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Limbuwan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Janakpur Zone"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tokyo"}]},"q1552":{"id":"q1552","difficulty":0.2565973564,"question":"In which country would you find Zoo Atlanta?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"El Salvador"}]},"q1553":{"id":"q1553","difficulty":0.2572928185,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Germany","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q1554":{"id":"q1554","difficulty":0.2583103982,"question":"What is the capital of North Korea?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Pyongyang","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jakarta"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kabul"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kathmandu"}]},"q1555":{"id":"q1555","difficulty":0.2587209146,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Germany?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vilnius","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Berlin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cologne"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hamburg"}]},"q1556":{"id":"q1556","difficulty":0.2588567363,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mexico","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Thailand"},{"id":"a3","text":"Uganda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uzbekistan"}]},"q1557":{"id":"q1557","difficulty":0.2591934439,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cape Verde","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Denmark"}]},"q1558":{"id":"q1558","difficulty":0.2593728259,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cameroon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangalla"},{"id":"a3","text":"Calbia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Khemed"}]},"q1559":{"id":"q1559","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Which of the following is not in Washington","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"[NULL]","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Coney Island"},{"id":"a3","text":"The Washington Monument"},{"id":"a4","text":"Thomas Jefferson Memorial"}]},"q1560":{"id":"q1560","difficulty":0.0792005447,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Norway","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cobra Island"},{"id":"a3","text":"Holy Britannian Empire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Impor"}]},"q1561":{"id":"q1561","difficulty":0.2614160876,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Russia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q1562":{"id":"q1562","difficulty":0.2619929429,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yemen","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kazakhstan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mexico"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mongolia"}]},"q1563":{"id":"q1563","difficulty":0.2625642051,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fiji"}]},"q1564":{"id":"q1564","difficulty":0.2629901859,"question":"Which of the following is not in New York City?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"The Art Institute of Chicago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Coney Island"},{"id":"a3","text":"The Flatiron Building"},{"id":"a4","text":"The Cloisters"}]},"q1565":{"id":"q1565","difficulty":0.2631547723,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malawi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aurelia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolumbia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Buenaventura"}]},"q1566":{"id":"q1566","difficulty":0.2633302244,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Indonesia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brunei"}]},"q1567":{"id":"q1567","difficulty":0.2652119597,"question":"Manila is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Philippines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brunei"}]},"q1568":{"id":"q1568","difficulty":0.2653711929,"question":"Which country's capital is Dublin?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Republic of Ireland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a3","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q1569":{"id":"q1569","difficulty":0.2654120439,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ukraine","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mauritius"}]},"q1570":{"id":"q1570","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Statue of Liberty?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"New York City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Calgary"},{"id":"a4","text":" Canada\""}]},"q1571":{"id":"q1571","difficulty":0.2658533042,"question":"What is the capital of Egypt?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cairo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Giza"},{"id":"a3","text":"Alexandria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sharm El Sheikh"}]},"q1572":{"id":"q1572","difficulty":0.2658533042,"question":"Cairo is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Egypt","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chad"}]},"q1573":{"id":"q1573","difficulty":0.2663198923,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkmenistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Drachma"},{"id":"a3","text":"Khemed"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kolechia"}]},"q1574":{"id":"q1574","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Puebla","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Tijuana?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mexico"},{"id":"a4","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"}]},"q1575":{"id":"q1575","difficulty":0.2683314887,"question":"In which country would you find San Diego Zoo Safari Park?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Haiti"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jamaica"}]},"q1576":{"id":"q1576","difficulty":0.2686778512,"question":"What is the capital of Philippines?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Manila","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bohol"},{"id":"a3","text":"Quezon City"},{"id":"a4","text":"Damascus"}]},"q1577":{"id":"q1577","difficulty":0.2690510266,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Norway","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Germany"}]},"q1578":{"id":"q1578","difficulty":0.2716275552,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Africa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burundi"}]},"q1579":{"id":"q1579","difficulty":null,"question":"The Hollywood Walk of Fame can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Los Angeles","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Magelang Regency"},{"id":"a4","text":" Indonesia\""}]},"q1580":{"id":"q1580","difficulty":0.2730136368,"question":"The capital of Argentina is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Buenos Aires","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Quito"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brasília"},{"id":"a4","text":"Córdoba"}]},"q1581":{"id":"q1581","difficulty":0.2731862065,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Sweden?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Stockholm","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barcelona"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dublin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hamburg"}]},"q1582":{"id":"q1582","difficulty":0.2732311487,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahamas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guinea-Bissau"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Korea"}]},"q1583":{"id":"q1583","difficulty":0.2740828474,"question":"Where does Flamenco dancing come from?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Spain","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Greece"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ireland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Italy"}]},"q1584":{"id":"q1584","difficulty":0.2741709188,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chile","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mongolia"}]},"q1585":{"id":"q1585","difficulty":0.2753266774,"question":"In which country would you find Melbourne City Centre?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Australia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kiribati"},{"id":"a4","text":"New Zealand"}]},"q1586":{"id":"q1586","difficulty":0.2756766282,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Egypt","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"}]},"q1587":{"id":"q1587","difficulty":0.2757180717,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Philippines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iran"}]},"q1588":{"id":"q1588","difficulty":0.2761355106,"question":"United Arab Emirates does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sulaymaniyah Governorate","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dubai"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sharjah"},{"id":"a4","text":"Abu Dhabi"}]},"q1589":{"id":"q1589","difficulty":0.2771581041,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cobrastan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Creta"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kashfar"}]},"q1590":{"id":"q1590","difficulty":0.2783063371,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guyana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Eagleland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Glubbdubdrib"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gondor"}]},"q1591":{"id":"q1591","difficulty":0.2797417747,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"France","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kuwait"}]},"q1592":{"id":"q1592","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Paris","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Marseille?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Andorra"}]},"q1593":{"id":"q1593","difficulty":0.2802469699,"question":"What is the capital of Finland?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Helsinki","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bratislava"},{"id":"a3","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moscow"}]},"q1594":{"id":"q1594","difficulty":0.2806596603,"question":"By which name is Bombay now known?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mumbai","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangalore"},{"id":"a3","text":"New Delhi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Pune"}]},"q1595":{"id":"q1595","difficulty":0.2821340686,"question":"What is the capital of Tunisia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tunis","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Monrovia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Moroni"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yaoundé"}]},"q1596":{"id":"q1596","difficulty":0.2827237968,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vietnam","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q1597":{"id":"q1597","difficulty":0.08334341649,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"China","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Colombia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Africa"}]},"q1598":{"id":"q1598","difficulty":0.2840024942,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tunisia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Atlantis"},{"id":"a3","text":"Elbonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malicuria"}]},"q1599":{"id":"q1599","difficulty":0.2841186263,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Luxembourg","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cambodia"}]},"q1600":{"id":"q1600","difficulty":0.2841354773,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Laos","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bialya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cagliostro"},{"id":"a4","text":"Creta"}]},"q1601":{"id":"q1601","difficulty":0.2843925685,"question":"Stockholm is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sweden","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q1602":{"id":"q1602","difficulty":0.2843925685,"question":"The capital of Sweden is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Stockholm","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Berlin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Helsinki"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moscow"}]},"q1603":{"id":"q1603","difficulty":0.2845729197,"question":"Which of the following is not in San Francisco?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"The Liberty Bell","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San Francisco Museum of Modern Art"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chinatown"},{"id":"a4","text":"California Academy of Sciences"}]},"q1604":{"id":"q1604","difficulty":0.2846340701,"question":"Which country's capital is Bern?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Switzerland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"}]},"q1605":{"id":"q1605","difficulty":0.2847808253,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Latvia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chernarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Coalition States"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cobra Island"}]},"q1606":{"id":"q1606","difficulty":0.08403678667,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Denmark","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Borduria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Drachma"},{"id":"a4","text":"Farfelu"}]},"q1607":{"id":"q1607","difficulty":null,"question":"The Space Needle can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Seattle","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Atlanta"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1608":{"id":"q1608","difficulty":0.2865314483,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malaysia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a3","text":"Somalia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ukraine"}]},"q1609":{"id":"q1609","difficulty":0.286964445,"question":"What is the capital of Jamaica?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kingston","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San José"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guatemala City"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kingstown"}]},"q1610":{"id":"q1610","difficulty":0.2885117016,"question":"France contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Poitou","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dnipropetrovsk"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madrid"},{"id":"a4","text":"Oslo"}]},"q1611":{"id":"q1611","difficulty":0.2888988039,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mexico","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominica"}]},"q1612":{"id":"q1612","difficulty":0.2895175599,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mozambique","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"Philippines"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q1613":{"id":"q1613","difficulty":0.2895939086,"question":"Algiers is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Algeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eritrea"}]},"q1614":{"id":"q1614","difficulty":0.2903591355,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Montenegro","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Deltora"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Kundu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Holy Britannian Empire"}]},"q1615":{"id":"q1615","difficulty":0.2907477916,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahrain","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aurelia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiore"},{"id":"a4","text":"Grenyarnia"}]},"q1616":{"id":"q1616","difficulty":0.08578529558,"question":"The Coliseum is in which European city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rome","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Reykjavik"},{"id":"a3","text":"Riga"},{"id":"a4","text":"Roscoe"}]},"q1617":{"id":"q1617","difficulty":0.2913930931,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Brazil?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Santa Cruz de la Sierra","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brasília"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fortaleza"},{"id":"a4","text":"Rio de Janeiro"}]},"q1618":{"id":"q1618","difficulty":0.2935941284,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brazil","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Colombia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saudi Arabia"}]},"q1619":{"id":"q1619","difficulty":0.2943580482,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Azerbaijan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Borduria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Borginia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Buranda"}]},"q1620":{"id":"q1620","difficulty":0.2947709219,"question":"Ankara is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkey","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estonia"}]},"q1621":{"id":"q1621","difficulty":0.2950169451,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Brazil?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Fortaleza","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cali"},{"id":"a3","text":"Arequipa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Medellín"}]},"q1622":{"id":"q1622","difficulty":0.2956592148,"question":"Which of these are you most likely to see on the canals of Venice?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gondolas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jet-skis"},{"id":"a3","text":"Junks"},{"id":"a4","text":"Punts"}]},"q1623":{"id":"q1623","difficulty":0.296000153,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Samoa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Netherlands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Solomon Islands"}]},"q1624":{"id":"q1624","difficulty":0.29658772,"question":"Turkey does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Berlin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bursa"},{"id":"a3","text":"İzmir"},{"id":"a4","text":"Istanbul"}]},"q1625":{"id":"q1625","difficulty":0.2969471572,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"China","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kyrgyzstan"}]},"q1626":{"id":"q1626","difficulty":0.08624066937,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"China","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Deltora"},{"id":"a3","text":"Farfelu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Illéa"}]},"q1627":{"id":"q1627","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Museum of Modern Art?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"New York City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Chicago"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1628":{"id":"q1628","difficulty":0.2977347676,"question":"Which country's capital is Kingston?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jamaica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Barbados"}]},"q1629":{"id":"q1629","difficulty":0.2977786532,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Kingdom","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lithuania"}]},"q1630":{"id":"q1630","difficulty":0.2996896584,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Australia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominican Republic"}]},"q1631":{"id":"q1631","difficulty":0.3009972983,"question":"Tunis is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tunisia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mozambique"}]},"q1632":{"id":"q1632","difficulty":0.3010547749,"question":"Amsterdam is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Netherlands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q1633":{"id":"q1633","difficulty":0.3010547749,"question":"The capital of Netherlands is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Amsterdam","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kiev"},{"id":"a4","text":"Madrid"}]},"q1634":{"id":"q1634","difficulty":0.08873090956,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Romania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Estoccia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Glovania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Illéa"}]},"q1635":{"id":"q1635","difficulty":0.3019003787,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nepal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tanzania"}]},"q1636":{"id":"q1636","difficulty":0.3020283868,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mexico"}]},"q1637":{"id":"q1637","difficulty":0.3020311619,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Borduria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brobdingnag"},{"id":"a4","text":"Earthsea"}]},"q1638":{"id":"q1638","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find California Academy of Sciences?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"San Francisco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Cork"},{"id":"a4","text":" Republic of Ireland\""}]},"q1639":{"id":"q1639","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The British Museum?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"London","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" UK\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Ascot"},{"id":"a4","text":" UK\""}]},"q1640":{"id":"q1640","difficulty":0.3032005076,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Central African Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Earthsea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ixania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kangan"}]},"q1641":{"id":"q1641","difficulty":0.3035272501,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovakia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bangladesh"}]},"q1642":{"id":"q1642","difficulty":0.3038932943,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Philippines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estonia"}]},"q1643":{"id":"q1643","difficulty":0.08985535451,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mexico","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aerugo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brobdingnag"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eriador"}]},"q1644":{"id":"q1644","difficulty":0.3042626151,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mali","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Atlantis"},{"id":"a3","text":"Babar's Kingdom"},{"id":"a4","text":"Blefuscu"}]},"q1645":{"id":"q1645","difficulty":0.3050682461,"question":"China contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tianjin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bishkek"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chittagong"},{"id":"a4","text":"Manama"}]},"q1646":{"id":"q1646","difficulty":0.3051665659,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rwanda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Blefuscu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chernarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equatorial Kundu"}]},"q1647":{"id":"q1647","difficulty":0.305660603,"question":"What is the capital of Chile?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Santiago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Quito"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a4","text":"Buenos Aires"}]},"q1648":{"id":"q1648","difficulty":0.305660603,"question":"Which country's capital is Santiago?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chile","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q1649":{"id":"q1649","difficulty":0.3057217455,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Niger","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q1650":{"id":"q1650","difficulty":0.3063083539,"question":"What is the capital of Norway?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Oslo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Berlin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bratislava"},{"id":"a4","text":"Podgorica"}]},"q1651":{"id":"q1651","difficulty":0.3063083539,"question":"Which country's capital is Oslo?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Norway","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q1652":{"id":"q1652","difficulty":0.3065571702,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chile","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Costa Rica"}]},"q1653":{"id":"q1653","difficulty":0.09016738113,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Australia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cagliostro"},{"id":"a3","text":"Deltora"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fe'ausi"}]},"q1654":{"id":"q1654","difficulty":0.3068993159,"question":"Colombo is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sri Lanka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"Japan"}]},"q1655":{"id":"q1655","difficulty":0.3073587928,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Myanmar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Niger"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sudan"}]},"q1656":{"id":"q1656","difficulty":0.3077186027,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Japan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sri Lanka"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkey"}]},"q1657":{"id":"q1657","difficulty":0.3088444288,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cape Verde","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Calbia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Creta"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fe'ausi"}]},"q1658":{"id":"q1658","difficulty":0.3089379674,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liechtenstein","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aerugo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Grenyarnia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mendorra"}]},"q1659":{"id":"q1659","difficulty":0.3095623097,"question":"Buenos Aires is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Argentina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q1660":{"id":"q1660","difficulty":0.3099593969,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Armenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"},{"id":"a3","text":"Singapore"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vanuatu"}]},"q1661":{"id":"q1661","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities New York City","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Philadelphia?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"United States of America"},{"id":"a4","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"}]},"q1662":{"id":"q1662","difficulty":0.3131359301,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Romania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"}]},"q1663":{"id":"q1663","difficulty":0.3150812646,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Turkey?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"İzmir","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Copenhagen"},{"id":"a3","text":"Helsinki"},{"id":"a4","text":"London"}]},"q1664":{"id":"q1664","difficulty":0.3166495519,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Russia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Morocco"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sudan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q1665":{"id":"q1665","difficulty":0.3169996427,"question":"What is the capital of Republic of Ireland?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dublin","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Podgorica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lisbon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Monaco"}]},"q1666":{"id":"q1666","difficulty":0.317213391,"question":"Hyatt Regency Atlanta can be found in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Grenada"}]},"q1667":{"id":"q1667","difficulty":0.3180620812,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Lucia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Borostyria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Deltora"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equestria"}]},"q1668":{"id":"q1668","difficulty":0.3183191418,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Malaysia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Beijing","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Johor Bahru"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kuala Lumpur"},{"id":"a4","text":"Subang Jaya"}]},"q1669":{"id":"q1669","difficulty":0.09055337944,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cuba","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antegria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Arendelle"},{"id":"a4","text":"Borostyria"}]},"q1670":{"id":"q1670","difficulty":0.3183397796,"question":"Dominican Republic contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Santo Domingo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chicago"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ciudad del Carmen"},{"id":"a4","text":"Calgary"}]},"q1671":{"id":"q1671","difficulty":0.3184582967,"question":"What is the capital of Czech Republic?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Prague","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jihozápad"},{"id":"a3","text":"Severovýchod"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moscow"}]},"q1672":{"id":"q1672","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Bursa","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Ankara are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Turkey"},{"id":"a4","text":"Armenia"}]},"q1673":{"id":"q1673","difficulty":0.3209607512,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Deltora"},{"id":"a3","text":"Emmeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Freedonia"}]},"q1674":{"id":"q1674","difficulty":0.3213977394,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sri Lanka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a4","text":"China"}]},"q1675":{"id":"q1675","difficulty":0.3215247755,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Czech Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belize"}]},"q1676":{"id":"q1676","difficulty":0.3217133306,"question":"Warsaw is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Poland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"France"},{"id":"a3","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q1677":{"id":"q1677","difficulty":0.0912643846,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"New Zealand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Eriador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gondor"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hyrule"}]},"q1678":{"id":"q1678","difficulty":0.3217133306,"question":"The capital of Poland is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Warsaw","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Madrid"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tallinn"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bucharest"}]},"q1679":{"id":"q1679","difficulty":0.322372008,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Madagascar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea"}]},"q1680":{"id":"q1680","difficulty":0.3225249086,"question":"Poland contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Łódź","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"İzmir"},{"id":"a3","text":"London"},{"id":"a4","text":"Monaco"}]},"q1681":{"id":"q1681","difficulty":0.3229012972,"question":"Prague is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Czech Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q1682":{"id":"q1682","difficulty":0.3231410301,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kyrgyzstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brobdingnag"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Kundu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gondour"}]},"q1683":{"id":"q1683","difficulty":0.3234534199,"question":"Which of these Mountains can be found in Hawaii?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mouna Loa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mount Elbert"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mount Everest"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mount Uno"}]},"q1684":{"id":"q1684","difficulty":0.324141265,"question":"Which of the following is not in Chicago?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Shoreline Amphitheatre","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Merchandise Mart"},{"id":"a3","text":"The Art Institute of Chicago"},{"id":"a4","text":"Shedd Aquarium"}]},"q1685":{"id":"q1685","difficulty":0.3241492147,"question":"The Amazon River does NOT run through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Argentina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Colombia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Peru"}]},"q1686":{"id":"q1686","difficulty":0.3247427072,"question":"The capital of Indonesia is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jakarta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Surabaya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bandung"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kuala Lumpur"}]},"q1687":{"id":"q1687","difficulty":0.09243190675,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Afghanistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arendelle"},{"id":"a3","text":"Blefuscu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Deltora"}]},"q1688":{"id":"q1688","difficulty":null,"question":"Alcatraz Island can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"San Francisco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Boston"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1689":{"id":"q1689","difficulty":0.3262083175,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belarus","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangalla"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chernarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cobrastan"}]},"q1690":{"id":"q1690","difficulty":0.3263116882,"question":"Which country's capital is Tehran?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iran","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a3","text":"Israel"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jordan"}]},"q1691":{"id":"q1691","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Mount Vesuvius?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Pompeii","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" Italy\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Beijing"},{"id":"a4","text":" China\""}]},"q1692":{"id":"q1692","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Limbuwan","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Janakpur Zone are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nepal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Afghanistan"}]},"q1693":{"id":"q1693","difficulty":0.3303781722,"question":"Dhaka is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bangladesh","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"Israel"}]},"q1694":{"id":"q1694","difficulty":0.3304015759,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Romania?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Warsaw","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Sud - Muntenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"București - Ilfov"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bucharest"}]},"q1695":{"id":"q1695","difficulty":0.09382479469,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Philippines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangalla"},{"id":"a3","text":"Freedonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Graznavia"}]},"q1696":{"id":"q1696","difficulty":0.3305085809,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bulgaria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Moldova"},{"id":"a4","text":"Swaziland"}]},"q1697":{"id":"q1697","difficulty":0.3311378887,"question":"Which country's capital is Pyongyang?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"North Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iraq"}]},"q1698":{"id":"q1698","difficulty":0.3313355096,"question":"Which of the following is not in Los Angeles?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Water Tower Place","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Hollywood Bowl"},{"id":"a3","text":"Walt Disney Concert Hall"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hollywood Boulevard"}]},"q1699":{"id":"q1699","difficulty":0.3320025175,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mozambique","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Buranda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Drachma"},{"id":"a4","text":"Markovia"}]},"q1700":{"id":"q1700","difficulty":0.3325837969,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Côte d’Ivoire","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"Spain"}]},"q1701":{"id":"q1701","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Moscow","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Nizhny Novgorod are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Russia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q1702":{"id":"q1702","difficulty":0.333035942,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nicaragua","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Coalition States"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiore"},{"id":"a4","text":"Grenyarnia"}]},"q1703":{"id":"q1703","difficulty":0.3333453438,"question":"What is the Spanish name for the Falkland islands?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Islas Malvinas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Las Vegas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Los Angeles"},{"id":"a4","text":"Los Zetas"}]},"q1704":{"id":"q1704","difficulty":0.09467972334,"question":"The Great Sphinx of Giza can be found in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Egypt","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea"}]},"q1705":{"id":"q1705","difficulty":0.3349326319,"question":"Which of the following is not in Atlanta?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chinatown","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"The Georgia Dome"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hyatt Regency Atlanta"},{"id":"a4","text":"Zoo Atlanta"}]},"q1706":{"id":"q1706","difficulty":0.3358985278,"question":"Which country's capital is Helsinki?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Finland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"}]},"q1707":{"id":"q1707","difficulty":0.3360312157,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Singapore","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Suriname"},{"id":"a4","text":"Timor-Leste"}]},"q1708":{"id":"q1708","difficulty":0.3366711211,"question":"The capital of Iceland is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Reykjavik","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Lisbon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Paris"},{"id":"a4","text":"Skopje"}]},"q1709":{"id":"q1709","difficulty":0.3367121045,"question":"Which of these American cities lies on the shores of Lake Michigan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chicago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Los Angeles"},{"id":"a3","text":"New York"},{"id":"a4","text":"San Francisco"}]},"q1710":{"id":"q1710","difficulty":0.3368868417,"question":"Philippines contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Caloocan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Karachi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mecca"},{"id":"a4","text":"Pyongyang"}]},"q1711":{"id":"q1711","difficulty":0.3373101626,"question":"Burgundy is a famous region in France for producing what?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Wine","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Beer"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cheese"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ham"}]},"q1712":{"id":"q1712","difficulty":0.3374584775,"question":"Netherlands contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Amsterdam","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Podgorica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Munich"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jihozápad"}]},"q1713":{"id":"q1713","difficulty":0.04704631566,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Australia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kiribati"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nauru"}]},"q1714":{"id":"q1714","difficulty":null,"question":"The White House can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Washington","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" D.C."},{"id":"a3","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a4","text":"\"Giza"}]},"q1715":{"id":"q1715","difficulty":0.3375918056,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Thailand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"}]},"q1716":{"id":"q1716","difficulty":0.3379321643,"question":"Which country's capital is Pretoria?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Africa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eritrea"}]},"q1717":{"id":"q1717","difficulty":0.3387486446,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mongolia"}]},"q1718":{"id":"q1718","difficulty":0.3391045213,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Poland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Sierra Leone"},{"id":"a4","text":"Suriname"}]},"q1719":{"id":"q1719","difficulty":0.3396191111,"question":"The capital of Thailand is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bangkok","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Beijing"},{"id":"a3","text":"Damascus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kabul"}]},"q1720":{"id":"q1720","difficulty":0.3396191111,"question":"Which country's capital is Bangkok?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Thailand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"India"}]},"q1721":{"id":"q1721","difficulty":0.3403283232,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Austria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eritrea"}]},"q1722":{"id":"q1722","difficulty":0.09634390946,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Germany","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Borginia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Earthsea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estovakia"}]},"q1723":{"id":"q1723","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Aleppo","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Homs?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Syria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Azerbaijan"}]},"q1724":{"id":"q1724","difficulty":0.3410123967,"question":"The Nile does NOT run through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Africa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Sudan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uganda"}]},"q1725":{"id":"q1725","difficulty":0.3410123967,"question":"In which of these countries could you see the Nile?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burundi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ghana"}]},"q1726":{"id":"q1726","difficulty":0.3412027039,"question":"Egypt contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cairo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Lubumbashi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Marrakesh"},{"id":"a4","text":"Port Elizabeth"}]},"q1727":{"id":"q1727","difficulty":0.3412277142,"question":"New Zealand contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Auckland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"South Tarawa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Perth"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ngerulmud"}]},"q1728":{"id":"q1728","difficulty":0.3415878526,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Djibouti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Drachma"},{"id":"a3","text":"Eagleland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estovakia"}]},"q1729":{"id":"q1729","difficulty":0.3418082302,"question":"Panama City is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Panama","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a4","text":"Canada"}]},"q1730":{"id":"q1730","difficulty":0.3418082302,"question":"The capital of Panama is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Panama City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San José"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guatemala City"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nassau"}]},"q1731":{"id":"q1731","difficulty":0.3420867943,"question":"The capital of Iran is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tehran","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Manila"},{"id":"a3","text":"Baghdad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Isfahan"}]},"q1732":{"id":"q1732","difficulty":0.09662038735,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Switzerland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Eriador"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gondour"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kashfar"}]},"q1733":{"id":"q1733","difficulty":0.3422699726,"question":"Which of the following cities is in South Korea?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Seoul","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Baghdad"},{"id":"a3","text":"Danang"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jerusalem"}]},"q1734":{"id":"q1734","difficulty":0.3423556934,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iceland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q1735":{"id":"q1735","difficulty":0.3425624518,"question":"\"What large Russian port city's name translates to \"\"Rule the East\"\"?\"","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vladivostok's","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Anadyr's"},{"id":"a3","text":"Irkutsk's"},{"id":"a4","text":"Magadan's"}]},"q1736":{"id":"q1736","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Arequipa","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Lima?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Peru"},{"id":"a4","text":"Argentina"}]},"q1737":{"id":"q1737","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Buenos Aires","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Rosario are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bolivia"}]},"q1738":{"id":"q1738","difficulty":0.342914258,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Senegal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cobra Island"},{"id":"a3","text":"Freedonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ixania"}]},"q1739":{"id":"q1739","difficulty":0.09698524857,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Babar's Kingdom"},{"id":"a3","text":"Creta"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moldovakia"}]},"q1740":{"id":"q1740","difficulty":0.3454934458,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uruguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Slovenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tonga"}]},"q1741":{"id":"q1741","difficulty":0.3455972813,"question":"The capital of Malaysia is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kuala Lumpur","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Johor Bahru"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jakarta"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kabul"}]},"q1742":{"id":"q1742","difficulty":0.3455972813,"question":"Kuala Lumpur is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malaysia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Israel"},{"id":"a4","text":"Japan"}]},"q1743":{"id":"q1743","difficulty":0.3458753369,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Turkmenistan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ashgabat","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dubai"},{"id":"a3","text":"Surabaya"},{"id":"a4","text":"Isfahan"}]},"q1744":{"id":"q1744","difficulty":0.3461555456,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Kingdom","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Malaysia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Netherlands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Uzbekistan"}]},"q1745":{"id":"q1745","difficulty":0.3469491384,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Moldova","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antegria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Borginia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eagleland"}]},"q1746":{"id":"q1746","difficulty":0.3479061147,"question":"Argentina contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Buenos Aires","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brasília"},{"id":"a3","text":"Valencia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Barquisimeto"}]},"q1747":{"id":"q1747","difficulty":0.09719567302,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Chile","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Amestris"},{"id":"a3","text":"Coalition States"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cobrastan"}]},"q1748":{"id":"q1748","difficulty":0.3482158665,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Egypt","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madagascar"},{"id":"a4","text":"Papua New Guinea"}]},"q1749":{"id":"q1749","difficulty":0.3494320647,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Madagascar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Canada"}]},"q1750":{"id":"q1750","difficulty":0.3496055394,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hungary","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea-Bissau"}]},"q1751":{"id":"q1751","difficulty":0.3496319444,"question":"In which city are the football stadiums of Old Trafford and the Etihad Stadium?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Manchester","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bath"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambridge"},{"id":"a4","text":"Oxford"}]},"q1752":{"id":"q1752","difficulty":0.3496723456,"question":"Singapore is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Singapore","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brunei"}]},"q1753":{"id":"q1753","difficulty":0.3496723456,"question":"What is the capital of Singapore?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Singapore","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Beijing"},{"id":"a3","text":"Baghdad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jakarta"}]},"q1754":{"id":"q1754","difficulty":0.3497456106,"question":"What is the capital of El Salvador?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"San Salvador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San José"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kingstown"},{"id":"a4","text":"Havana"}]},"q1755":{"id":"q1755","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Manila","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Davao?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Philippines"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bhutan"}]},"q1756":{"id":"q1756","difficulty":0.09735265158,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Thailand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Amestris"},{"id":"a3","text":"Antegria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Borduria"}]},"q1757":{"id":"q1757","difficulty":0.350139861,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Grenada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bialya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Coalition States"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estovakia"}]},"q1758":{"id":"q1758","difficulty":0.3506483745,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guatemala","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estonia"}]},"q1759":{"id":"q1759","difficulty":0.3507497267,"question":"Egypt does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Addis Ababa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Giza"},{"id":"a3","text":"Alexandria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sharm El Sheikh"}]},"q1760":{"id":"q1760","difficulty":0.3510050686,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Nepal?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Can Tho","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Limbuwan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kathmandu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Janakpur Zone"}]},"q1761":{"id":"q1761","difficulty":0.3523473802,"question":"Which state contains the top 10 tallest mountains in the United States?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Alaska","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Alabama"},{"id":"a3","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Idaho"}]},"q1762":{"id":"q1762","difficulty":0.3524333214,"question":"The capital of Switzerland is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bern","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tallinn"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yerevan"}]},"q1763":{"id":"q1763","difficulty":0.3527158658,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Antigua and Barbuda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Elbonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estovakia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Latveria"}]},"q1764":{"id":"q1764","difficulty":0.3537762712,"question":"What is the capital city of the Australian state of Western Australia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Perth","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albany"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bunbury"},{"id":"a4","text":"Esperance"}]},"q1765":{"id":"q1765","difficulty":0.0974927952,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Kingdom","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Holy Britannian Empire"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mendorra"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mypos"}]},"q1766":{"id":"q1766","difficulty":0.3538957482,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vatican City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"},{"id":"a3","text":"Samoa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tuvalu"}]},"q1767":{"id":"q1767","difficulty":0.3539201625,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Guatemala?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guatemala City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Puebla"},{"id":"a3","text":"San José"},{"id":"a4","text":"Calgary"}]},"q1768":{"id":"q1768","difficulty":0.3541984619,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"France","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q1769":{"id":"q1769","difficulty":0.3548958846,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Ukraine?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kiev","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Oslo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Rome"},{"id":"a4","text":"Riga"}]},"q1770":{"id":"q1770","difficulty":0.3551483421,"question":"In which of these countries could you see the Mississippi River?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Haiti"}]},"q1771":{"id":"q1771","difficulty":0.3552799149,"question":"North Korea contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Pyongyang","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jakarta"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kathmandu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Janakpur Zone"}]},"q1772":{"id":"q1772","difficulty":0.3561065577,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in France?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Severovýchod","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Paris"},{"id":"a3","text":"Poitou"},{"id":"a4","text":"Marseille"}]},"q1773":{"id":"q1773","difficulty":0.09790020505,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iceland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Archenland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Arendelle"},{"id":"a4","text":"Creta"}]},"q1774":{"id":"q1774","difficulty":0.3563637779,"question":"Which country's capital is Vatican City?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vatican City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Germany"}]},"q1775":{"id":"q1775","difficulty":0.3569176367,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Chile?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Santiago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Quito"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a4","text":"Buenos Aires"}]},"q1776":{"id":"q1776","difficulty":0.3572036071,"question":"San José is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Costa Rica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Barbados"}]},"q1777":{"id":"q1777","difficulty":0.3575840403,"question":"The capital of Denmark is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Copenhagen","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a3","text":"Oslo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Paris"}]},"q1778":{"id":"q1778","difficulty":0.3575840403,"question":"Which country's capital is Copenhagen?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Denmark","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iceland"}]},"q1779":{"id":"q1779","difficulty":0.3578503728,"question":"Italy does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Copenhagen","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Rome"},{"id":"a3","text":"Turin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Milan"}]},"q1780":{"id":"q1780","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Liberty Bell?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Philadelphia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Bloomington"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1781":{"id":"q1781","difficulty":null,"question":"Chinatown can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"San Francisco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Boston"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1782":{"id":"q1782","difficulty":0.09807652332,"question":"Russia contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Moscow","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kiev"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dnipropetrovsk"},{"id":"a4","text":"Monaco"}]},"q1783":{"id":"q1783","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Icheon","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Busan are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Korea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Israel"}]},"q1784":{"id":"q1784","difficulty":0.3586469535,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Afghanistan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kabul","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Beijing"},{"id":"a3","text":"Danang"},{"id":"a4","text":"Savar Upazila"}]},"q1785":{"id":"q1785","difficulty":0.3586934207,"question":"The capital of Jordan is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Amman","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Baku"},{"id":"a3","text":"Damascus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kathmandu"}]},"q1786":{"id":"q1786","difficulty":0.3596184899,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Indonesia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bandung","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Baku"},{"id":"a3","text":"Johor Bahru"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chittagong"}]},"q1787":{"id":"q1787","difficulty":0.3603626242,"question":"Kyoto was formerly the capital of which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Japan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"North Korea"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Korea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q1788":{"id":"q1788","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Durban","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Johannesburg are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Africa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Algeria"}]},"q1789":{"id":"q1789","difficulty":0.3619242525,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Philippines?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Almaty","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Manila"},{"id":"a3","text":"Quezon City"},{"id":"a4","text":"Caloocan"}]},"q1790":{"id":"q1790","difficulty":0.09825385315,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sweden","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bialya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Drachma"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kolechia"}]},"q1791":{"id":"q1791","difficulty":0.3620250716,"question":"Kabul is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Afghanistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iran"}]},"q1792":{"id":"q1792","difficulty":0.3626513122,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burundi"}]},"q1793":{"id":"q1793","difficulty":0.362985591,"question":"Bulgaria contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sofia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Berlin"},{"id":"a3","text":"London"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moscow"}]},"q1794":{"id":"q1794","difficulty":0.3639786653,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Germany","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Malawi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nepal"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q1795":{"id":"q1795","difficulty":0.3645994691,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liechtenstein","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Benin"}]},"q1796":{"id":"q1796","difficulty":0.04876492108,"question":"Paris is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"France","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q1797":{"id":"q1797","difficulty":0.09832663468,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bangladesh","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antegria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Calbia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Elbonia"}]},"q1798":{"id":"q1798","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Johor Bahru","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Subang Jaya are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malaysia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Azerbaijan"}]},"q1799":{"id":"q1799","difficulty":0.3651175315,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cuba","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominican Republic"}]},"q1800":{"id":"q1800","difficulty":0.3656818327,"question":"Argentina does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Quito","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Córdoba"},{"id":"a3","text":"Buenos Aires"},{"id":"a4","text":"San Martín"}]},"q1801":{"id":"q1801","difficulty":0.3659090909,"question":"In which of these countries could you see the Rio Grande?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Haiti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis"},{"id":"a4","text":"Saint Lucia"}]},"q1802":{"id":"q1802","difficulty":0.3659205463,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rwanda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gambia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mauritius"}]},"q1803":{"id":"q1803","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Surabaya","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Bekasi are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Azerbaijan"}]},"q1804":{"id":"q1804","difficulty":0.366489902,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Samoa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Earthsea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estoccia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Florin"}]},"q1805":{"id":"q1805","difficulty":0.3665465127,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brazil","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Canada"}]},"q1806":{"id":"q1806","difficulty":0.366571293,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Morocco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estonia"}]},"q1807":{"id":"q1807","difficulty":0.366678176,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mongolia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Montenegro"},{"id":"a4","text":"Samoa"}]},"q1808":{"id":"q1808","difficulty":0.09836663869,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iraq","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Creta"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fe'ausi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Genosha"}]},"q1809":{"id":"q1809","difficulty":0.3667117315,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Austria?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vienna","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bratislava"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barcelona"},{"id":"a4","text":"Munich"}]},"q1810":{"id":"q1810","difficulty":0.3685801386,"question":"Hanoi is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vietnam","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bangladesh"}]},"q1811":{"id":"q1811","difficulty":0.3685801386,"question":"What is the capital of Vietnam?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hanoi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Danang"},{"id":"a3","text":"Damascus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Can Tho"}]},"q1812":{"id":"q1812","difficulty":0.3690481718,"question":"What is the capital of United Arab Emirates?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Abu Dhabi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Beijing"},{"id":"a3","text":"Manila"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dubai"}]},"q1813":{"id":"q1813","difficulty":0.3690481718,"question":"Abu Dhabi is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Arab Emirates","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brunei"}]},"q1814":{"id":"q1814","difficulty":0.09865163191,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Finland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Estoccia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Farfelu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ixania"}]},"q1815":{"id":"q1815","difficulty":0.3696484192,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Hungary?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Budapest","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Hamburg"},{"id":"a3","text":"Moscow"},{"id":"a4","text":"Madrid"}]},"q1816":{"id":"q1816","difficulty":null,"question":"Walt Disney Concert Hall can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Los Angeles","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Breckenridge"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1817":{"id":"q1817","difficulty":0.3705323741,"question":"In which country would you find Pebble Beach Golf Links?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guatemala"}]},"q1818":{"id":"q1818","difficulty":0.3707830567,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sierra Leone","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Buranda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Elbonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Florin"}]},"q1819":{"id":"q1819","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Almaty","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Astana?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kazakhstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bangladesh"}]},"q1820":{"id":"q1820","difficulty":0.3716993285,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Greece","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gambia"}]},"q1821":{"id":"q1821","difficulty":0.3717888599,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Argentina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bulgaria"}]},"q1822":{"id":"q1822","difficulty":0.3721567166,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Central African Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guyana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Luxembourg"}]},"q1823":{"id":"q1823","difficulty":0.3723118486,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Algeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iran"},{"id":"a4","text":"Pakistan"}]},"q1824":{"id":"q1824","difficulty":0.3728138377,"question":"Iraq contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sulaymaniyah Governorate","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Beijing"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jeddah"},{"id":"a4","text":"Faisalabad"}]},"q1825":{"id":"q1825","difficulty":0.3736962787,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Iran?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tokyo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Isfahan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Karaj"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tehran"}]},"q1826":{"id":"q1826","difficulty":0.3740221757,"question":"With how many countries does the United States share land borders?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"2","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"1"},{"id":"a3","text":"3"},{"id":"a4","text":"4"}]},"q1827":{"id":"q1827","difficulty":0.374140796,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Comoros","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Lebanon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Netherlands"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovenia"}]},"q1828":{"id":"q1828","difficulty":0.3746476786,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Libya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q1829":{"id":"q1829","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Giza","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Shubra El Kheima?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Egypt"},{"id":"a4","text":"Benin"}]},"q1830":{"id":"q1830","difficulty":0.3750088646,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Central African Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jordan"}]},"q1831":{"id":"q1831","difficulty":0.09952426319,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vietnam","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Amestris"},{"id":"a3","text":"Aurelia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Elbonia"}]},"q1832":{"id":"q1832","difficulty":0.375578169,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Czech Republic?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paris","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jihozápad"},{"id":"a3","text":"Severovýchod"},{"id":"a4","text":"Prague"}]},"q1833":{"id":"q1833","difficulty":0.3756733661,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Indonesia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iceland"}]},"q1834":{"id":"q1834","difficulty":0.3764953823,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Solomon Islands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Coalition States"},{"id":"a3","text":"Eriador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estovakia"}]},"q1835":{"id":"q1835","difficulty":0.376855612,"question":"Which country's capital is Kiev?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ukraine","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estonia"}]},"q1836":{"id":"q1836","difficulty":0.376855612,"question":"What is the capital of Ukraine?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kiev","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Podgorica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dnipropetrovsk"},{"id":"a4","text":"Oslo"}]},"q1837":{"id":"q1837","difficulty":0.3771016026,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Morocco","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q1838":{"id":"q1838","difficulty":0.3777213913,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jamaica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"}]},"q1839":{"id":"q1839","difficulty":0.3777582364,"question":"What is the capital of Austria?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vienna","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Moscow"},{"id":"a3","text":"Riga"},{"id":"a4","text":"Stockholm"}]},"q1840":{"id":"q1840","difficulty":0.1010564505,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in United States of America?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"San José","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chicago"},{"id":"a3","text":"Los Angeles"},{"id":"a4","text":"Houston"}]},"q1841":{"id":"q1841","difficulty":0.3780089137,"question":"Syria contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Damascus","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dubai"},{"id":"a3","text":"Isfahan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Savar Upazila"}]},"q1842":{"id":"q1842","difficulty":0.3786026961,"question":"Kazakhstan does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Karachi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Almaty"},{"id":"a3","text":"Shymkent"},{"id":"a4","text":"Astana"}]},"q1843":{"id":"q1843","difficulty":0.3787561879,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Equatorial Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Buranda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chernarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Grand Fenwick"}]},"q1844":{"id":"q1844","difficulty":0.3789168271,"question":"São Tomé is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a4","text":"Central African Republic"}]},"q1845":{"id":"q1845","difficulty":0.3798940447,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Fiji","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Lithuania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Qatar"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sierra Leone"}]},"q1846":{"id":"q1846","difficulty":0.3799618241,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Swaziland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Amestris"},{"id":"a3","text":"Borostyria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Buenaventura"}]},"q1847":{"id":"q1847","difficulty":0.3801337177,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Slovenia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mauritius"},{"id":"a3","text":"Singapore"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vanuatu"}]},"q1848":{"id":"q1848","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Diamond Head?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Honolulu","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Berlin"},{"id":"a4","text":" Germany\""}]},"q1849":{"id":"q1849","difficulty":0.3811870548,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Papua New Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Federated States of Micronesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiribati"}]},"q1850":{"id":"q1850","difficulty":0.1017294542,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malaysia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Earthsea"},{"id":"a3","text":"Freedonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Glovania"}]},"q1851":{"id":"q1851","difficulty":0.3814009304,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Netherlands","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mauritius"},{"id":"a4","text":"Montenegro"}]},"q1852":{"id":"q1852","difficulty":0.3819550846,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Peru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mexico"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turkey"}]},"q1853":{"id":"q1853","difficulty":0.3822285681,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Italy","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gabon"}]},"q1854":{"id":"q1854","difficulty":0.3822730396,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Greece","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q1855":{"id":"q1855","difficulty":0.3822797958,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Madagascar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kazakhstan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mongolia"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q1856":{"id":"q1856","difficulty":0.3825521626,"question":"The capital of Sri Lanka is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Colombo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bishkek"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jerusalem"},{"id":"a4","text":"Singapore"}]},"q1857":{"id":"q1857","difficulty":0.3825551023,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gabon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bialya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gérolstein"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kangan"}]},"q1858":{"id":"q1858","difficulty":0.382562344,"question":"Malaysia contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Subang Jaya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bishkek"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bohol"},{"id":"a4","text":"Can Tho"}]},"q1859":{"id":"q1859","difficulty":0.1019503072,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Colombia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Atlantis"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estovakia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Loompa Land"}]},"q1860":{"id":"q1860","difficulty":0.3827871378,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahamas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominican Republic"}]},"q1861":{"id":"q1861","difficulty":0.383013821,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mexico","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Germany"}]},"q1862":{"id":"q1862","difficulty":0.383138612,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burkina Faso","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Peru"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saudi Arabia"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Korea"}]},"q1863":{"id":"q1863","difficulty":0.3832016662,"question":"Which of these is not one the four time zones that apply to the United States?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Phoenix Time Zone","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Central Time Zone"},{"id":"a3","text":"Eastern Time Zone"},{"id":"a4","text":"Pacific Time Zone"}]},"q1864":{"id":"q1864","difficulty":0.3840534002,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rwanda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q1865":{"id":"q1865","difficulty":0.3855107107,"question":"What is the capital of Peru?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lima","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Quito"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brasília"},{"id":"a4","text":"Arequipa"}]},"q1866":{"id":"q1866","difficulty":0.3855107107,"question":"Which country's capital is Lima?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Peru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q1867":{"id":"q1867","difficulty":0.3860033719,"question":"Honduras contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"San Pedro Sula","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chicago"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nassau"},{"id":"a4","text":"Havana"}]},"q1868":{"id":"q1868","difficulty":0.3869089065,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sudan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q1869":{"id":"q1869","difficulty":0.3869260773,"question":"Damascus is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Syria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"China"}]},"q1870":{"id":"q1870","difficulty":0.3869260773,"question":"What is the capital of Syria?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Damascus","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aleppo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Baku"},{"id":"a4","text":"Manama"}]},"q1871":{"id":"q1871","difficulty":0.3871509597,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bulgaria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cape Verde"}]},"q1872":{"id":"q1872","difficulty":0.3871751056,"question":"Vietnam contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Can Tho","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Beijing"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dhi Qar Governorate"},{"id":"a4","text":"Baghdad"}]},"q1873":{"id":"q1873","difficulty":0.3873577511,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malaysia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jordan"}]},"q1874":{"id":"q1874","difficulty":0.3876786138,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Croatia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q1875":{"id":"q1875","difficulty":0.1043008084,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Austria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Blefuscu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Eriador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Fe'ausi"}]},"q1876":{"id":"q1876","difficulty":0.3877494457,"question":"The Himalayas can be found in which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"India","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lebanon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q1877":{"id":"q1877","difficulty":0.3877494457,"question":"The Himalayas are NOT located in which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lebanon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nepal"}]},"q1878":{"id":"q1878","difficulty":0.3886853739,"question":"Ukraine does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bucharest","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dnipropetrovsk"},{"id":"a3","text":"Lviv"},{"id":"a4","text":"Odessa"}]},"q1879":{"id":"q1879","difficulty":0.3888585074,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nigeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kuwait"}]},"q1880":{"id":"q1880","difficulty":0.3888894665,"question":"Which of the following is not in Nashville?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Red Rocks Amphitheatre","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ascend Amphitheater"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bridgestone Arena"},{"id":"a4","text":"The Ryman Auditorium"}]},"q1881":{"id":"q1881","difficulty":0.3896603964,"question":"The Volga River runs through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Russia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q1882":{"id":"q1882","difficulty":0.04917192867,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Japan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bialya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gondor"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hyrule"}]},"q1883":{"id":"q1883","difficulty":0.1046841366,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Syria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aurelia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolumbia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eagleland"}]},"q1884":{"id":"q1884","difficulty":0.3901531207,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saudi Arabia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iran"}]},"q1885":{"id":"q1885","difficulty":0.3909973441,"question":"Qatar contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Doha","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chengdu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Baghdad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mashhad"}]},"q1886":{"id":"q1886","difficulty":0.3918218771,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jamaica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a3","text":"Samoa"},{"id":"a4","text":"Seychelles"}]},"q1887":{"id":"q1887","difficulty":0.3918655928,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Fiji","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"El Salvador"}]},"q1888":{"id":"q1888","difficulty":0.3921786704,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Switzerland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a3","text":"Comoros"},{"id":"a4","text":"Qatar"}]},"q1889":{"id":"q1889","difficulty":0.3928016529,"question":"Finish the African country's name: Republic of Equatorial _______.","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Anguilla"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bermuda"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tobago"}]},"q1890":{"id":"q1890","difficulty":0.3930164863,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United Arab Emirates","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q1891":{"id":"q1891","difficulty":0.3935554154,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Laos","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Canada"}]},"q1892":{"id":"q1892","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Coney Island?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"New York City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Dallas"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1893":{"id":"q1893","difficulty":0.3953469122,"question":"Nairobi is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kenya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burkina Faso"}]},"q1894":{"id":"q1894","difficulty":0.3953469122,"question":"What is the capital of Kenya?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nairobi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mombasa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Yaoundé"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tripoli"}]},"q1895":{"id":"q1895","difficulty":0.3955047414,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"North Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a4","text":"El Salvador"}]},"q1896":{"id":"q1896","difficulty":0.396166034,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Algeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estonia"}]},"q1897":{"id":"q1897","difficulty":0.396335814,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kazakhstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Central African Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ecuador"}]},"q1898":{"id":"q1898","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Can Tho","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Ho Chi Minh City?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Vietnam"},{"id":"a4","text":"Azerbaijan"}]},"q1899":{"id":"q1899","difficulty":0.3969197619,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Somalia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q1900":{"id":"q1900","difficulty":0.3973631975,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Saudi Arabia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mecca","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Isfahan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Damascus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kabul"}]},"q1901":{"id":"q1901","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Dubai","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Abu Dhabi are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"United Arab Emirates"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bahrain"}]},"q1902":{"id":"q1902","difficulty":0.3974749194,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Indonesia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hyderabad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Surabaya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bandung"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bekasi"}]},"q1903":{"id":"q1903","difficulty":0.397480727,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Africa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malaysia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sweden"}]},"q1904":{"id":"q1904","difficulty":0.3978481769,"question":"Syria does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Baghdad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aleppo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Damascus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Homs"}]},"q1905":{"id":"q1905","difficulty":0.3981679112,"question":"Peru does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bogotá","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arequipa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Callao"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lima"}]},"q1906":{"id":"q1906","difficulty":0.398750006,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ethiopia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Georgia"}]},"q1907":{"id":"q1907","difficulty":0.4002834769,"question":"Dallas Arboretum and Botanical Garden can be found in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominican Republic"}]},"q1908":{"id":"q1908","difficulty":0.4016051041,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Yemen?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sana'a","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dubai"},{"id":"a3","text":"Isfahan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bohol"}]},"q1909":{"id":"q1909","difficulty":0.4024014441,"question":"The capital of Hungary is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Budapest","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Berlin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bratislava"},{"id":"a4","text":"Madrid"}]},"q1910":{"id":"q1910","difficulty":0.4024014441,"question":"Which country's capital is Budapest?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hungary","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q1911":{"id":"q1911","difficulty":0.1064888254,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zimbabwe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Caledonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Corto Maltese"},{"id":"a4","text":"Earthsea"}]},"q1912":{"id":"q1912","difficulty":0.4025907436,"question":"What is the capital of Slovakia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bratislava","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Podgorica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dublin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiev"}]},"q1913":{"id":"q1913","difficulty":0.4030858248,"question":"Iran contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Karaj","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aleppo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Baghdad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sulaymaniyah Governorate"}]},"q1914":{"id":"q1914","difficulty":0.4031359892,"question":"Which of the following cities is in United Arab Emirates?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Abu Dhabi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Surabaya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Quezon City"},{"id":"a4","text":"Narayanganj"}]},"q1915":{"id":"q1915","difficulty":0.4031689137,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in South Africa?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Oran","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Durban"},{"id":"a3","text":"Port Elizabeth"},{"id":"a4","text":"Johannesburg"}]},"q1916":{"id":"q1916","difficulty":0.4033626718,"question":"The capital of Colombia is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bogotá","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brasília"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cali"},{"id":"a4","text":"Medellín"}]},"q1917":{"id":"q1917","difficulty":0.4033626718,"question":"Bogotá is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Colombia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q1918":{"id":"q1918","difficulty":0.4037885042,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Peru","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Grenada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Haiti"}]},"q1919":{"id":"q1919","difficulty":0.4038828543,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Algeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tanzania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ukraine"}]},"q1920":{"id":"q1920","difficulty":0.4039467331,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Africa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Morocco"},{"id":"a3","text":"Niger"},{"id":"a4","text":"Syria"}]},"q1921":{"id":"q1921","difficulty":0.4041825906,"question":"What is the capital of Costa Rica?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"San José","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ottawa"},{"id":"a3","text":"St. John's"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kingston"}]},"q1922":{"id":"q1922","difficulty":0.4043442133,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea-Bissau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q1923":{"id":"q1923","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find The Forbidden City?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Beijing","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" China\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Bloomington"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q1924":{"id":"q1924","difficulty":0.40481483,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"China","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q1925":{"id":"q1925","difficulty":0.4055994821,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yemen","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"}]},"q1926":{"id":"q1926","difficulty":0.4060317251,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Peru?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Arequipa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brasília"},{"id":"a4","text":"Medellín"}]},"q1927":{"id":"q1927","difficulty":0.4065194818,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Thailand","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"India"}]},"q1928":{"id":"q1928","difficulty":0.4066266686,"question":"The Florence Cathedral can be found in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Italy","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Lithuania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Republic of Macedonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Slovenia"}]},"q1929":{"id":"q1929","difficulty":0.1066231981,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belize"}]},"q1930":{"id":"q1930","difficulty":0.4066945406,"question":"Which of these rivers is the longest?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Niger River","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Madeira River"},{"id":"a3","text":"Purus River"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yukon River"}]},"q1931":{"id":"q1931","difficulty":0.4067829523,"question":"San Salvador is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"El Salvador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Costa Rica"}]},"q1932":{"id":"q1932","difficulty":0.406819705,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Togo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arstotzka"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estoccia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Freedonia"}]},"q1933":{"id":"q1933","difficulty":0.4068355601,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"El Salvador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estonia"}]},"q1934":{"id":"q1934","difficulty":0.4072764979,"question":"Reykjavik is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iceland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estonia"}]},"q1935":{"id":"q1935","difficulty":0.4078209078,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tunisia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q1936":{"id":"q1936","difficulty":0.4081848638,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea-Bissau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Babar's Kingdom"},{"id":"a3","text":"Holy Britannian Empire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Panau"}]},"q1937":{"id":"q1937","difficulty":0.4083553078,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uruguay","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lithuania"}]},"q1938":{"id":"q1938","difficulty":0.1080003914,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ukraine","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Blefuscu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Buenaventura"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cagliostro"}]},"q1939":{"id":"q1939","difficulty":0.4085754706,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Georgia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ecuador"}]},"q1940":{"id":"q1940","difficulty":0.4085824824,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lithuania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Comoros"}]},"q1941":{"id":"q1941","difficulty":0.4085891627,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Japan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"}]},"q1942":{"id":"q1942","difficulty":0.408696111,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kuwait","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nauru"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saint Lucia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vatican City"}]},"q1943":{"id":"q1943","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Dnipropetrovsk","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Odessa are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ukraine"},{"id":"a4","text":"Andorra"}]},"q1944":{"id":"q1944","difficulty":0.4090335258,"question":"The capital of Bulgaria is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sofia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bratislava"},{"id":"a3","text":"Copenhagen"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dublin"}]},"q1945":{"id":"q1945","difficulty":0.4097067153,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uganda","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nicaragua"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sierra Leone"}]},"q1946":{"id":"q1946","difficulty":0.4099356127,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vietnam","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belarus"}]},"q1947":{"id":"q1947","difficulty":0.409980665,"question":"Guatemala City is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guatemala","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cuba"}]},"q1948":{"id":"q1948","difficulty":0.409980665,"question":"The capital of Guatemala is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guatemala City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kingstown"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ottawa"},{"id":"a4","text":"St. John's"}]},"q1949":{"id":"q1949","difficulty":0.4103403674,"question":"Which European city is nicknamed 'The Eternal City'?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rome","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"London"},{"id":"a3","text":"Madrid"},{"id":"a4","text":"Paris"}]},"q1950":{"id":"q1950","difficulty":0.4104060252,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkey","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Russia"}]},"q1951":{"id":"q1951","difficulty":0.4105116451,"question":"The capital of Croatia is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zagreb","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kiev"},{"id":"a3","text":"London"},{"id":"a4","text":"Moscow"}]},"q1952":{"id":"q1952","difficulty":0.4105116451,"question":"Zagreb is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Croatia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Latvia"}]},"q1953":{"id":"q1953","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Mashhad","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Tehran?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iran"},{"id":"a4","text":"Azerbaijan"}]},"q1954":{"id":"q1954","difficulty":0.4108967851,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Libya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Congo"}]},"q1955":{"id":"q1955","difficulty":0.1092894081,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Indonesia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a4","text":"China"}]},"q1956":{"id":"q1956","difficulty":0.4116362447,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Romania?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"București - Ilfov","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kiev"},{"id":"a3","text":"Riga"},{"id":"a4","text":"Reykjavik"}]},"q1957":{"id":"q1957","difficulty":0.411643197,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saudi Arabia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Germany"}]},"q1958":{"id":"q1958","difficulty":0.4117758859,"question":"Which country's capital is Bucharest?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Romania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bulgaria"}]},"q1959":{"id":"q1959","difficulty":0.4120209799,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Canada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Haiti"}]},"q1960":{"id":"q1960","difficulty":0.4124884988,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belize","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Buenaventura"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chernarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eagleland"}]},"q1961":{"id":"q1961","difficulty":0.4125025963,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malaysia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q1962":{"id":"q1962","difficulty":0.4125791019,"question":"Colombia contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cartagena","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Quito"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brasília"},{"id":"a4","text":"Córdoba"}]},"q1963":{"id":"q1963","difficulty":0.4130133728,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zimbabwe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Central African Republic"}]},"q1964":{"id":"q1964","difficulty":0.4131956517,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Nepal?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Janakpur Zone","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nineveh Governorate"},{"id":"a3","text":"Baghdad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Baku"}]},"q1965":{"id":"q1965","difficulty":0.1105913706,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jamaica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Archenland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Arendelle"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bialya"}]},"q1966":{"id":"q1966","difficulty":0.4133016491,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Angola","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q1967":{"id":"q1967","difficulty":0.4142515367,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Qatar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Luxembourg"}]},"q1968":{"id":"q1968","difficulty":0.4147709736,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Argentina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q1969":{"id":"q1969","difficulty":0.4150848101,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cameroon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Georgia"}]},"q1970":{"id":"q1970","difficulty":0.4151179396,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lebanon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iceland"}]},"q1971":{"id":"q1971","difficulty":0.4151313762,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sierra Leone","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bhutan"}]},"q1972":{"id":"q1972","difficulty":0.4151551997,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q1973":{"id":"q1973","difficulty":0.04949331277,"question":"Mexico City is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mexico","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cuba"}]},"q1974":{"id":"q1974","difficulty":0.111797139,"question":"Disneyland Paris can be found in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"France","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Germany"}]},"q1975":{"id":"q1975","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Jeddah","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Medina?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Saudi Arabia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bahrain"}]},"q1976":{"id":"q1976","difficulty":0.4163827274,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jordan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q1977":{"id":"q1977","difficulty":0.4165881532,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tonga","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bialya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gondor"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ivalice"}]},"q1978":{"id":"q1978","difficulty":0.4166249915,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lesotho","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Qatar"}]},"q1979":{"id":"q1979","difficulty":0.4167083855,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Philippines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mali"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mozambique"},{"id":"a4","text":"Papua New Guinea"}]},"q1980":{"id":"q1980","difficulty":0.4172690334,"question":"The Mekong runs through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Laos","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"India"},{"id":"a3","text":"Malaysia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Nepal"}]},"q1981":{"id":"q1981","difficulty":0.417893906,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malaysia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mali"},{"id":"a3","text":"Somalia"},{"id":"a4","text":"South Sudan"}]},"q1982":{"id":"q1982","difficulty":0.4184264013,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ghana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q1983":{"id":"q1983","difficulty":0.4184850785,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sri Lanka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Liechtenstein"}]},"q1984":{"id":"q1984","difficulty":0.4189648031,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Russia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tirana","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Saint Petersburg"},{"id":"a3","text":"Novosibirsk"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yekaterinburg"}]},"q1985":{"id":"q1985","difficulty":0.1118435687,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Argentina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antegria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolumbia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Idris"}]},"q1986":{"id":"q1986","difficulty":null,"question":"The Tower Bridge can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"London","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" UK\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Ascot"},{"id":"a4","text":" UK\""}]},"q1987":{"id":"q1987","difficulty":0.419524432,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vatican City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a3","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tonga"}]},"q1988":{"id":"q1988","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Bogotá","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Cartagena are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Colombia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Argentina"}]},"q1989":{"id":"q1989","difficulty":0.4198963907,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Belarus","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Burundi"}]},"q1990":{"id":"q1990","difficulty":0.4200241593,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkmenistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ghana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea-Bissau"}]},"q1991":{"id":"q1991","difficulty":0.4203915105,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Togo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a3","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tajikistan"}]},"q1992":{"id":"q1992","difficulty":0.4204165859,"question":"Iraq does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hyderabad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dhi Qar Governorate"},{"id":"a3","text":"Baghdad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sulaymaniyah Governorate"}]},"q1993":{"id":"q1993","difficulty":0.4205801528,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Sri Lanka?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gampaha","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Baku"},{"id":"a3","text":"Damascus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kabul"}]},"q1994":{"id":"q1994","difficulty":0.4206708346,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Germany","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Georgia"}]},"q1995":{"id":"q1995","difficulty":0.1143744925,"question":"The capital of Greece is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Athens","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kiev"},{"id":"a3","text":"Moscow"},{"id":"a4","text":"Prague"}]},"q1996":{"id":"q1996","difficulty":0.4215713425,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Australia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Togo"}]},"q1997":{"id":"q1997","difficulty":0.4217149917,"question":"Canberra is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Australia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kiribati"},{"id":"a4","text":"Marshall Islands"}]},"q1998":{"id":"q1998","difficulty":0.4219658514,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Palau","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Equatorial Kundu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fe'ausi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ixania"}]},"q1999":{"id":"q1999","difficulty":0.4228569141,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritius","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Archenland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Blefuscu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Glovania"}]},"q2000":{"id":"q2000","difficulty":0.4235345943,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kazakhstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"China"}]},"q2001":{"id":"q2001","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Alhambra?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Granada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" Spain\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Barcelona"},{"id":"a4","text":" Spain\""}]},"q2002":{"id":"q2002","difficulty":0.4238920696,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Czech Republic?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jihozápad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dnipropetrovsk"},{"id":"a3","text":"Stockholm"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sud - Muntenia"}]},"q2003":{"id":"q2003","difficulty":0.4240592874,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Sweden","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"France"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lithuania"}]},"q2004":{"id":"q2004","difficulty":0.4241446905,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"San Marino","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolumbia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cagliostro"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chernarus"}]},"q2005":{"id":"q2005","difficulty":null,"question":"Tiger Stadium can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Detroit","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Boston"},{"id":"a4","text":" USA\""}]},"q2006":{"id":"q2006","difficulty":0.4245207031,"question":"The capital of Venezuela is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Caracas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brasília"},{"id":"a4","text":"Maracaibo"}]},"q2007":{"id":"q2007","difficulty":0.4245207031,"question":"Caracas is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Venezuela","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a4","text":"Chile"}]},"q2008":{"id":"q2008","difficulty":0.4249779899,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kuwait","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bulgaria"}]},"q2009":{"id":"q2009","difficulty":0.4256488873,"question":"Which of the following cities is in South Africa?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Port Elizabeth","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"São Tomé"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kumasi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Victoria"}]},"q2010":{"id":"q2010","difficulty":0.4257016532,"question":"In which of these countries could you see the Yellow River?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"China","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"India"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iran"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iraq"}]},"q2011":{"id":"q2011","difficulty":0.4258220299,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Kitts and Nevis","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolumbia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Borginia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Emmeria"}]},"q2012":{"id":"q2012","difficulty":0.4258257733,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iran","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chile"},{"id":"a3","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equatorial Guinea"}]},"q2013":{"id":"q2013","difficulty":0.4259490369,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"São Tomé and Príncipe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aurelia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Genovia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kyrat"}]},"q2014":{"id":"q2014","difficulty":0.1154202726,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Libya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Atlantis"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fe'ausi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kazirstan"}]},"q2015":{"id":"q2015","difficulty":0.4261228179,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kenya","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a4","text":"China"}]},"q2016":{"id":"q2016","difficulty":0.4268364385,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bangladesh","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Indonesia"}]},"q2017":{"id":"q2017","difficulty":0.427355243,"question":"Colombia does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brasília","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a3","text":"Medellín"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cartagena"}]},"q2018":{"id":"q2018","difficulty":0.427367793,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Republic of Ireland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Latvia"}]},"q2019":{"id":"q2019","difficulty":null,"question":"The Terracotta Army can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Xi'an","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" China\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Beijing"},{"id":"a4","text":" China\""}]},"q2020":{"id":"q2020","difficulty":0.427852761,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Syria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guatemala"},{"id":"a3","text":"Latvia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Republic of Ireland"}]},"q2021":{"id":"q2021","difficulty":0.4283251432,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Madagascar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kenya"},{"id":"a4","text":"Poland"}]},"q2022":{"id":"q2022","difficulty":0.4285861803,"question":"Which country's capital is Santo Domingo?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominican Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cuba"}]},"q2023":{"id":"q2023","difficulty":0.1158003664,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mongolia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cagliostro"},{"id":"a3","text":"Drachma"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ivalice"}]},"q2024":{"id":"q2024","difficulty":0.4285861803,"question":"What is the capital of Dominican Republic?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Santo Domingo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Guatemala City"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kingstown"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mexico City"}]},"q2025":{"id":"q2025","difficulty":0.4285932651,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nepal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brunei"}]},"q2026":{"id":"q2026","difficulty":0.4286577696,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ghana"},{"id":"a4","text":"Malawi"}]},"q2027":{"id":"q2027","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Jihozápad","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Prague are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Albania"}]},"q2028":{"id":"q2028","difficulty":0.4289968617,"question":"The capital of Haiti is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Port-au-Prince","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kingstown"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nassau"},{"id":"a4","text":"St. John's"}]},"q2029":{"id":"q2029","difficulty":0.4291861399,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vietnam","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bhutan"}]},"q2030":{"id":"q2030","difficulty":0.430091992,"question":"In which country would you find The Calgary Stampede?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Canada","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guatemala"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jamaica"}]},"q2031":{"id":"q2031","difficulty":0.4301641087,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mongolia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Botswana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a4","text":"El Salvador"}]},"q2032":{"id":"q2032","difficulty":0.430299349,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uzbekistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burundi"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gambia"}]},"q2033":{"id":"q2033","difficulty":null,"question":"In which city would you find Thomas Jefferson Memorial?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Washington","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" D.C."},{"id":"a3","text":" USA\""},{"id":"a4","text":"\"Golden"}]},"q2034":{"id":"q2034","difficulty":0.1159413932,"question":"The Berlin Wall can be found in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Germany","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Iceland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"Luxembourg"}]},"q2035":{"id":"q2035","difficulty":0.4306919687,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Algeria?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Algiers","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nairobi"},{"id":"a3","text":"Wouri"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tripoli"}]},"q2036":{"id":"q2036","difficulty":0.4308900518,"question":"The capital of Romania is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bucharest","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Podgorica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Dublin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Helsinki"}]},"q2037":{"id":"q2037","difficulty":0.4311641796,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Myanmar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nigeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Vietnam"}]},"q2038":{"id":"q2038","difficulty":0.4312340883,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mali","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estonia"}]},"q2039":{"id":"q2039","difficulty":null,"question":"Sagrada Família can be found in which city?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"\"Barcelona","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":" Spain\""},{"id":"a3","text":"\"Granada"},{"id":"a4","text":" Spain\""}]},"q2040":{"id":"q2040","difficulty":0.4314419161,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Egypt","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Madagascar"}]},"q2041":{"id":"q2041","difficulty":0.4317705915,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Croatia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Zagreb","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Munich"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kiev"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lisbon"}]},"q2042":{"id":"q2042","difficulty":0.4321580999,"question":"Tbilisi is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Georgia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lithuania"}]},"q2043":{"id":"q2043","difficulty":0.4322559639,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cape Verde","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a4","text":"Finland"}]},"q2044":{"id":"q2044","difficulty":0.1165968546,"question":"United States of America contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Houston","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mexico City"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ottawa"},{"id":"a4","text":"St. John's"}]},"q2045":{"id":"q2045","difficulty":0.4324330919,"question":"Haiti contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Port-au-Prince","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Calgary"},{"id":"a3","text":"Los Angeles"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guatemala City"}]},"q2046":{"id":"q2046","difficulty":0.4333489337,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Venezuela?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Barquisimeto","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a3","text":"Córdoba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Buenos Aires"}]},"q2047":{"id":"q2047","difficulty":0.4341498515,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tanzania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cape Verde"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q2048":{"id":"q2048","difficulty":0.4342028617,"question":"The capital of Bangladesh is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dhaka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chittagong"},{"id":"a3","text":"Savar Upazila"},{"id":"a4","text":"Damascus"}]},"q2049":{"id":"q2049","difficulty":0.434472017,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Afghanistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iceland"}]},"q2050":{"id":"q2050","difficulty":0.4352902561,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Turkey","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ethiopia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Fiji"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gambia"}]},"q2051":{"id":"q2051","difficulty":0.4354767885,"question":"What is the capital of Armenia?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Yerevan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Podgorica"},{"id":"a3","text":"San Marino"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kiev"}]},"q2052":{"id":"q2052","difficulty":0.4356074255,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Indonesia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"France"},{"id":"a3","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sudan"}]},"q2053":{"id":"q2053","difficulty":0.4357463499,"question":"What is the capital of Turkey?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ankara","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bursa"},{"id":"a3","text":"Podgorica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Adana"}]},"q2054":{"id":"q2054","difficulty":0.1180755341,"question":"The capital of Vatican City is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vatican City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kiev"},{"id":"a3","text":"Monaco"},{"id":"a4","text":"Riga"}]},"q2055":{"id":"q2055","difficulty":0.4361501113,"question":"Port of Spain is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Trinidad and Tobago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belize"}]},"q2056":{"id":"q2056","difficulty":0.4362457402,"question":"Breckenridge Ski Resort can be found in which country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominican Republic"}]},"q2057":{"id":"q2057","difficulty":0.4364362528,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Uzbekistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Myanmar"},{"id":"a3","text":"South Korea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Thailand"}]},"q2058":{"id":"q2058","difficulty":0.4364403812,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kyrgyzstan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Colombia"}]},"q2059":{"id":"q2059","difficulty":0.4366745092,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Suriname","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Arendelle"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ivalice"},{"id":"a4","text":"Metrofulus"}]},"q2060":{"id":"q2060","difficulty":0.4370017597,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in Bangladesh?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nineveh Governorate","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chittagong"},{"id":"a3","text":"Narayanganj"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dhaka"}]},"q2061":{"id":"q2061","difficulty":0.4373074797,"question":"Nassau is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahamas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"El Salvador"}]},"q2062":{"id":"q2062","difficulty":0.4374163891,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iceland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Gabon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Slovenia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Swaziland"}]},"q2063":{"id":"q2063","difficulty":0.1198446487,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kuwait","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Blefuscu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Carpathia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Deltora"}]},"q2064":{"id":"q2064","difficulty":0.4374255229,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ukraine","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belarus"}]},"q2065":{"id":"q2065","difficulty":0.4374667474,"question":"Kuwait City is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kuwait","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"Japan"}]},"q2066":{"id":"q2066","difficulty":0.437508282,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bahamas","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belarus"}]},"q2067":{"id":"q2067","difficulty":0.437605753,"question":"Addis Ababa is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ethiopia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Guinea"}]},"q2068":{"id":"q2068","difficulty":0.437818318,"question":"Nicaragua contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Managua","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"San Pedro Sula"},{"id":"a3","text":"New York City"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mexico City"}]},"q2069":{"id":"q2069","difficulty":0.4380413255,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Somalia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mongolia"}]},"q2070":{"id":"q2070","difficulty":0.4383932014,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Côte d’Ivoire","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antegria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Arstotzka"},{"id":"a4","text":"Babar's Kingdom"}]},"q2071":{"id":"q2071","difficulty":0.4389605124,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iceland"}]},"q2072":{"id":"q2072","difficulty":0.05373998406,"question":"Which country's capital is Moscow?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Russia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Estonia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Georgia"}]},"q2073":{"id":"q2073","difficulty":0.1210791034,"question":"In which country would you find San Francisco Museum of Modern Art?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a4","text":"Dominica"}]},"q2074":{"id":"q2074","difficulty":0.4397329009,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nepal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"}]},"q2075":{"id":"q2075","difficulty":0.4399922046,"question":"Quito is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ecuador","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bolivia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brazil"}]},"q2076":{"id":"q2076","difficulty":0.4399922046,"question":"What is the capital of Ecuador?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Quito","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bogotá"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guayaquil"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brasília"}]},"q2077":{"id":"q2077","difficulty":0.4400158588,"question":"Bangladesh contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dhaka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aleppo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Baghdad"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sulaymaniyah Governorate"}]},"q2078":{"id":"q2078","difficulty":0.440485484,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burundi","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Blefuscu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Buenaventura"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cobra Island"}]},"q2079":{"id":"q2079","difficulty":0.4409368417,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cape Verde","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a4","text":"Djibouti"}]},"q2080":{"id":"q2080","difficulty":0.4412507164,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Burkina Faso","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Morocco"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yemen"}]},"q2081":{"id":"q2081","difficulty":0.4414022641,"question":"Amman is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Jordan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brunei"}]},"q2082":{"id":"q2082","difficulty":0.4421420582,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gambia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Italy"},{"id":"a4","text":"Lithuania"}]},"q2083":{"id":"q2083","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Oran","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Algiers are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Algeria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Angola"}]},"q2084":{"id":"q2084","difficulty":null,"question":"\"In which country can you find the cities Sud - Muntenia","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Bucharest?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Romania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Armenia"}]},"q2085":{"id":"q2085","difficulty":0.4425577374,"question":"In which country would you find Stone Mountain?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"United States of America","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Costa Rica"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cuba"},{"id":"a4","text":"Honduras"}]},"q2086":{"id":"q2086","difficulty":0.4425693497,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Finland","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"France"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hungary"},{"id":"a4","text":"Italy"}]},"q2087":{"id":"q2087","difficulty":0.4427207317,"question":"Port-au-Prince is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Haiti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Antigua and Barbuda"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahamas"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belize"}]},"q2088":{"id":"q2088","difficulty":0.1223843596,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hungary","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Glubbdubdrib"},{"id":"a3","text":"Grenyarnia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kinakuta"}]},"q2089":{"id":"q2089","difficulty":0.4432066101,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nigeria","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Kenya"},{"id":"a3","text":"Norway"},{"id":"a4","text":"Oman"}]},"q2090":{"id":"q2090","difficulty":0.4433721861,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bosnia and Herzegovina","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Ecuador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gabon"}]},"q2091":{"id":"q2091","difficulty":0.4439854445,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Malta","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q2092":{"id":"q2092","difficulty":0.444215267,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Jordan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Amman","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chongqing"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bandung"},{"id":"a4","text":"Caloocan"}]},"q2093":{"id":"q2093","difficulty":0.4442319626,"question":"What is the only country in the world that doesn't have a rectangular flag?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nepal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"Libya"},{"id":"a4","text":"Swaziland"}]},"q2094":{"id":"q2094","difficulty":0.4443910207,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Hungary","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Guinea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Switzerland"}]},"q2095":{"id":"q2095","difficulty":0.444523911,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Equatorial Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Dominican Republic"},{"id":"a3","text":"North Korea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Togo"}]},"q2096":{"id":"q2096","difficulty":0.4446256046,"question":"Beirut is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Lebanon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a4","text":"Israel"}]},"q2097":{"id":"q2097","difficulty":0.1224962843,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Africa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Aurelia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Equatorial Kundu"},{"id":"a4","text":"Eriador"}]},"q2098":{"id":"q2098","difficulty":0.4446256046,"question":"What is the capital of Lebanon?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Beirut","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Manila"},{"id":"a3","text":"Jerusalem"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jakarta"}]},"q2099":{"id":"q2099","difficulty":0.4448169772,"question":"What is the capital of Algeria?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Algiers","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Oran"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cairo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tlemcen"}]},"q2100":{"id":"q2100","difficulty":0.4449864796,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Côte d’Ivoire","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iran"},{"id":"a4","text":"Kuwait"}]},"q2101":{"id":"q2101","difficulty":0.4451328189,"question":"Myanmar does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Kabul","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Mandalay"},{"id":"a3","text":"Naypyidaw"},{"id":"a4","text":"Yangon"}]},"q2102":{"id":"q2102","difficulty":0.4452030003,"question":"Which two colors are on the flag of Ukraine?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Blue and yellow","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Green and white"},{"id":"a3","text":"White and black"},{"id":"a4","text":"White and red"}]},"q2103":{"id":"q2103","difficulty":0.4452713598,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iraq","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brunei"}]},"q2104":{"id":"q2104","difficulty":0.4455998679,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Timor-Leste","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Archenland"},{"id":"a3","text":"Aurelia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brobdingnag"}]},"q2105":{"id":"q2105","difficulty":0.4460922574,"question":"Kazakhstan contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Shymkent","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Beijing"},{"id":"a3","text":"Chittagong"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mandalay"}]},"q2106":{"id":"q2106","difficulty":0.4468606484,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Djibouti","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q2107":{"id":"q2107","difficulty":0.4472053714,"question":"Which of the following cities is NOT in South Korea?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dhaka","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Icheon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Seoul"},{"id":"a4","text":"Busan"}]},"q2108":{"id":"q2108","difficulty":0.4473684211,"question":"The Indus River does NOT run through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iran","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"China"},{"id":"a3","text":"India"},{"id":"a4","text":"Pakistan"}]},"q2109":{"id":"q2109","difficulty":0.4477674114,"question":"Antananarivo is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Madagascar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a3","text":"Eritrea"},{"id":"a4","text":"Ethiopia"}]},"q2110":{"id":"q2110","difficulty":0.4480049488,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Tajikistan?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dushanbe","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Nineveh Governorate"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bishkek"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jeddah"}]},"q2111":{"id":"q2111","difficulty":0.123645896,"question":"The capital of Italy is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Rome","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Paris"},{"id":"a3","text":"Prague"},{"id":"a4","text":"Turin"}]},"q2112":{"id":"q2112","difficulty":0.4487410623,"question":"Mongolia contains which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Ulaanbaatar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chengdu"},{"id":"a3","text":"Mandalay"},{"id":"a4","text":"Caloocan"}]},"q2113":{"id":"q2113","difficulty":0.4487459943,"question":"Which of these countries has the smallest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mali","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Australia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Indonesia"},{"id":"a4","text":"United States of America"}]},"q2114":{"id":"q2114","difficulty":0.4492991948,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Venezuela","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Andorra"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a4","text":"Belarus"}]},"q2115":{"id":"q2115","difficulty":0.4497469157,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mongolia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iran"}]},"q2116":{"id":"q2116","difficulty":0.4500565439,"question":"Venezuela does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Paramaribo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Maracaibo"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barquisimeto"},{"id":"a4","text":"Caracas"}]},"q2117":{"id":"q2117","difficulty":0.4503935093,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Iran","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Estonia"}]},"q2118":{"id":"q2118","difficulty":0.4504120975,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Guinea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Armenia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Greece"}]},"q2119":{"id":"q2119","difficulty":0.4506051054,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Oman","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Canada"},{"id":"a3","text":"Croatia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Czech Republic"}]},"q2120":{"id":"q2120","difficulty":0.4509480132,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Belarus?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Minsk","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"İzmir"},{"id":"a3","text":"Moscow"},{"id":"a4","text":"Prague"}]},"q2121":{"id":"q2121","difficulty":0.4510993203,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest population?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Afghanistan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Romania"}]},"q2122":{"id":"q2122","difficulty":0.4513782223,"question":"Doha is the capital of what country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Qatar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Afghanistan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brunei"},{"id":"a4","text":"Iraq"}]},"q2123":{"id":"q2123","difficulty":0.4513782223,"question":"What is the capital of Qatar?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Doha","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Beijing"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bishkek"},{"id":"a4","text":"Manama"}]},"q2124":{"id":"q2124","difficulty":0.4514770164,"question":"Baku is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Azerbaijan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Cambodia"},{"id":"a3","text":"China"},{"id":"a4","text":"Indonesia"}]},"q2125":{"id":"q2125","difficulty":0.4515644418,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Somalia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Cameroon"},{"id":"a4","text":"Congo"}]},"q2126":{"id":"q2126","difficulty":0.4524950376,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Cuba","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Georgia"},{"id":"a3","text":"Germany"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q2127":{"id":"q2127","difficulty":0.1240558718,"question":"The capital of Japan is...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Tokyo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Damascus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Singapore"},{"id":"a4","text":"Phnom Penh"}]},"q2128":{"id":"q2128","difficulty":0.4526342762,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Vatican City","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Benin"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brazil"},{"id":"a4","text":"Central African Republic"}]},"q2129":{"id":"q2129","difficulty":0.4528075344,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Saint Vincent and the Grenadines","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Borostyria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Holy Britannian Empire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Markovia"}]},"q2130":{"id":"q2130","difficulty":0.4537815293,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Brunei","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Babar's Kingdom"},{"id":"a3","text":"Brobdingnag"},{"id":"a4","text":"Equatorial Kundu"}]},"q2131":{"id":"q2131","difficulty":0.4539021861,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nicaragua","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"France"}]},"q2132":{"id":"q2132","difficulty":0.4543980666,"question":"Saudi Arabia does NOT contain which of the following cities?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Baghdad","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Jeddah"},{"id":"a3","text":"Hofuf"},{"id":"a4","text":"Riyadh"}]},"q2133":{"id":"q2133","difficulty":0.1240558718,"question":"Tokyo is the capital of...","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Japan","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bangladesh"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bhutan"}]},"q2134":{"id":"q2134","difficulty":null,"question":"\"Dhi Qar Governorate","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":" and Baghdad are cities in which country?\"","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"[NULL]"},{"id":"a3","text":"Iraq"},{"id":"a4","text":"Brunei"}]},"q2135":{"id":"q2135","difficulty":0.4552088463,"question":"Which of these countries has the largest area?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"France","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Ghana"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kyrgyzstan"},{"id":"a4","text":"Paraguay"}]},"q2136":{"id":"q2136","difficulty":0.4553269794,"question":"Which countries entered in European Union in 2007?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Bulgaria and Romania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria and Italy"},{"id":"a3","text":"France and Germany"},{"id":"a4","text":"Sweden and Norway"}]},"q2137":{"id":"q2137","difficulty":0.4555618785,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Dominican Republic","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Azerbaijan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bulgaria"},{"id":"a4","text":"Denmark"}]},"q2138":{"id":"q2138","difficulty":0.4558624836,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Nepal","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belarus"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"France"}]},"q2139":{"id":"q2139","difficulty":0.4560996584,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Atlantis"},{"id":"a3","text":"Bialya"},{"id":"a4","text":"Borduria"}]},"q2140":{"id":"q2140","difficulty":0.4561123707,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Korea","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Belize"},{"id":"a3","text":"El Salvador"},{"id":"a4","text":"Gabon"}]},"q2141":{"id":"q2141","difficulty":0.4561266074,"question":"What is the English name for Gebel-al-Tarik in North Africa?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gibraltar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Malta"},{"id":"a3","text":"Montserrat"},{"id":"a4","text":"The Balearic Islands"}]},"q2142":{"id":"q2142","difficulty":0.456476047,"question":"What country is this?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Mauritius","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Burkina Faso"},{"id":"a4","text":"Cameroon"}]},"q2143":{"id":"q2143","difficulty":0.4565842924,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Costa Rica","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bhutan"},{"id":"a3","text":"Finland"},{"id":"a4","text":"Morocco"}]},"q2144":{"id":"q2144","difficulty":0.1259784903,"question":"Which of the following is a real country?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Venezuela","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Borduria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Borginia"},{"id":"a4","text":"Drachma"}]},"q2145":{"id":"q2145","difficulty":0.4567871094,"question":"What is Europe's busiest shopping street?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Oxford Street","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Avenue Montaigne"},{"id":"a3","text":"Kaufingerstrasse"},{"id":"a4","text":"Regent Street"}]},"q2146":{"id":"q2146","difficulty":0.4571558684,"question":"Which of the following cities is in Uruguay?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Montevideo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Quito"},{"id":"a3","text":"Guayaquil"},{"id":"a4","text":"Córdoba"}]},"q2147":{"id":"q2147","difficulty":0.4579787875,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest north?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Albania","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Argentina"},{"id":"a3","text":"Barbados"},{"id":"a4","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"}]},"q2148":{"id":"q2148","difficulty":0.4582447197,"question":"In which African country is the administrative capital Pretoria?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"South Africa","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Djibouti"},{"id":"a3","text":"Tanzania"},{"id":"a4","text":"Tunisia"}]},"q2149":{"id":"q2149","difficulty":0.4585308057,"question":"The Congo River does NOT run through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Liberia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Angola"},{"id":"a3","text":"Democratic Republic of the Congo"},{"id":"a4","text":"Rwanda"}]},"q2150":{"id":"q2150","difficulty":0.4585308057,"question":"The Congo River runs through which of these countries?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Gabon","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Chad"},{"id":"a3","text":"Côte d’Ivoire"},{"id":"a4","text":"Mali"}]},"q2151":{"id":"q2151","difficulty":0.4586486826,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Trinidad and Tobago","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Bahrain"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"Jordan"}]},"q2152":{"id":"q2152","difficulty":0.4596716157,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Myanmar","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Austria"},{"id":"a3","text":"Denmark"},{"id":"a4","text":"Hungary"}]},"q2153":{"id":"q2153","difficulty":0.4599618714,"question":"Which of these countries is furthest south?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Colombia","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Albania"},{"id":"a3","text":"Czech Republic"},{"id":"a4","text":"France"}]},"q2154":{"id":"q2154","difficulty":0.4602741769,"question":"What is the capital of Madagascar?","answers":[{"id":"a1","text":"Antananarivo","correct":true},{"id":"a2","text":"Khartoum"},{"id":"a3","text":"Nouakchott"},{"id":"a4","text":"Bamako"}]}}
